[{"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_0", "question": "When did Valentino Lazaro start playing for Austria national under-16 football team the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2011", "1996", "1999", "2002"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_0_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1", "question": "When did Domenico Caso start playing for ACF Fiorentina the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1951", "1971", "1949", "1941"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_2", "question": "When did Marco Ferrante start playing for S.S.C. Napoli the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1988", "id": "1988"}], "options": ["1988", "1960", "1963", "1961"], "target_options": "1988", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_2_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_3", "question": "When did Federico Bonazzoli start playing for Italy national under-17 football team the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2006", "2012", "1998", "2003"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_3_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_4", "question": "When did Luciano Bodini start playing for U.S. Cremonese the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1966", "1967", "1968", "1974"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_4_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_5", "question": "When did Mame Thiam start playing for Inter Milan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2004", "2007", "2011", "1997"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_5_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_6", "question": "When did Annibale Frossi stop playing for Como 1907 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1945", "2001", "2002", "1992"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_6_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_7", "question": "When did Orazio Rancati start playing for Inter Milan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1958", "id": "1958"}], "options": ["1944", "1952", "1954", "1958"], "target_options": "1958", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_7_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_8", "question": "When did Vampeta start playing for E.C. Vit√≥ria the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1993", "1968", "1974", "1971"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_8_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_9", "question": "When did Silvio Pietroboni stop playing for S.G. Gallaratese A.S.D. the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1934", "id": "1934"}], "options": ["1989", "1934", "1980", "1991"], "target_options": "1934", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_9_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_10", "question": "When did Filippo Mancini start playing for Inter Milan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["2004", "1993", "2002", "2008"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_10_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_11", "question": "When did George V stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1936", "id": "1936"}], "options": ["1938", "1931", "1936", "1941"], "target_options": "1936", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_11_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_12", "question": "When did Prithvi Narayan Shah stop holding King of Nepal the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1775", "id": "1775"}], "options": ["1777", "1781", "1779", "1775"], "target_options": "1775", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_12_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_13", "question": "When did Princess Zhejue stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["405", "397", "403", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_13_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_14", "question": "When did Po Tisuntiraidapuran stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1793", "id": "1793"}], "options": ["1793", "1798", "1795", "1785"], "target_options": "1793", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_14_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_15", "question": "When did Wuffa of East Anglia stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "578", "id": "578"}], "options": ["580", "579", "581", "578"], "target_options": "578", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_15_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_16", "question": "When did Po Tisuntiraidapuran stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1793", "id": "1793"}], "options": ["1785", "1795", "1793", "1797"], "target_options": "1793", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_16_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_17", "question": "When did Ibrahim Njoya stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1933", "id": "1933"}], "options": ["1938", "1935", "1933", "1928"], "target_options": "1933", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_17_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_18", "question": "When did Gwangjong of Goryeo stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "975", "id": "975"}], "options": ["977", "979", "969", "975"], "target_options": "975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_18_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_19", "question": "When did Dokka Umarov stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2013", "2015", "2008", "2017"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_19_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_20", "question": "When did Alexander I of Scotland stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1124", "id": "1124"}], "options": ["1129", "1124", "1126", "1122"], "target_options": "1124", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_20_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_21", "question": "When did Napoleon Louis Bonaparte stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1810", "id": "1810"}], "options": ["1836", "1832", "1810", "1833"], "target_options": "1810", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_21_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_22", "question": "When did Ngawang Namgyal start holding monarch the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1512", "id": "1512"}], "options": ["1504", "1512", "1505", "1507"], "target_options": "1512", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_22_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_23", "question": "When did Empress Matilda stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1141", "id": "1141"}], "options": ["1171", "1141", "1169", "1163"], "target_options": "1141", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_23_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_24", "question": "When did Gongyang of Goryeo stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1392", "id": "1392"}], "options": ["1396", "1392", "1387", "1397"], "target_options": "1392", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_24_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_25", "question": "When did Edward the Elder stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "924", "id": "924"}], "options": ["924", "928", "918", "926"], "target_options": "924", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_25_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_26", "question": "When did Donyo stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1512", "id": "1512"}], "options": ["1512", "1508", "1514", "1516"], "target_options": "1512", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_26_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_27", "question": "When did Chungnyeol stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1308", "id": "1308"}], "options": ["1301", "1311", "1308", "1310"], "target_options": "1308", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_27_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_28", "question": "When did Talorgan II stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "782", "id": "782"}], "options": ["784", "785", "782", "777"], "target_options": "782", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_28_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_29", "question": "When did Chungnyeol stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1308", "id": "1308"}], "options": ["1308", "1310", "1311", "1301"], "target_options": "1308", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_29_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_30", "question": "When did Ngwane V stop holding monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1899", "id": "1899"}], "options": ["1904", "1894", "1901", "1899"], "target_options": "1899", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_30_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_31", "question": "When did Levi Woodbury stop holding Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1851", "id": "1851"}], "options": ["1850", "1851", "1853", "1854"], "target_options": "1851", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_31_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_32", "question": "When did Jacques Delors start holding member of the European Parliament the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1960", "1955", "1962", "1979"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_32_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_33", "question": "When did Jacques Santer start holding Deputy of the Chamber of Deputies of Luxembourg the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1958", "1979", "1959", "1955"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_33_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_34", "question": "When did Ward Hunt stop holding Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1891", "1885", "1888", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_34_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_35", "question": "When did William Paterson stop holding Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1806", "id": "1806"}], "options": ["1809", "1808", "1813", "1806"], "target_options": "1806", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_35_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_36", "question": "When did Willis Van Devanter stop holding Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1937", "id": "1937"}], "options": ["1937", "1945", "1936", "1943"], "target_options": "1937", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_36_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_37", "question": "When did David Souter start holding New Hampshire Attorney General the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1976", "id": "1976"}], "options": ["1986", "1985", "1976", "1980"], "target_options": "1976", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_37_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_38", "question": "When did Abe Fortas stop holding Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1969", "id": "1969"}], "options": ["1978", "1984", "1969", "1986"], "target_options": "1969", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_38_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_39", "question": "When did Thomas Campbell Clark stop holding Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1972", "1979", "1982", "1967"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_39_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_40", "question": "When did Joseph Story stop holding Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1845", "id": "1845"}], "options": ["1845", "1850", "1851", "1847"], "target_options": "1845", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_40_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_41", "question": "When did Edward Douglass White stop holding Chief Justice of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1921", "id": "1921"}], "options": ["1923", "1921", "1920", "1926"], "target_options": "1921", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_41_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_42", "question": "When did Romano Prodi start holding Italian Minister of Economic Development the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1978", "id": "1978"}], "options": ["1974", "1978", "1966", "1972"], "target_options": "1978", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_42_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_43", "question": "When did Sonia Sotomayor start holding Judge of the United States District Court for the Southern District of New York the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1992", "1979", "1982", "1969"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_43_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_44", "question": "When did Stanley Forman Reed stop holding Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1957", "id": "1957"}], "options": ["1983", "1957", "1976", "1982"], "target_options": "1957", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_44_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_45", "question": "When did Charles Evans Hughes stop holding Chief Justice of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1941", "id": "1941"}], "options": ["1947", "1952", "1950", "1941"], "target_options": "1941", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_45_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_46", "question": "When did William Johnson stop holding Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1834", "id": "1834"}], "options": ["1834", "1836", "1826", "1837"], "target_options": "1834", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_46_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_47", "question": "When did Samuel Blatchford stop holding Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1893", "id": "1893"}], "options": ["1897", "1893", "1887", "1895"], "target_options": "1893", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_47_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_48", "question": "When did Mike Rogers start holding Federal Bureau of Investigation the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1984", "1989", "1971", "1981"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_48_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_49", "question": "When did William Henry Moody stop holding Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1910", "id": "1910"}], "options": ["1918", "1920", "1919", "1910"], "target_options": "1910", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_49_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_50", "question": "When did Horace Gray stop holding Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1902", "id": "1902"}], "options": ["1902", "1904", "1905", "1896"], "target_options": "1902", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_50_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_51", "question": "When did John Hessin Clarke stop holding Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1922", "id": "1922"}], "options": ["1947", "1940", "1922", "1949"], "target_options": "1922", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_51_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_52", "question": "When did Sicco Mansholt stop holding President of the European Commission the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1973", "id": "1973"}], "options": ["1991", "1973", "1997", "1998"], "target_options": "1973", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_52_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_53", "question": "When did Brett Kavanaugh start holding Judge of the United States Court of Appeals for the D.C. Circuit the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["1995", "1997", "1994", "2006"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_53_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_54", "question": "When did Samuel Alito start holding United States Attorney for the District of New Jersey the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1987", "id": "1987"}], "options": ["1975", "1968", "1987", "1976"], "target_options": "1987", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_54_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_55", "question": "When did Jean Rey stop holding member of the European Parliament the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1980", "id": "1980"}], "options": ["1985", "1983", "1987", "1980"], "target_options": "1980", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_55_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_56", "question": "When did Howell Edmunds Jackson stop holding Associate Justice of the Supreme Court of the United States the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1895", "id": "1895"}], "options": ["1892", "1895", "1897", "1898"], "target_options": "1895", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_56_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_57", "question": "When did Flemming Lentfer receive Order of the Dannebrog the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2005", "2013", "1998", "2004"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_57_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_58", "question": "When did Hubert Lynes receive Order of Leopold the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1944", "1947", "2024", "1934"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_58_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_59", "question": "When did Markkleeberg receive Fairtrade Town the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2012", "2011", "2015", "2014"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_59_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_60", "question": "When did Ainring receive Fairtrade Town the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2003", "2009", "2015", "2007"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_60_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_61", "question": "When did An Unbelievable Story of Rape receive Pulitzer Prize the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2008", "2016", "2006", "2007"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_61_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_62", "question": "When did Semyon Kosberg receive Lenin Prize the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1967", "2024", "1965", "1968"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_62_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_63", "question": "When did Alexander III of Russia receive Order of the Dannebrog the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1888", "2024", "1896", "1897"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_63_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_64", "question": "When did Frederick II of Prussia receive Order of the Black Eagle the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1786", "id": "1786"}], "options": ["1786", "1788", "1785", "1789"], "target_options": "1786", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_64_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_65", "question": "When did Arthur Balfour receive Order of Merit the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1935", "1932", "1923"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_65_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_66", "question": "When did Bill Pickering receive Order of New Zealand the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1997", "2006", "2024", "2009"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_66_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_67", "question": "When did Daizhan Cheng receive IEEE Fellow the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2006", "2003", "2001", "1998"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_67_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_68", "question": "When did Rafael Hui receive Gold Bauhinia Star the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1968", "1963", "1969", "1998"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_68_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_69", "question": "When did Graz receive European Capital of Culture the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2003", "2004", "1993", "2002"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_69_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_70", "question": "When did Athens receive European Capital of Culture the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1985", "id": "1985"}], "options": ["1985", "1978", "1983", "1981"], "target_options": "1985", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_70_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_71", "question": "When did Bonn Minster receive minor basilica the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1956", "id": "1956"}], "options": ["1937", "1947", "1956", "1948"], "target_options": "1956", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_71_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_72", "question": "When did Rita Moreno receive Academy Award for Best Supporting Actress the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1993", "1960", "1983", "1994"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_72_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_73", "question": "When did Sherlock Holmes receive Legion of Honour the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1894", "id": "1894"}], "options": ["1889", "1877", "1894", "1887"], "target_options": "1894", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_73_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_74", "question": "When did Ivan Selifonov receive Hero of the Soviet Union the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2020", "2021", "2017", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_74_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_75", "question": "When did Henry VIII of England receive Prince of Wales the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1551", "1545", "1549", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_75_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_76", "question": "When did Ivan Selifonov receive Hero of the Soviet Union the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2016", "2019", "2024", "2021"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_76_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_77", "question": "When did Central Volga Krai receive Order of Lenin the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1938", "2024", "1935", "1941"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_77_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_78", "question": "When did Rexford Tugwell stop working for University of Chicago the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1957", "id": "1957"}], "options": ["1972", "1981", "1983", "1957"], "target_options": "1957", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_78_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_79", "question": "When did Patricia Harris start working for Bloomberg L.P. the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1996", "1994", "1993", "1991"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_79_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_80", "question": "When did John Celivergos Zachos stop working for Cooper Union the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1898", "id": "1898"}], "options": ["1900", "1893", "1901", "1898"], "target_options": "1898", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_80_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_81", "question": "When did George Forsythe stop working for Stanford University the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1972", "id": "1972"}], "options": ["1968", "1972", "1976", "1974"], "target_options": "1972", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_81_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_82", "question": "When did Cornelius Lanczos stop working for Dublin Institute for Advanced Studies the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1971", "1976", "1974", "1979"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_82_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_83", "question": "When did Thomas Pynchon start working for Boeing the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1953", "1947", "1950", "1960"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_83_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_84", "question": "When did Robert Love start working for Google the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2007", "2004", "1997", "2006"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_84_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_85", "question": "When did Laurent Rossi start working for Renault S.A. the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["2000", "1993", "1981", "1991"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_85_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_86", "question": "When did Tianyi Geng start working for Google the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2016", "2007", "2009", "2012"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_86_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_87", "question": "When did Manu Cornet start working for Google the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["1996", "2005", "2006", "2007"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_87_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_88", "question": "When did David Weinberger start working for Google the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2016", "2018", "2017", "2020"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_88_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_89", "question": "When did Arnnon Geshuri start working for Google the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["2002", "2004", "1997", "2003"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_89_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_90", "question": "When did Jarkko Oikarinen start working for Capricode the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["1961", "1960", "1952", "2003"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_90_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_91", "question": "When did Quoc Viet Le start working for Google the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2007", "2004", "2013", "2000"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_91_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_92", "question": "When did Ifeoma Ozoma start working for Google the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2008", "2009", "2015", "2010"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_92_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_93", "question": "When did Samy Bengio start working for Idiap Research Institute the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1977", "1999", "1975", "1980"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_93_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_94", "question": "When did West Yorkshire start being located in England the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1974", "1970", "1959", "1968"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_94_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_95", "question": "When did Prince Edward Island start being located in Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1873", "id": "1873"}], "options": ["1871", "1865", "1876", "1873"], "target_options": "1873", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_95_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_96", "question": "When did East Midlands start being located in England the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1986", "1991", "1988", "1994"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_96_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_97", "question": "When did Cleveland start being located in England the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1966", "1961", "1969", "1974"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_97_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_98", "question": "When did preserved county of Wales start being located in Wales the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1989", "1994", "1997", "1996"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_98_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_99", "question": "When did Humberside stop being located in Yorkshire and the Humber the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1998", "1992", "2001", "1996"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_99_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_100", "question": "When did Budapest start being located in Hungary the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1979", "1986", "1988", "1989"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_100_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_101", "question": "When did West Lothian start being located in Lothian the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1953", "1958", "1961", "1975"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_101_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_102", "question": "When did Newry and Mourne District Council start being located in Northern Ireland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1973", "id": "1973"}], "options": ["1961", "1973", "1970", "1968"], "target_options": "1973", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_102_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_103", "question": "When did Moray start being located in Grampian the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1975", "1961", "1967", "1969"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_103_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_104", "question": "When did City of Edinburgh start being located in Lothian the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1960", "1965", "1967", "1975"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_104_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_105", "question": "When did Vale of Glamorgan start being located in Wales the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1970", "1962", "1967", "1996"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_105_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_106", "question": "When did County Down start being located in Northern Ireland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1921", "id": "1921"}], "options": ["1917", "1922", "1921", "1919"], "target_options": "1921", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_106_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_107", "question": "When did Edinburgh start being located in Scotland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1707", "id": "1707"}], "options": ["1695", "1707", "1697", "1699"], "target_options": "1707", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_107_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_108", "question": "When did East Lothian start being located in Lothian the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1965", "1959", "1975", "1963"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_108_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_109", "question": "When did Wismar start being located in Sweden the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1632", "id": "1632"}], "options": ["1626", "1629", "1632", "1618"], "target_options": "1632", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_109_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_110", "question": "When did Rhode Island start being located in United States of America the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1790", "id": "1790"}], "options": ["1780", "1774", "1783", "1790"], "target_options": "1790", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_110_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_111", "question": "When did Galicia start being located in Kingdom of Galicia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "409", "id": "409"}], "options": ["1924", "1927", "409", "1929"], "target_options": "409", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_111_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_112", "question": "When did Alytus District Municipality start being located in Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1953", "id": "1953"}], "options": ["1953", "1923", "1931", "1928"], "target_options": "1953", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_112_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_113", "question": "When did Kaunas District Municipality start being located in Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1955", "id": "1955"}], "options": ["1945", "1955", "1951", "1953"], "target_options": "1955", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_113_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_114", "question": "When did Kaunas District Municipality start being located in Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1955", "id": "1955"}], "options": ["1948", "1955", "1951", "1945"], "target_options": "1955", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_114_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_115", "question": "When did Jurbarkas District Municipality start being located in Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1953", "id": "1953"}], "options": ["1904", "1953", "1901", "1893"], "target_options": "1953", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_115_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_116", "question": "When did Skuodas District Municipality start being located in Klaipeda Oblast the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1950", "id": "1950"}], "options": ["1950", "1931", "1929", "1923"], "target_options": "1950", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_116_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_117", "question": "When did Kalisz Voivodeship stop being located in Poland the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["2000", "2001", "1998", "1995"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_117_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_118", "question": "When did Ignalina District Municipality start being located in Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1953", "id": "1953"}], "options": ["1939", "1948", "1953", "1947"], "target_options": "1953", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_118_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_119", "question": "When did Vilnius District Municipality start being located in Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1953", "id": "1953"}], "options": ["1921", "1917", "1924", "1953"], "target_options": "1953", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_119_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_120", "question": "When did Skuodas District Municipality start being located in Klaipeda Oblast the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1950", "id": "1950"}], "options": ["1943", "1950", "1952", "1949"], "target_options": "1950", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_120_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_121", "question": "When did Vilnius District Municipality start being located in Lithuanian Soviet Socialist Republic the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1953", "id": "1953"}], "options": ["1940", "1941", "1953", "1938"], "target_options": "1953", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_121_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_122", "question": "When did Alexander Neckam stop educating at Paris the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1182", "id": "1182"}], "options": ["1219", "1220", "1182", "1212"], "target_options": "1182", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_122_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_123", "question": "When did Pierre de Villiers start educating at Prytan√©e National Militaire the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1973", "id": "1973"}], "options": ["1965", "1968", "1973", "1956"], "target_options": "1973", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_123_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_124", "question": "When did Rodolphe Belmer start educating at Prytan√©e National Militaire the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1980", "id": "1980"}], "options": ["1980", "1975", "1973", "1967"], "target_options": "1980", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_124_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_125", "question": "When did Pierre Schill start educating at Prytan√©e National Militaire the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1984", "id": "1984"}], "options": ["1974", "1984", "1973", "1975"], "target_options": "1984", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_125_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_126", "question": "When did Louis Rossel stop educating at √âcole polytechnique the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1864", "id": "1864"}], "options": ["1864", "1875", "1873", "1869"], "target_options": "1864", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_126_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_127", "question": "When did Arnaud de La Grange start educating at Prytan√©e National Militaire the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1979", "1978", "1971", "1982"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_127_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_128", "question": "When did Olivier de Germay start educating at Prytan√©e National Militaire the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1978", "id": "1978"}], "options": ["1972", "1976", "1978", "1974"], "target_options": "1978", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_128_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_129", "question": "When did censorship start happending to TikTok the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2018", "2004", "2013", "2014"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_129_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_130", "question": "When did censorship start happending to TikTok the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2011", "2013", "2014", "2018"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_130_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_131", "question": "When did Basic Law for the Federal Republic of Germany start happending to Germany the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1948", "1951", "1943", "1949"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_131_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_132", "question": "When did construction start happending to NTT Docomo Yoyogi Building the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1999", "1997", "1995", "1990"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_132_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_133", "question": "When did keel laying start happending to HMS Erebus the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1824", "id": "1824"}], "options": ["1835", "1829", "1824", "1837"], "target_options": "1824", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_133_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_134", "question": "When did construction start happending to Panathenaic Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "-329", "id": "-329"}], "options": ["-329", "1988", "1998", "1997"], "target_options": "-329", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_134_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_135", "question": "When did spaceflight end happending to Vasily Lazarev the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1982", "2024", "1992", "1995"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_135_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_136", "question": "When did spaceflight start happending to Yusaku Maezawa the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2021", "id": "2021"}], "options": ["2009", "2013", "2012", "2021"], "target_options": "2021", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_136_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_137", "question": "When did spaceflight start happending to Mark Shuttleworth the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["2002", "1999", "2001", "2004"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_137_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_138", "question": "When did spaceflight start happending to Richard Garriott the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["1998", "1999", "2000", "2008"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_138_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_139", "question": "When did spaceflight start happending to Mamoru Mohri the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1992", "1991", "2001", "1998"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_139_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_140", "question": "When did spaceflight start happending to Mamoru Mohri the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1989", "1992", "1985", "1987"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_140_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_141", "question": "When did spaceflight start happending to Klim Shipenko the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2021", "id": "2021"}], "options": ["2012", "2019", "2021", "2020"], "target_options": "2021", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_141_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_142", "question": "When did spaceflight start happending to Dennis Tito the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["2001", "1991", "1996", "1998"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_142_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_143", "question": "When did spaceflight start happending to Yulia Peresild the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2021", "id": "2021"}], "options": ["2019", "2021", "2015", "2022"], "target_options": "2021", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_143_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_144", "question": "When did Caspar Schmalkalden work at Gotha the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1668", "id": "1668"}], "options": ["1675", "1668", "1677", "1665"], "target_options": "1668", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_144_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_145", "question": "When did Konstantin Somov work at United States of America the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1932", "1941", "2024", "1944"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_145_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_146", "question": "When did Theodor de Bry work at England the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1596", "1600", "1602"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_146_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_147", "question": "When did Eva Zeisel work at United States of America the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1997", "2014", "2007", "2013"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_147_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_148", "question": "When did George Soros work at United Kingdom the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1929", "1946", "1922", "1931"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_148_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_149", "question": "When did Anders Zorn work at United States of America the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1925", "1913", "2024", "1922"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_149_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_150", "question": "When did George Herriman work at United States of America the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1944", "id": "1944"}], "options": ["1946", "1948", "1940", "1944"], "target_options": "1944", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_150_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_151", "question": "When did Thomas Eakins work at Spain the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1910", "2024", "1920", "1918"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_151_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_152", "question": "When did Dominique Vivant work at Spain the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1824", "1827", "1828"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_152_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_153", "question": "When did Nikolai Sheremetev work at England the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1811", "1814", "1805", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_153_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_154", "question": "When did Lee Miller work at Great Britain the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1977", "id": "1977"}], "options": ["1981", "1969", "1977", "1979"], "target_options": "1977", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_154_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_155", "question": "When did Henry VII of England work at London the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1509", "id": "1509"}], "options": ["1514", "1507", "1509", "1511"], "target_options": "1509", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_155_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_156", "question": "When did Josep Maria Subirachs work at Belgium the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2006", "2016", "2024", "2017"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_156_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_157", "question": "When did Guillaume Apollinaire work at Paris the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1918", "id": "1918"}], "options": ["1916", "1922", "1918", "1920"], "target_options": "1918", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_157_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_158", "question": "When did Paolo Troubetzkoy work at Kingdom of Italy the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1938", "id": "1938"}], "options": ["1938", "1937", "1943", "1940"], "target_options": "1938", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_158_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_159", "question": "When did PZL Mielec owned by PZL the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1938", "id": "1938"}], "options": ["1936", "1938", "1933", "1925"], "target_options": "1938", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_159_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_160", "question": "When did Ainola owned by Finland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1972", "id": "1972"}], "options": ["1963", "1967", "1972", "1969"], "target_options": "1972", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_160_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_161", "question": "When did The Great Masturbator owned by Spain the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1990", "1989", "1981", "1992"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_161_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_162", "question": "When did Mount Vernon owned by George Washington the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1754", "id": "1754"}], "options": ["1749", "1745", "1746", "1754"], "target_options": "1754", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_162_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_163", "question": "When did Saint George owned by Italy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1856", "id": "1856"}], "options": ["1856", "1854", "1841", "1851"], "target_options": "1856", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_163_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_164", "question": "When did The Tempest owned by Italy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1856", "id": "1856"}], "options": ["1845", "1856", "1847", "1846"], "target_options": "1856", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_164_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_165", "question": "When did Hotel Bellevue Palace owned by Swiss National Bank the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1976", "id": "1976"}], "options": ["1955", "1950", "1976", "1958"], "target_options": "1976", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_165_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_166", "question": "When did Palais Wilson owned by League of Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1920", "id": "1920"}], "options": ["1907", "1920", "1898", "1910"], "target_options": "1920", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_166_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_167", "question": "When did Bank of England owned by United Kingdom the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1946", "1936", "1939", "1933"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_167_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_168", "question": "When did Dante and Virgil in Hell owned by France the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["1995", "2000", "2003", "2010"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_168_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_169", "question": "When did The Magpie owned by France the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1984", "id": "1984"}], "options": ["1975", "1981", "1984", "1983"], "target_options": "1984", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_169_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_170", "question": "When did Palau join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1985", "1986", "1983", "1994"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_170_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_171", "question": "When did Yemen join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1930", "id": "1930"}], "options": ["1921", "1930", "1916", "1923"], "target_options": "1930", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_171_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_172", "question": "When did Turkmenistan join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1991", "1989", "1992", "1987"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_172_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_173", "question": "When did Pakistan join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1947", "id": "1947"}], "options": ["1947", "1943", "1944", "1945"], "target_options": "1947", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_173_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_174", "question": "When did Kiribati join Asian Development Bank the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1954", "1947", "1956", "1974"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_174_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_175", "question": "When did Afghanistan join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1928", "id": "1928"}], "options": ["1913", "1928", "1915", "1906"], "target_options": "1928", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_175_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_176", "question": "When did Philippines join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1912", "id": "1912"}], "options": ["1896", "1906", "1912", "1903"], "target_options": "1912", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_176_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_177", "question": "When did Tuvalu join Commonwealth of Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1978", "id": "1978"}], "options": ["1966", "1961", "1978", "1965"], "target_options": "1978", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_177_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_178", "question": "When did Ecuador join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1880", "id": "1880"}], "options": ["1876", "1879", "1881", "1880"], "target_options": "1880", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_178_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_179", "question": "When did Honduras join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1879", "id": "1879"}], "options": ["1819", "1879", "1821", "1820"], "target_options": "1879", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_179_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_180", "question": "When did Bolivia join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1886", "id": "1886"}], "options": ["1862", "1886", "1873", "1871"], "target_options": "1886", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_180_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_181", "question": "When did Colombia join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1881", "id": "1881"}], "options": ["1881", "1883", "1871", "1880"], "target_options": "1881", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_181_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_182", "question": "When did Indonesia join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1877", "id": "1877"}], "options": ["1877", "1824", "1826", "1821"], "target_options": "1877", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_182_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_183", "question": "When did Nauru join Commonwealth of Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1968", "id": "1968"}], "options": ["1961", "1954", "1968", "1962"], "target_options": "1968", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_183_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_184", "question": "When did The Gambia join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1965", "id": "1965"}], "options": ["1962", "1954", "1965", "1961"], "target_options": "1965", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_184_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_185", "question": "When did Singapore join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1965", "id": "1965"}], "options": ["1958", "1965", "1961", "1948"], "target_options": "1965", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_185_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_186", "question": "When did Grenada join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1959", "1966", "1969", "1974"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_186_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_187", "question": "When did East Timor join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["2002", "1990", "2005", "2000"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_187_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_188", "question": "When did Belize join Caribbean Community the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1921", "1974", "1926", "1927"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_188_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_189", "question": "When did Senegal join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1961", "1959", "1960", "1950"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_189_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_190", "question": "When did Cyprus join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1947", "1950", "1952", "1960"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_190_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_191", "question": "When did Commonwealth of the Philippines join United Nations the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1948", "1951", "1939", "1946"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_191_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_192", "question": "When did Republic of Ireland join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1923", "id": "1923"}], "options": ["1923", "1903", "1895", "1906"], "target_options": "1923", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_192_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_193", "question": "When did Albania join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1922", "id": "1922"}], "options": ["1915", "1913", "1922", "1905"], "target_options": "1922", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_193_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_194", "question": "When did Czech Republic join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1986", "1993", "1985", "1975"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_194_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_195", "question": "When did Kingdom of Burundi join United Nations the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1968", "1971", "1966", "1959"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_195_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_196", "question": "When did Monaco join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1908", "id": "1908"}], "options": ["1890", "1908", "1888", "1880"], "target_options": "1908", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_196_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_197", "question": "When did United States of America join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1875", "id": "1875"}], "options": ["1875", "1860", "1861", "1856"], "target_options": "1875", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_197_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_198", "question": "When did Turkey join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1866", "id": "1866"}], "options": ["1857", "1866", "1853", "1860"], "target_options": "1866", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_198_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_199", "question": "When did Uzbekistan join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1992", "1991", "1990", "1989"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_199_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_200", "question": "When did Australia join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1878", "id": "1878"}], "options": ["1869", "1864", "1878", "1872"], "target_options": "1878", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_200_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_201", "question": "When did Iraq join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1928", "id": "1928"}], "options": ["1916", "1928", "1917", "1918"], "target_options": "1928", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_201_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_202", "question": "When did Guatemala join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1881", "id": "1881"}], "options": ["1865", "1881", "1870", "1871"], "target_options": "1881", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_202_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_203", "question": "When did Dominican Republic join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1880", "id": "1880"}], "options": ["1826", "1824", "1880", "1822"], "target_options": "1880", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_203_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_204", "question": "When did Ethiopia join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1908", "id": "1908"}], "options": ["1883", "1884", "1908", "1877"], "target_options": "1908", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_204_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_205", "question": "When did Iceland join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1906", "id": "1906"}], "options": ["1906", "1888", "1892", "1893"], "target_options": "1906", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_205_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_206", "question": "When did North Macedonia join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1993", "1985", "1983", "1987"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_206_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_207", "question": "When did Ukraine join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1937", "1927", "1940", "1945"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_207_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_208", "question": "When did Bahrain join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1971", "1965", "1964", "1959"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_208_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_209", "question": "When did United Arab Emirates join Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1934", "1933", "1930", "1967"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_209_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_210", "question": "When did Kenya join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1963", "id": "1963"}], "options": ["1963", "1959", "1954", "1962"], "target_options": "1963", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_210_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_211", "question": "When did Angola join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1976", "id": "1976"}], "options": ["1976", "1965", "1972", "1975"], "target_options": "1976", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_211_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_212", "question": "When did Sierra Leone join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1961", "id": "1961"}], "options": ["1961", "1956", "1947", "1959"], "target_options": "1961", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_212_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_213", "question": "When did Mali join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1952", "1953", "1960", "1949"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_213_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_214", "question": "When did Vanuatu join Organisation internationale de la Francophonie the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1972", "1974", "1979", "1966"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_214_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_215", "question": "When did Sudan join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1956", "id": "1956"}], "options": ["1956", "1946", "1939", "1947"], "target_options": "1956", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_215_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_216", "question": "When did Republic of China join United Nations the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1942", "1951", "1952", "1971"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_216_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_217", "question": "When did Laos join UNESCO the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1951", "id": "1951"}], "options": ["1941", "1942", "1933", "1951"], "target_options": "1951", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_217_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_218", "question": "When did Israel join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1948", "id": "1948"}], "options": ["1943", "1934", "1948", "1941"], "target_options": "1948", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_218_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_219", "question": "When did Russia join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1866", "id": "1866"}], "options": ["1845", "1849", "1866", "1846"], "target_options": "1866", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_219_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_220", "question": "When did Latvia join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1921", "id": "1921"}], "options": ["1895", "1886", "1921", "1898"], "target_options": "1921", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_220_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_221", "question": "When did Croatia join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1987", "1992", "1984", "1976"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_221_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_222", "question": "When did Slovakia join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1983", "1993", "1980", "1984"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_222_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_223", "question": "When did Tajikistan join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1990", "1993", "1985", "1992"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_223_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_224", "question": "When did Chile join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1881", "id": "1881"}], "options": ["1872", "1878", "1880", "1881"], "target_options": "1881", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_224_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_225", "question": "When did Federation of Malaya join United Nations the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1963", "id": "1963"}], "options": ["1968", "1963", "1955", "1965"], "target_options": "1963", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_225_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_226", "question": "When did Thailand join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1883", "id": "1883"}], "options": ["1855", "1864", "1883", "1865"], "target_options": "1883", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_226_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_227", "question": "When did Cuba join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1902", "id": "1902"}], "options": ["1857", "1856", "1902", "1846"], "target_options": "1902", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_227_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_228", "question": "When did Germany join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1866", "id": "1866"}], "options": ["1855", "1845", "1866", "1852"], "target_options": "1866", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_228_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_229", "question": "When did Malta join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1964", "id": "1964"}], "options": ["1957", "1951", "1960", "1964"], "target_options": "1964", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_229_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_230", "question": "When did Montenegro join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["1996", "1998", "1990", "2006"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_230_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_231", "question": "When did Portugal join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1866", "id": "1866"}], "options": ["1849", "1866", "1858", "1859"], "target_options": "1866", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_231_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_232", "question": "When did Central African Empire join United Nations the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1980", "1983", "1979", "1981"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_232_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_233", "question": "When did Indonesia join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1877", "id": "1877"}], "options": ["1859", "1877", "1862", "1864"], "target_options": "1877", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_233_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_234", "question": "When did United Arab Republic join United Nations the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1971", "1974", "1964", "1973"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_234_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_235", "question": "When did Belgium join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1866", "id": "1866"}], "options": ["1859", "1868", "1866", "1863"], "target_options": "1866", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_235_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_236", "question": "When did Brazil join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1877", "id": "1877"}], "options": ["1857", "1864", "1877", "1865"], "target_options": "1877", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_236_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_237", "question": "When did Central African Republic join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1956", "1953", "1960", "1951"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_237_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_238", "question": "When did Mauritius join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1968", "id": "1968"}], "options": ["1968", "1966", "1965", "1956"], "target_options": "1968", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_238_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_239", "question": "When did Uganda join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1962", "id": "1962"}], "options": ["1961", "1964", "1962", "1952"], "target_options": "1962", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_239_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_240", "question": "When did Algeria join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1907", "id": "1907"}], "options": ["1884", "1889", "1886", "1907"], "target_options": "1907", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_240_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_241", "question": "When did Guyana join Caribbean Free Trade Association the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1965", "id": "1965"}], "options": ["1964", "1955", "1965", "1963"], "target_options": "1965", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_241_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_242", "question": "When did Fiji join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1970", "id": "1970"}], "options": ["1970", "1965", "1967", "1957"], "target_options": "1970", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_242_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_243", "question": "When did South Africa join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1910", "id": "1910"}], "options": ["1895", "1886", "1898", "1910"], "target_options": "1910", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_243_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_244", "question": "When did Guinea join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1958", "id": "1958"}], "options": ["1957", "1947", "1956", "1958"], "target_options": "1958", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_244_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_245", "question": "When did Central African Republic join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1953", "1948", "1960", "1955"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_245_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_246", "question": "When did Rwanda join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1962", "id": "1962"}], "options": ["1962", "1961", "1958", "1964"], "target_options": "1962", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_246_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_247", "question": "When did Papua New Guinea join Asian Development Bank the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1961", "1971", "1956", "1963"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_247_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_248", "question": "When did Tunisia join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1888", "id": "1888"}], "options": ["1889", "1888", "1887", "1877"], "target_options": "1888", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_248_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_249", "question": "When did Commonwealth realm of Guyana join United Nations the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1970", "id": "1970"}], "options": ["1972", "1970", "1973", "1968"], "target_options": "1970", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_249_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_250", "question": "When did Nigeria join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1954", "1951", "1947", "1960"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_250_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_251", "question": "When did Niger join United Nations the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1961", "1957", "1960", "1955"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_251_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_252", "question": "When did Antigua and Barbuda join Caribbean Free Trade Association the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1965", "id": "1965"}], "options": ["1956", "1953", "1952", "1965"], "target_options": "1965", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_252_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_253", "question": "When did Federated States of Micronesia join Asian Development Bank the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1989", "1976", "1990", "1986"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_253_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_254", "question": "When did New Zealand join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1878", "id": "1878"}], "options": ["1859", "1857", "1854", "1878"], "target_options": "1878", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_254_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_255", "question": "When did India join International Telecommunication Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1869", "id": "1869"}], "options": ["1857", "1869", "1853", "1859"], "target_options": "1869", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_255_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_256", "question": "When did Venezuela join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1880", "id": "1880"}], "options": ["1872", "1880", "1875", "1870"], "target_options": "1880", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_256_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_257", "question": "When did Republic of Ireland join Universal Postal Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1923", "id": "1923"}], "options": ["1918", "1923", "1917", "1920"], "target_options": "1923", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_257_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_258", "question": "When did Belgium become part of European Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1958", "id": "1958"}], "options": ["1945", "1958", "1955", "1956"], "target_options": "1958", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_258_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_259", "question": "When did Belgium become part of European Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1958", "id": "1958"}], "options": ["1958", "1946", "1947", "1944"], "target_options": "1958", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_259_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_260", "question": "When did Hungary become part of Organization of Turkic States the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2004", "2018", "2016", "2013"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_260_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_261", "question": "When did Spain become part of Schengen Area the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1995", "id": "1995"}], "options": ["1984", "1991", "1995", "1994"], "target_options": "1995", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_261_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_262", "question": "When did Norway become part of Council of Europe the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1930", "1932", "1933", "1949"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_262_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_263", "question": "When did Canada become part of NATO the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1919", "1920", "1949", "1914"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_263_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_264", "question": "When did Spain become part of Schengen Area the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1995", "id": "1995"}], "options": ["1973", "1982", "1980", "1995"], "target_options": "1995", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_264_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_265", "question": "When did Canada become part of NATO the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1947", "1941", "1944", "1949"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_265_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_266", "question": "When did Norway become part of Council of Europe the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1949", "1947", "1945", "1941"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_266_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_267", "question": "When did United States of America cease to part of Allies of the First World War the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1922", "1920", "1919"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_267_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_268", "question": "When did Portugal become part of Community of Portuguese Language Countries the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1994", "1996", "1992", "1983"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_268_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_269", "question": "When did Ukraine become part of Commonwealth of Independent States the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1985", "1991", "1974", "1984"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_269_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_270", "question": "When did Uzbekistan become part of Collective Security Treaty Organization the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1992", "1988", "1978", "1989"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_270_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_271", "question": "When did Russia become part of Eurasian Customs Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2007", "1994", "2004", "2010"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_271_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_272", "question": "When did Russia become part of Eurasian Economic Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2007", "2010", "1998", "2014"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_272_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_273", "question": "When did Ukraine become part of Commonwealth of Independent States the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1991", "1986", "1977", "1985"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_273_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_274", "question": "When did North Macedonia become part of Stabilisation and Association Agreement the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["2002", "2004", "2005", "1992"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_274_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_275", "question": "When did Google become part of Alliance for Open Media the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2009", "2006", "2004", "2015"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_275_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_276", "question": "When did Saint Lucia cease to part of British Windward Islands the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1958", "id": "1958"}], "options": ["1950", "1958", "1963", "1960"], "target_options": "1958", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_276_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_277", "question": "When did Algeria become part of Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1969", "id": "1969"}], "options": ["1962", "1964", "1969", "1966"], "target_options": "1969", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_277_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_278", "question": "When did Indonesia become part of ASEAN the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1958", "1964", "1967", "1968"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_278_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_279", "question": "When did Hungary become part of Organization of Turkic States the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2017", "2006", "2018", "2015"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_279_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_280", "question": "When did Annapolis Royal start belonging to Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1867", "id": "1867"}], "options": ["1867", "1861", "1862", "1855"], "target_options": "1867", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_280_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_281", "question": "When did BritBox start belonging to United States of America the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2009", "2017", "2002", "2011"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_281_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_282", "question": "When did Vision Eternel start belonging to Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["1987", "2007", "1999", "1997"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_282_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_283", "question": "When did Eurocorps start belonging to France the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1967", "1974", "1992", "1972"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_283_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_284", "question": "When did Urup start belonging to Dutch East India Company the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1643", "id": "1643"}], "options": ["1852", "1854", "1643", "1847"], "target_options": "1643", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_284_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_285", "question": "When did Broutona start belonging to Russian Empire the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1855", "id": "1855"}], "options": ["1850", "1846", "1855", "1851"], "target_options": "1855", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_285_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_286", "question": "When did Kurilsk start belonging to Russian Empire the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1736", "id": "1736"}], "options": ["1736", "1722", "1725", "1721"], "target_options": "1736", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_286_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_287", "question": "When did Simushir start belonging to Russian Empire the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1855", "id": "1855"}], "options": ["1834", "1843", "1855", "1845"], "target_options": "1855", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_287_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_288", "question": "When did Kunashir Island start belonging to Empire of Japan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1866", "id": "1866"}], "options": ["1847", "1844", "1866", "1845"], "target_options": "1866", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_288_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_289", "question": "When did Sakhalin start belonging to Russian Empire the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1875", "id": "1875"}], "options": ["1875", "1855", "1865", "1862"], "target_options": "1875", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_289_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_290", "question": "When did Balthazar start belonging to Black people the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1400", "id": "1400"}], "options": ["1390", "1400", "1394", "1393"], "target_options": "1400", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_290_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_291", "question": "When did Ilya Ponomarev start belonging to Communist Party of the Russian Federation the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["2002", "1982", "1972", "1985"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_291_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_292", "question": "When did Jerzy Buzek start belonging to Solidarity the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1980", "id": "1980"}], "options": ["1972", "1971", "1980", "1974"], "target_options": "1980", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_292_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_293", "question": "When did Oleksandr Vilkul start belonging to Party of Regions the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["2004", "2005", "1997", "2001"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_293_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_294", "question": "When did Viktor Yanukovych start belonging to Communist Party of Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1980", "id": "1980"}], "options": ["1996", "2001", "1980", "1999"], "target_options": "1980", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_294_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_295", "question": "When did Konstantin Pavlov start belonging to Party of Regions the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["1997", "2005", "1996", "1987"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_295_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_296", "question": "When was the last time that Anatoliy Fedorchuk was not belonging to Our Land?", "answer": [{"label": "2020", "id": "2020"}], "options": ["2022", "2015", "2020", "2018"], "target_options": "2020", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_296_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_297", "question": "When did Valentin Demidov start belonging to Party of Regions the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["1997", "2005", "1998", "1995"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_297_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_298", "question": "When did Olga Kovitidi start belonging to Party of Regions the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2010", "1991", "2001", "2003"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_298_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_299", "question": "When did Yuriy Boyko start belonging to Labour Ukraine the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["2005", "2000", "1999", "2001"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_299_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_300", "question": "When was the last time that Wilhelm Kopf was not belonging to Nazi Party?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2003", "1996", "2004", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_300_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_301", "question": "When was the last time that Hans Weisbach was not belonging to Nazi Party?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1963", "1953", "2024", "1965"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_301_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_302", "question": "When did Soon Cho become the head of government of Seoul the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1995", "id": "1995"}], "options": ["1995", "1983", "1973", "1985"], "target_options": "1995", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_302_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_303", "question": "When did Edmund Barton become the head of government of Australia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1901", "id": "1901"}], "options": ["1881", "1880", "1870", "1901"], "target_options": "1901", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_303_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_304", "question": "When did Pascal Koupaki become the head of government of Benin the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2006", "2004", "1995", "2011"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_304_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_305", "question": "When did Tung Chee Hwa become the head of government of Hong Kong the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1978", "1997", "1969", "1976"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_305_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_306", "question": "When did Karl Renner become the head of government of Austria the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1945", "1939", "1934", "1942"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_306_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_307", "question": "When did Todor Zhivkov become the head of government of Sofia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1941", "1949", "1952", "1947"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_307_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_308", "question": "When did George Washington become the head of government of United States of America the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1789", "id": "1789"}], "options": ["1785", "1789", "1786", "1779"], "target_options": "1789", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_308_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_309", "question": "When did Edmund Barton become the head of government of Australia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1901", "id": "1901"}], "options": ["1901", "1900", "1897", "1890"], "target_options": "1901", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_309_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_310", "question": "When did Mohammad Hatta stop the head of government of First Hatta Cabinet the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1950", "1949", "1941", "1953"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_310_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_311", "question": "When did Huang Ta-chou become the head of government of Taipei the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1971", "1961", "1990", "1968"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_311_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_312", "question": "When did Huang Ta-chou become the head of government of Taipei the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1990", "1974", "1977", "1970"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_312_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_313", "question": "When did Vitali Klitschko become the head of government of Kyiv the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2008", "2015", "2012", "2014"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_313_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_314", "question": "When did Steve Bullock become the head of government of Montana the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2015", "2005", "2013", "2010"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_314_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_315", "question": "When did Antoni Mart√≠ become the head of government of Andorra the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2012", "2011", "2010", "2002"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_315_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_316", "question": "When did Jussi Pajunen become the head of government of Helsinki the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["1989", "1986", "1979", "2005"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_316_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_317", "question": "When did Alun Michael become the head of government of Wales the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1999", "1998", "1988", "2001"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_317_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_318", "question": "When did Boris Yeltsin become the head of government of Russia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1983", "1991", "1989", "1988"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_318_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_319", "question": "When did V√°clav Klaus become the head of government of Czech Republic the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1993", "1990", "1980", "1995"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_319_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_320", "question": "When did Huang Ta-chou become the head of government of Taipei City Government the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1977", "1976", "1990", "1975"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_320_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_321", "question": "When did V√°clav Klaus become the head of government of Czech Republic the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1991", "1993", "1988", "1990"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_321_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_322", "question": "When did Huang Ta-chou become the head of government of Taipei City Government the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1990", "1979", "1982", "1981"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_322_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_323", "question": "When did Boris Yeltsin become the head of government of Russia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1990", "1989", "1991", "1983"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_323_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_324", "question": "When did George Washington become the head of government of United States of America the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1789", "id": "1789"}], "options": ["1789", "1775", "1773", "1768"], "target_options": "1789", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_324_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_325", "question": "When did Ihor Palytsia become the head of government of Odesa Oblast the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2008", "2000", "2007", "2014"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_325_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_326", "question": "When did Vitold Fokin stop the head of government of Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1987", "1991", "1995", "1993"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_326_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_327", "question": "When did Tadeusz Mazowiecki become the head of government of Poland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1989", "1965", "1962", "1953"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_327_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_328", "question": "When did Konrad Adenauer become the head of government of Germany the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1925", "1949", "1920", "1923"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_328_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_329", "question": "When did John A. Macdonald become the head of government of Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1867", "id": "1867"}], "options": ["2005", "1867", "2003", "2001"], "target_options": "1867", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_329_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_330", "question": "When did Jawaharlal Nehru become the head of government of India the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1947", "id": "1947"}], "options": ["1939", "1946", "1945", "1947"], "target_options": "1947", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_330_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_331", "question": "When did Jawaharlal Nehru stop the head of government of Dominion of India the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1950", "id": "1950"}], "options": ["1950", "1953", "1952", "1949"], "target_options": "1950", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_331_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_332", "question": "When did Konrad Adenauer become the head of government of Germany the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1945", "1943", "1949", "1948"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_332_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_333", "question": "When did David Cameron become the head of government of United Kingdom the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2010", "1998", "2009", "2007"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_333_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_334", "question": "When did Boris Yeltsin stop the head of government of Russian Soviet Federative Socialist Republic the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1993", "1992", "1989", "1995"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_334_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_335", "question": "When did Jawaharlal Nehru become the head of government of India the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1947", "id": "1947"}], "options": ["1943", "1944", "1947", "1936"], "target_options": "1947", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_335_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_336", "question": "When did Tadeusz Mazowiecki become the head of government of Poland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1975", "1989", "1972", "1969"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_336_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_337", "question": "When did Alcide De Gasperi become the head of government of Italy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1941", "1946", "1936", "1944"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_337_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_338", "question": "When did Vladimir Lenin stop the head of government of Russian Socialist Federative Soviet Republic the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1924", "id": "1924"}], "options": ["1924", "1929", "1916", "1926"], "target_options": "1924", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_338_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_339", "question": "When did Alcide De Gasperi become the head of government of Italy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1922", "1921", "1946", "1912"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_339_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_340", "question": "When did Ernst Reuter become the head of government of Berlin the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1948", "id": "1948"}], "options": ["1938", "1948", "1935", "1930"], "target_options": "1948", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_340_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_341", "question": "When did Angela Merkel stop the head of government of Second Merkel cabinet the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2013", "2012", "2016", "2015"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_341_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_342", "question": "When did Donald Tusk become the head of government of Third Cabinet of Donald Tusk the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2023", "id": "2023"}], "options": ["2019", "2021", "2023", "2015"], "target_options": "2023", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_342_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_343", "question": "When did Louis-Basile de Bernage become the head of government of Paris the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1743", "id": "1743"}], "options": ["1976", "1743", "1977", "1971"], "target_options": "1743", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_343_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_344", "question": "When did Tansu √áiller become the head of government of Turkey the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1984", "1996", "1992", "1993"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_344_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_345", "question": "When did Lara Fabian acquire Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1981", "1996", "1992", "1989"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_345_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_346", "question": "When did Kenny Omega acquire Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1983", "id": "1983"}], "options": ["1978", "1972", "1983", "1981"], "target_options": "1983", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_346_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_347", "question": "When did Dennis Kwok acquire Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1978", "id": "1978"}], "options": ["1976", "1973", "1978", "1967"], "target_options": "1978", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_347_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_348", "question": "When did Alex Trebek renounce Canada the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2022", "2018", "2024", "2020"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_348_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_349", "question": "When did Shenae Grimes acquire Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1973", "1989", "1983", "1985"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_349_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_350", "question": "When did Victor Li acquire British Hong Kong the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1964", "id": "1964"}], "options": ["1964", "1944", "1941", "1936"], "target_options": "1964", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_350_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_351", "question": "When did Alvin Yeung acquire British Hong Kong the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1981", "id": "1981"}], "options": ["1981", "1973", "1971", "1967"], "target_options": "1981", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_351_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_352", "question": "When did Rafael Bienvenido Cruz acquire Cuba the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1939", "id": "1939"}], "options": ["1928", "1926", "1930", "1939"], "target_options": "1939", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_352_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_353", "question": "When did Nellie Chin Yu acquire Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1976", "id": "1976"}], "options": ["1971", "1968", "1976", "1965"], "target_options": "1976", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_353_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_354", "question": "When did Liu Qikun acquire Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1988", "id": "1988"}], "options": ["1988", "1983", "1982", "1977"], "target_options": "1988", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_354_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_355", "question": "When did Evgeny Bareev acquire Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2004", "2015", "2005", "2006"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_355_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_356", "question": "When did Tom Green acquire Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1969", "1971", "1968", "1962"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_356_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_357", "question": "When did Aliocha Schneider acquire Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1993", "1991", "1994", "1987"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_357_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_358", "question": "When did Anastasia Lin acquire People's Republic of China the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1985", "1979", "1990", "1983"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_358_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_359", "question": "When did Ted Cruz acquire Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1970", "id": "1970"}], "options": ["1964", "1961", "1970", "1953"], "target_options": "1970", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_359_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_360", "question": "When did Patty Tsai acquire Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1974", "1983", "1993", "1985"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_360_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_361", "question": "When did Eddie Peng acquire Taiwan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1934", "1982", "1924", "1932"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_361_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_362", "question": "When did Jasmin Glaesser acquire Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2011", "2002", "2008", "2009"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_362_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_363", "question": "When did Richard Lee Armstrong renounce Canada the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1995", "1993", "1988", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_363_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_364", "question": "When did Frank Stallone renounce Italy the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2014", "2008", "2011", "2013"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_364_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_365", "question": "When did Li Hak Kan renounce Canada the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2022", "2020", "2024", "2018"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_365_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_366", "question": "When did Mike Schreiner acquire Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2000", "1998", "2007", "1988"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_366_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_367", "question": "When did Lauren Holly acquire Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["1996", "2002", "2008", "2003"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_367_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_368", "question": "When did Nina Dobrev acquire Bulgaria the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1973", "1980", "1982", "1989"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_368_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_369", "question": "When did Beno√Æt Potier become the chairperson of Air Liquide the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2000", "2006", "2004", "2001"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_369_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_370", "question": "When did Theodor Heuss become the chairperson of Free Democratic Party the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1948", "id": "1948"}], "options": ["1939", "1938", "1942", "1948"], "target_options": "1948", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_370_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_371", "question": "When did Kurt Schumacher become the chairperson of Social Democratic Party of Germany the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1939", "1929", "1938", "1946"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_371_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_372", "question": "When did Erich K√∂hler become the chairperson of German Bundestag the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1928", "1949", "1931", "1919"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_372_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_373", "question": "When did Thomas Dehler become the chairperson of Federal Ministry of Justice the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1949", "1945", "1944", "1948"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_373_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_374", "question": "When did Richard Stallman become the chairperson of Free Software Foundation the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1985", "id": "1985"}], "options": ["1977", "1975", "1966", "1985"], "target_options": "1985", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_374_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_375", "question": "When did Ingmar Bergman become the chairperson of European Film Academy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1989", "1985", "1981", "1984"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_375_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_376", "question": "When did Konrad Adenauer become the chairperson of Christian Democratic Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1950", "id": "1950"}], "options": ["1945", "1951", "1948", "1950"], "target_options": "1950", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_376_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_377", "question": "When did Jacques Attali become the chairperson of European Bank for Reconstruction and Development the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1991", "1974", "1975", "1964"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_377_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_378", "question": "When did Fritz Sch√§ffer become the chairperson of Federal Ministry of Finance the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1949", "1934", "1927", "1936"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_378_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_379", "question": "When did Jean-Luc M√©lenchon become the chairperson of La France Insoumise group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2009", "2017", "2011", "2006"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_379_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_380", "question": "When did Walter Scheel become the chairperson of Federal Ministry for Economic Cooperation and Development the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1961", "id": "1961"}], "options": ["1951", "1954", "1947", "1961"], "target_options": "1961", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_380_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_381", "question": "When did Jean-Marie Le Pen become the chairperson of National Rally the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1972", "id": "1972"}], "options": ["1970", "1967", "1972", "1964"], "target_options": "1972", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_381_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_382", "question": "When did Sergei Shoigu become the chairperson of United Russia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["1984", "1982", "1981", "2001"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_382_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_383", "question": "When did Kathleen Lonsdale become the chairperson of British Science Association the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1964", "1962", "1952", "1967"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_383_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_384", "question": "When did Jacint Borr√†s i Manuel cease the chairperson of Democratic Convergence of Catalonia the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2022", "2017", "2019", "2018"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_384_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_385", "question": "When did Theodor Blank become the chairperson of Federal Ministry of Defence of Germany the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1955", "id": "1955"}], "options": ["1937", "1939", "1955", "1934"], "target_options": "1955", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_385_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_386", "question": "When did Mao Zedong become the chairperson of Chinese Communist Party the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1935", "1945", "1938", "1926"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_386_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_387", "question": "When did Theodor Heuss become the chairperson of Free Democratic Party the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1948", "id": "1948"}], "options": ["1948", "1926", "1934", "1936"], "target_options": "1948", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_387_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_388", "question": "When did Theodor Heuss become the chairperson of FDP Bundestag fraction the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1944", "1949", "1948", "1947"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_388_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_389", "question": "When did Konrad Adenauer become the chairperson of Federal Foreign Office the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1951", "id": "1951"}], "options": ["1913", "1921", "1951", "1923"], "target_options": "1951", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_389_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_390", "question": "When did Lech Kaczy≈Ñski become the chairperson of Law and Justice the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["1997", "2001", "1990", "1998"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_390_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_391", "question": "When did Thomas Jefferson become the chairperson of United States Department of State the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1790", "id": "1790"}], "options": ["1959", "1962", "1790", "1953"], "target_options": "1790", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_391_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_392", "question": "When did Jean-Michel Aulas become the chairperson of Olympique Lyonnais the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1987", "id": "1987"}], "options": ["1981", "1978", "1987", "1968"], "target_options": "1987", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_392_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_393", "question": "When did Jimmy Wales become the chairperson of Wikimedia Foundation the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["1982", "2003", "1981", "1975"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_393_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_394", "question": "When did Franz-Josef Wuermeling become the chairperson of Federal Chancellery the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1940", "1936", "1939", "1949"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_394_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_395", "question": "When did Kurt Schumacher become the chairperson of Social Democratic Party of Germany the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1946", "1933", "1930", "1935"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_395_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_396", "question": "When did Joe Biden become the chairperson of Cabinet of Joe Biden the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2021", "id": "2021"}], "options": ["2012", "2005", "2021", "2014"], "target_options": "2021", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_396_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_397", "question": "When did √âtienne Gnassingb√© Eyad√©ma become the chairperson of Economic Community of West African States the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1944", "1975", "1954", "1956"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_397_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_398", "question": "When did Otto Hahn become the chairperson of Max Planck Society the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1948", "id": "1948"}], "options": ["1937", "1936", "1948", "1928"], "target_options": "1948", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_398_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_399", "question": "When did Konrad Adenauer become the chairperson of Federal Foreign Office the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1951", "id": "1951"}], "options": ["1949", "1951", "1940", "1950"], "target_options": "1951", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_399_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_400", "question": "When did Ebbe Schwartz become the chairperson of UEFA the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1954", "id": "1954"}], "options": ["1950", "1954", "1940", "1952"], "target_options": "1954", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_400_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_401", "question": "When did Yelena Isinbayeva become the chairperson of RUSADA the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2016", "2007", "2008", "1998"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_401_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_402", "question": "When did Artur Mas cease the chairperson of Convergence and Union the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2007", "2017", "2015", "2018"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_402_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_403", "question": "When did Konrad Adenauer become the chairperson of Christian Democratic Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1950", "id": "1950"}], "options": ["1940", "1950", "1934", "1942"], "target_options": "1950", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_403_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_404", "question": "When did Ludwig Erhard become the chairperson of Federal Ministry for Economic Affairs and Climate Action the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1945", "1942", "1949", "1932"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_404_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_405", "question": "When did Hermann Harnisch become the chairperson of SPD Berlin the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1930", "1945", "1928", "1922"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_405_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_406", "question": "When did Poul Nyrup Rasmussen become the chairperson of Social Democrats the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1963", "1992", "1960", "1954"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_406_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_407", "question": "When did Karl Brammer become the chairperson of CDU Berlin the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1941", "1945", "1933", "1940"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_407_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_408", "question": "When did Mildred Cohn become the chairperson of American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1978", "id": "1978"}], "options": ["1978", "1974", "1973", "1967"], "target_options": "1978", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_408_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_409", "question": "When did Michel Poniatowski cease the chairperson of Independent Republicans the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1977", "id": "1977"}], "options": ["1979", "1980", "1973", "1977"], "target_options": "1977", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_409_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_410", "question": "When did Sigfrid Edstr√∂m become the chairperson of World Athletics the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1912", "id": "1912"}], "options": ["1912", "1903", "1904", "1899"], "target_options": "1912", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_410_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_411", "question": "When did Pavel Axelrod cease the chairperson of Russian Social Democratic Labour Party the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1924", "id": "1924"}], "options": ["1920", "1919", "1924", "1916"], "target_options": "1924", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_411_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_412", "question": "When did Nicolas Sarkozy cease the chairperson of Union for a Popular Movement the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2020", "2015", "2017", "2011"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_412_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_413", "question": "When did Carlo Schmid become the chairperson of Committee on Foreign Affairs the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1945", "1942", "1946", "1949"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_413_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_414", "question": "When did Stephen Harper cease the chairperson of Canadian Alliance the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2005", "2003", "2008", "2004"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_414_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_415", "question": "When did Giacomo Grillo become the chairperson of Bank of Italy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1893", "id": "1893"}], "options": ["1866", "1876", "1893", "1877"], "target_options": "1893", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_415_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_416", "question": "When did Sigfrid Edstr√∂m become the chairperson of World Athletics the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1912", "id": "1912"}], "options": ["1912", "1913", "1905", "1910"], "target_options": "1912", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_416_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_417", "question": "When did John Lynch-Staunton become the chairperson of Conservative Party of Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2003", "1988", "1991", "1987"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_417_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_418", "question": "When did Dimitrios Vikelas become the chairperson of International Olympic Committee the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1894", "id": "1894"}], "options": ["1894", "1879", "1883", "1886"], "target_options": "1894", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_418_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_419", "question": "When did Nicolas Sarkozy cease the chairperson of Union for a Popular Movement the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2018", "2008", "2015", "2017"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_419_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_420", "question": "When did Nicolas Sarkozy become the chairperson of The Republicans the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2010", "2004", "2011", "2015"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_420_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_421", "question": "When did Dimitrios Vikelas become the chairperson of International Olympic Committee the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1894", "id": "1894"}], "options": ["1890", "1894", "1887", "1892"], "target_options": "1894", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_421_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_422", "question": "When did Jos√© Ayala Lasso become the chairperson of Office of the High Commissioner for Human Rights the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1994", "1984", "1982", "1975"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_422_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_423", "question": "When did Duncan Sandys become the chairperson of European Movement International the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1948", "id": "1948"}], "options": ["1930", "1948", "1931", "1926"], "target_options": "1948", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_423_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_424", "question": "When did Jimmy Wales become the chairperson of Wikimedia Foundation the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["1994", "2005", "2003", "2002"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_424_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_425", "question": "When did European Atomic Energy Community become a part of European Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1958", "1959", "1949", "1967"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_425_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_426", "question": "When did Finland become a part of European Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1995", "id": "1995"}], "options": ["1990", "1989", "1986", "1995"], "target_options": "1995", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_426_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_427", "question": "When did Romania become a part of European Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["1989", "1998", "2007", "2000"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_427_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_428", "question": "When did European Coal and Steel Community cease to a part of European Union the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2005", "2024", "1998", "2004"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_428_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_429", "question": "When did Poland become a part of European Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["1996", "1994", "2004", "1993"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_429_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_430", "question": "When did United Kingdom become a part of European Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1973", "id": "1973"}], "options": ["1970", "1959", "1967", "1973"], "target_options": "1973", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_430_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_431", "question": "When did Sylhet Region become a part of British Raj the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1858", "id": "1858"}], "options": ["1852", "1858", "1854", "1850"], "target_options": "1858", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_431_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_432", "question": "When did Pierrefonds become a part of Montreal the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["1992", "2002", "1995", "1982"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_432_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_433", "question": "When did Sylhet Region become a part of British Raj the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1858", "id": "1858"}], "options": ["1833", "1844", "1841", "1858"], "target_options": "1858", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_433_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_434", "question": "When did Gabu become a part of Guinea-Bissau the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1973", "id": "1973"}], "options": ["1974", "1967", "1973", "1971"], "target_options": "1973", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_434_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_435", "question": "When did Golm become a part of Potsdam the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1935", "id": "1935"}], "options": ["1999", "1996", "1935", "1998"], "target_options": "1935", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_435_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_436", "question": "When did Klein Glienicke become a part of Nowawes the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1938", "id": "1938"}], "options": ["1929", "1933", "1934", "1938"], "target_options": "1938", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_436_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_437", "question": "When did High Speed Photometer become a part of Hubble Space Telescope the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1971", "1981", "1983", "1990"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_437_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_438", "question": "When did Cosmic Origins Spectrograph become a part of Hubble Space Telescope the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["2007", "2006", "1996", "2009"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_438_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_439", "question": "When did Faint Object Camera become a part of Hubble Space Telescope the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1977", "1982", "1984", "1990"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_439_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_440", "question": "When did Wide Field and Planetary Camera become a part of Hubble Space Telescope the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1984", "1987", "1979", "1990"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_440_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_441", "question": "When did Corrective Optics Space Telescope Axial Replacement become a part of Hubble Space Telescope the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1992", "1982", "1993", "1995"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_441_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_442", "question": "When did Space Telescope Imaging Spectrograph become a part of Hubble Space Telescope the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1982", "1989", "1992", "1997"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_442_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_443", "question": "When did Goddard High Resolution Spectrograph become a part of Hubble Space Telescope the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1987", "1986", "1990", "1981"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_443_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_444", "question": "When did Faint Object Spectrograph become a part of Hubble Space Telescope the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1977", "1990", "1983", "1985"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_444_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_445", "question": "When did Advanced Camera for Surveys become a part of Hubble Space Telescope the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["2002", "2000", "1990", "1999"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_445_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_446", "question": "When did Maine become a part of Massachusetts the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1652", "id": "1652"}], "options": ["1652", "1645", "1647", "1635"], "target_options": "1652", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_446_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_447", "question": "When did European Union Civil Service Tribunal cease to a part of Court of Justice of the European Union the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2016", "2019", "2009", "2018"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_447_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_448", "question": "When did Thomas Romain start residing at Japan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2003", "1994", "1998", "1995"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_448_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_449", "question": "When did Michael Redmond start residing at Japan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1976", "id": "1976"}], "options": ["1974", "1971", "1973", "1976"], "target_options": "1976", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_449_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_450", "question": "When did Christabel Pankhurst end residing at French Riviera the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1926", "id": "1926"}], "options": ["1926", "1962", "1960", "1951"], "target_options": "1926", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_450_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_451", "question": "When did Ferenc Rofusz start residing at Hungary the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1946", "1921", "1932", "1931"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_451_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_452", "question": "When did Rahaf Mohammed start residing at Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2019", "2017", "2016", "2012"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_452_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_453", "question": "When did Wolf Koenig end residing at Canada the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2007", "2016", "2024", "2018"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_453_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_454", "question": "When did Alexandre Alexeieff end residing at Canada the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1947", "id": "1947"}], "options": ["1947", "1979", "1987", "1984"], "target_options": "1947", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_454_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_455", "question": "When did Maurice Ascalon end residing at Palestine the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1956", "id": "1956"}], "options": ["2005", "1956", "2004", "2006"], "target_options": "1956", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_455_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_456", "question": "When did Ferenc Rofusz start residing at Hungary the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1946", "1937", "1938", "1930"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_456_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_457", "question": "When did National Aeronautics and Space Administration become the operator of Orbiter Processing Facility the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1970", "1977", "1982", "1979"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_457_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_458", "question": "When did National Aeronautics and Space Administration become the operator of astronaut transfer van the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["2017", "1967", "2013", "2016"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_458_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_459", "question": "When did Turkey become the operator of Embassy of Turkey in Austria the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1916", "id": "1916"}], "options": ["1913", "1911", "1916", "1903"], "target_options": "1916", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_459_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_460", "question": "When did Google become the operator of reCAPTCHA the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["1998", "2007", "2009", "2011"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_460_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_461", "question": "When did Wikimedia Foundation become the operator of Wikipedia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["1989", "2003", "1997", "1999"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_461_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_462", "question": "When did United States Army become the operator of Fort Barry the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1908", "id": "1908"}], "options": ["1909", "1906", "1899", "1908"], "target_options": "1908", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_462_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_463", "question": "When did United States Army become the operator of Fort Washington Park the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1809", "id": "1809"}], "options": ["1809", "1800", "1796", "1799"], "target_options": "1809", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_463_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_464", "question": "When did United States Army become the operator of Fort Tilden the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1917", "id": "1917"}], "options": ["1903", "1910", "1917", "1907"], "target_options": "1917", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_464_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_465", "question": "When did Grand Duchy of Mecklenburg Friedrich-Franz Railway become the operator of Molli railway the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1890", "id": "1890"}], "options": ["1872", "1875", "1890", "1864"], "target_options": "1890", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_465_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_466", "question": "When did Everton F.C. become the operator of Anfield the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1884", "id": "1884"}], "options": ["1881", "1871", "1884", "1886"], "target_options": "1884", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_466_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_467", "question": "When did United States Air Force end the operator of Brooks Air Force Base the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2016", "2013", "2011", "2012"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_467_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_468", "question": "When did Cardiff Airport end the operator of MOD St Athan the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2007", "2008", "2010", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_468_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_469", "question": "When did North Rhine-Westphalia become the operator of Robert Schumann Hochschule the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1973", "id": "1973"}], "options": ["1964", "1960", "1967", "1973"], "target_options": "1973", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_469_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_470", "question": "When did United States Navy become the operator of USS Foote the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1919", "id": "1919"}], "options": ["1919", "1912", "1917", "1920"], "target_options": "1919", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_470_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_471", "question": "When did the twinning between Saint Petersburg and Turku start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1953", "id": "1953"}], "options": ["1948", "1953", "1947", "1951"], "target_options": "1953", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_471_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_472", "question": "When did the twinning between Amman and Rabat start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1986", "1984", "1980", "1982"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_472_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_473", "question": "When did the twinning between Bordeaux and Bristol start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1947", "id": "1947"}], "options": ["1912", "1910", "1909", "1947"], "target_options": "1947", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_473_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_474", "question": "When did the twinning between Salzburg and Reims start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1964", "id": "1964"}], "options": ["1953", "1964", "1943", "1952"], "target_options": "1964", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_474_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_475", "question": "When did the twinning between Miami Beach and Fujisawa start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1959", "id": "1959"}], "options": ["1960", "1953", "1957", "1959"], "target_options": "1959", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_475_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_476", "question": "When did the twinning between Delhi and Chicago start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["1990", "2001", "2005", "2000"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_476_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_477", "question": "When did the twinning between Nagoya and Los Angeles start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1959", "id": "1959"}], "options": ["1959", "1950", "1949", "1953"], "target_options": "1959", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_477_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_478", "question": "When did the twinning between Berlin and Los Angeles start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1967", "1953", "1962", "1964"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_478_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_479", "question": "When did the twinning between New York City and Tokyo start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1960", "1951", "1950", "1941"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_479_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_480", "question": "When did the twinning between Tbilisi and Saarbr√ºcken start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1961", "1966", "1975", "1968"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_480_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_481", "question": "When did the twinning between Beijing and Tokyo start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1979", "1966", "1964", "1956"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_481_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_482", "question": "When did the twinning between Taipei and Houston start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1961", "id": "1961"}], "options": ["1964", "1961", "1959", "1957"], "target_options": "1961", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_482_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_483", "question": "When did the twinning between Amman and Rabat start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1986", "1968", "1959", "1971"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_483_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_484", "question": "When did the twinning between Zagreb and Mainz start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1957", "1956", "1967", "1953"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_484_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_485", "question": "When did the twinning between Tokyo and New York City start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1952", "1951", "1946", "1960"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_485_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_486", "question": "When did the twinning between Moscow and Vienna start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1956", "id": "1956"}], "options": ["1956", "1933", "1936", "1935"], "target_options": "1956", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_486_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_487", "question": "When did the twinning between New York City and Tokyo start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1942", "1944", "1960", "1933"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_487_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_488", "question": "When did the twinning between Auckland and Los Angeles start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1964", "1954", "1971", "1963"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_488_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_489", "question": "When did the twinning between Mexico City and Los Angeles start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1969", "id": "1969"}], "options": ["1964", "1969", "1960", "1967"], "target_options": "1969", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_489_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_490", "question": "When did the twinning between Berlin and Los Angeles start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1961", "1954", "1967", "1959"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_490_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_491", "question": "When did the twinning between San Francisco and Osaka start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1957", "id": "1957"}], "options": ["1952", "1957", "1951", "1953"], "target_options": "1957", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_491_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_492", "question": "When did the twinning between Lusaka and Dushanbe start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1966", "1963", "1962", "1960"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_492_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_493", "question": "When did the twinning between Yerevan and Carrara start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1965", "id": "1965"}], "options": ["1953", "1956", "1959", "1965"], "target_options": "1965", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_493_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_494", "question": "When did the twinning between Cotonou and Taipei start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1967", "1960", "1961", "1951"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_494_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_495", "question": "When did the twinning between Rio de Janeiro and Istanbul start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1965", "id": "1965"}], "options": ["1953", "1948", "1965", "1952"], "target_options": "1965", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_495_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_496", "question": "When did the twinning between Vinnytsia and Peterborough start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1991", "1990", "1995", "1980"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_496_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_497", "question": "When did the twinning between Los Angeles and Nagoya start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1959", "id": "1959"}], "options": ["1936", "1927", "1959", "1938"], "target_options": "1959", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_497_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_498", "question": "When did the twinning between Eilat and Los Angeles start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1959", "id": "1959"}], "options": ["1943", "1959", "1950", "1953"], "target_options": "1959", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_498_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_499", "question": "When did the twinning between Shanghai and Yokohama start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1973", "id": "1973"}], "options": ["1973", "1968", "1971", "1960"], "target_options": "1973", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_499_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_500", "question": "When did the twinning between Kunming and Fujisawa start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1981", "id": "1981"}], "options": ["1966", "1981", "1975", "1976"], "target_options": "1981", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_500_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_501", "question": "When did the twinning between Tehran and Los Angeles start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1972", "id": "1972"}], "options": ["1970", "1964", "1972", "1974"], "target_options": "1972", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_501_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_502", "question": "When did the twinning between Shanghai and Yokohama start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1973", "id": "1973"}], "options": ["1945", "1973", "1946", "1936"], "target_options": "1973", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_502_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_503", "question": "When did the twinning between City of Brussels and Berlin start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1976", "1987", "1992", "1985"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_503_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_504", "question": "When did the twinning between Aalborg Municipality and Fredrikstad Municipality start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1951", "id": "1951"}], "options": ["1922", "1927", "1951", "1930"], "target_options": "1951", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_504_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_505", "question": "When did the twinning between Tokyo and New York City start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1960", "1937", "1935", "1925"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_505_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_506", "question": "When did the twinning between Leiria and Set√∫bal start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1982", "1956", "1962", "1960"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_506_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_507", "question": "When did the twinning between Milan and S√£o Paulo start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1961", "id": "1961"}], "options": ["1957", "1951", "1961", "1956"], "target_options": "1961", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_507_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_508", "question": "When did the twinning between Buenos Aires and Berlin start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1952", "1960", "1961", "1994"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_508_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_509", "question": "When did the twinning between Beijing and Tokyo start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1969", "1970", "1979", "1962"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_509_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_510", "question": "When did the twinning between Erfurt and Gy≈ër start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1954", "1962", "1965", "1971"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_510_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_511", "question": "When did the twinning between Montevideo and Santa Fe start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1999", "1994", "1986", "1996"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_511_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_512", "question": "When did the twinning between Tbilisi and Saarbr√ºcken start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1961", "1975", "1964", "1954"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_512_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_513", "question": "When did the twinning between Santiago and S√£o Paulo start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1989", "1986", "1988", "1998"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_513_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_514", "question": "When did the twinning between Riga and Rostock start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1961", "id": "1961"}], "options": ["1941", "1938", "1936", "1961"], "target_options": "1961", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_514_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_515", "question": "When did the twinning between Huaibei and S√£o Paulo start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2016", "2010", "2017", "2019"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_515_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_516", "question": "When did the twinning between Havana and Cusco start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1946", "1943", "1949", "1993"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_516_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_517", "question": "When did the twinning between Kyoto Prefecture and Shaanxi start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1983", "id": "1983"}], "options": ["1979", "1971", "1982", "1983"], "target_options": "1983", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_517_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_518", "question": "When did the twinning between Milan and S√£o Paulo start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1961", "id": "1961"}], "options": ["1961", "1962", "1958", "1959"], "target_options": "1961", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_518_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_519", "question": "When did the twinning between Luanda and S√£o Paulo start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1985", "1986", "1993", "1989"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_519_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_520", "question": "When did the twinning between La Paz and Cusco start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1984", "id": "1984"}], "options": ["1968", "1970", "1984", "1964"], "target_options": "1984", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_520_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_521", "question": "When did the twinning between Bamako and Angers start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1953", "1960", "1963", "1974"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_521_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_522", "question": "When did the twinning between Damascus and S√£o Paulo start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1984", "1996", "1999", "1994"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_522_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_523", "question": "When did the twinning between Yerevan and Carrara start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1965", "id": "1965"}], "options": ["1965", "1949", "1954", "1955"], "target_options": "1965", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_523_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_524", "question": "When did the twinning between Toyama Prefecture and Liaoning start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1984", "id": "1984"}], "options": ["1984", "1986", "1973", "1983"], "target_options": "1984", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_524_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_525", "question": "When did the twinning between Saint Petersburg and Turku start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1953", "id": "1953"}], "options": ["1949", "1944", "1953", "1948"], "target_options": "1953", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_525_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_526", "question": "When did the twinning between Salzburg and Reims start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1964", "id": "1964"}], "options": ["1964", "1961", "1960", "1951"], "target_options": "1964", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_526_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_527", "question": "When did the twinning between Toronto and Chongqing start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1968", "1966", "1986", "1964"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_527_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_528", "question": "When did the twinning between Duisburg and Portsmouth start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1950", "id": "1950"}], "options": ["1943", "1950", "1932", "1940"], "target_options": "1950", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_528_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_529", "question": "When did the twinning between Oslo and Vilnius start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1986", "1991", "1983", "1978"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_529_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_530", "question": "When did the twinning between Santiago de Compostela and S√£o Paulo start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["1993", "2000", "1986", "1995"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_530_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_531", "question": "When did the twinning between Macau and Lisbon start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1930", "1920", "1931", "1982"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_531_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_532", "question": "When did the twinning between Tokushima Prefecture and S√£o Paulo start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1984", "id": "1984"}], "options": ["1978", "1980", "1984", "1975"], "target_options": "1984", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_532_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_533", "question": "When did the twinning between Chicago and Warsaw start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1942", "1944", "1934", "1960"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_533_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_534", "question": "When did the twinning between Madison and Freiburg im Breisgau start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1987", "id": "1987"}], "options": ["1961", "1960", "1987", "1955"], "target_options": "1987", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_534_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_535", "question": "When did the twinning between Osaka and San Francisco start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1957", "id": "1957"}], "options": ["1947", "1949", "1957", "1945"], "target_options": "1957", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_535_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_536", "question": "When did the twinning between Mendoza and S√£o Paulo start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1983", "1992", "1991", "1998"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_536_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_537", "question": "When did the twinning between Bila Tserkva and Suizhou start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1982", "1986", "1997", "1985"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_537_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_538", "question": "When did the twinning between Funchal and Honolulu start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1966", "1962", "1979", "1964"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_538_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_539", "question": "When did the twinning between Dnipro and Herzliya start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1966", "1969", "1993", "1965"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_539_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_540", "question": "When did the twinning between Lisbon and Zagreb start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1977", "id": "1977"}], "options": ["1964", "1962", "1966", "1977"], "target_options": "1977", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_540_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_541", "question": "When did the twinning between Tel Aviv and Toulouse start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1958", "id": "1958"}], "options": ["1935", "1930", "1936", "1958"], "target_options": "1958", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_541_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_542", "question": "When did the twinning between Seoul and Taipei start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1968", "id": "1968"}], "options": ["1932", "1968", "1939", "1941"], "target_options": "1968", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_542_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_543", "question": "When did the twinning between Almaty and Tucson start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1967", "1964", "1965", "1989"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_543_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_544", "question": "When did the twinning between Mie Prefecture and S√£o Paulo start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1973", "id": "1973"}], "options": ["1954", "1973", "1965", "1964"], "target_options": "1973", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_544_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_545", "question": "When did the twinning between Coimbra and Halle (Saale) start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1959", "1967", "1975", "1970"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_545_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_546", "question": "When did the twinning between Guangzhou and Frankfurt start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1988", "id": "1988"}], "options": ["1983", "1988", "1985", "1979"], "target_options": "1988", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_546_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_547", "question": "When did the twinning between Naha and Honolulu start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1935", "1960", "1944", "1942"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_547_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_548", "question": "When did the twinning between Abidjan and Marseille start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1958", "id": "1958"}], "options": ["1955", "1958", "1953", "1952"], "target_options": "1958", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_548_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_549", "question": "When did the twinning between Budapest and Tel Aviv-Yafo start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1969", "1961", "1972", "1989"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_549_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_550", "question": "When did the twinning between Donetsk and Bochum start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1987", "id": "1987"}], "options": ["1964", "1954", "1987", "1962"], "target_options": "1987", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_550_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_551", "question": "When did the twinning between Tallinn and Kotka start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1955", "id": "1955"}], "options": ["1943", "1947", "1955", "1946"], "target_options": "1955", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_551_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_552", "question": "When did Pavel Shuvalov lose hold captain the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1907", "1902", "1908", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_552_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_553", "question": "When did Andrei Grechko lose hold colonel the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1973", "1981", "1978"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_553_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_554", "question": "When did Captain Nazi attain captain the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["1982", "2000", "1990", "1991"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_554_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_555", "question": "When did Pierre Henri Hugoniot lose hold captain the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1889", "1882", "1892"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_555_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_556", "question": "When did Rumen Radev attain lieutenant the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1987", "id": "1987"}], "options": ["1987", "1973", "1985", "1983"], "target_options": "1987", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_556_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_557", "question": "When did Alexander Yefimov lose hold captain the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2007", "2014", "2017", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_557_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_558", "question": "When did David Dragunsky lose hold captain the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1996", "1987", "2024", "1994"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_558_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_559", "question": "When did Sergey Denisov lose hold captain the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1974", "1967", "2024", "1973"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_559_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_560", "question": "When did Vladimir Ilyushin lose hold colonel the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2012", "2024", "2015", "2003"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_560_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_561", "question": "When did Alexander Molodchy lose hold colonel the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "2007", "1999", "2004"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_561_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_562", "question": "When did August von Werder lose hold colonel the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1891", "1889", "1886", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_562_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_563", "question": "When did Vladimir Arsenyev lose hold lieutenant colonel the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1917", "id": "1917"}], "options": ["1932", "1935", "1923", "1917"], "target_options": "1917", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_563_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_564", "question": "When did Alexander III of Russia lose hold colonel the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1888", "1896", "1899"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_564_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_565", "question": "When did Heather Mills marry Paul McCartney the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["1991", "2002", "1998", "2000"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_565_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_566", "question": "When did Maureen Starkey Tigrett divorce with Isaac Tigrett the last time", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1994", "1998", "1996", "2000"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_566_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_567", "question": "When did Hildegard of Vinzgouw divorce with Charlemagne the last time", "answer": [{"label": "783", "id": "783"}], "options": ["784", "786", "783", "785"], "target_options": "783", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_567_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_568", "question": "When did Freddie Stroma marry Johanna Braddy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2016", "2014", "2001", "2011"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_568_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_569", "question": "When did Christina Hendricks marry Geoffrey Arend the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["2002", "2009", "1997", "2000"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_569_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_570", "question": "When did Linda McCartney divorce with Paul McCartney the last time", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["2000", "2003", "1998", "1997"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_570_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_571", "question": "When did Emma Heming Willis marry Bruce Willis the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["1994", "2003", "2009", "2006"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_571_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_572", "question": "When did Desiderata of the Lombards divorce with Charlemagne the last time", "answer": [{"label": "771", "id": "771"}], "options": ["779", "771", "777", "778"], "target_options": "771", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_572_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_573", "question": "When did Carrie Fisher divorce with Paul Simon the last time", "answer": [{"label": "1984", "id": "1984"}], "options": ["2018", "2017", "1984", "2021"], "target_options": "1984", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_573_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_574", "question": "When did Fastrada divorce with Charlemagne the last time", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["799", "796", "786", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_574_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_575", "question": "When did Fastrada divorce with Charlemagne the last time", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "798", "792", "796"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_575_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_576", "question": "When did Lisa Marie Presley marry Danny Keough the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1988", "id": "1988"}], "options": ["1988", "1957", "1959", "1961"], "target_options": "1988", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_576_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_577", "question": "When did Barbara Bach marry Augusto Gregorini the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1968", "id": "1968"}], "options": ["1968", "1980", "1981", "1975"], "target_options": "1968", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_577_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_578", "question": "When did Hildegard of Vinzgouw divorce with Charlemagne the last time", "answer": [{"label": "783", "id": "783"}], "options": ["786", "785", "775", "783"], "target_options": "783", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_578_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_579", "question": "When did Josh Blaylock marry Johanna Braddy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2003", "1996", "2006", "2012"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_579_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_580", "question": "When did David Furnish marry Elton John the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["2004", "2002", "2005", "2006"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_580_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_581", "question": "When did Maria Shriver marry Arnold Schwarzenegger the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1976", "1977", "1986", "1972"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_581_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_582", "question": "When did Carrie Fisher divorce with Paul Simon the last time", "answer": [{"label": "1984", "id": "1984"}], "options": ["2018", "2019", "1984", "2013"], "target_options": "1984", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_582_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_583", "question": "When did Casimir Dudevant divorce with George Sand the last time", "answer": [{"label": "1835", "id": "1835"}], "options": ["1871", "1876", "1835", "1873"], "target_options": "1835", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_583_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_584", "question": "When did Sonia Orwell divorce with Michael Pitt-Rivers the last time", "answer": [{"label": "1965", "id": "1965"}], "options": ["1965", "1975", "1984", "1982"], "target_options": "1965", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_584_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_585", "question": "When did Daniella Pick marry Quentin Tarantino the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2017", "2018", "2014", "2005"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_585_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_586", "question": "When did Margot Honecker divorce with Erich Honecker the last time", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["2018", "2012", "1994", "2021"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_586_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_587", "question": "When did Debbie Rowe marry Michael Jackson the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1986", "1987", "1996", "1976"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_587_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_588", "question": "When did Olivia Harrison marry George Harrison the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1978", "id": "1978"}], "options": ["1965", "1979", "1975", "1978"], "target_options": "1978", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_588_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_589", "question": "When did Claudia Schiffer marry Matthew Vaughn the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["2002", "1999", "1993", "1997"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_589_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_590", "question": "When did Edie Brickell marry Paul Simon the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1992", "1985", "1978", "1984"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_590_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_591", "question": "When did Pattie Boyd marry George Harrison the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1962", "1952", "1966", "1964"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_591_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_592", "question": "When did Queen Paola of Belgium marry Albert II of Belgium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1959", "id": "1959"}], "options": ["1946", "1953", "1959", "1956"], "target_options": "1959", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_592_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_593", "question": "When did Demi Moore marry Freddy Moore the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1980", "id": "1980"}], "options": ["1980", "1952", "1945", "1953"], "target_options": "1980", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_593_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_594", "question": "When did Galina Lukashenko marry Alexander Lukashenko the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1975", "1974", "1977", "1972"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_594_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_595", "question": "When did Princess Hermine Reuss of Greiz divorce with Wilhelm II the last time", "answer": [{"label": "1941", "id": "1941"}], "options": ["1951", "1949", "1940", "1941"], "target_options": "1941", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_595_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_596", "question": "When did Anna Magdalena Bach divorce with Johann Sebastian Bach the last time", "answer": [{"label": "1750", "id": "1750"}], "options": ["1762", "1764", "1750", "1760"], "target_options": "1750", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_596_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_597", "question": "When did Julia Domna divorce with Septimius Severus the last time", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["219", "2024", "220", "211"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_597_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_598", "question": "When did David Thornton marry Cyndi Lauper the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1991", "1985", "1978", "1982"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_598_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_599", "question": "When did Maria Barbara Bach divorce with Johann Sebastian Bach the last time", "answer": [{"label": "1720", "id": "1720"}], "options": ["1724", "1719", "1722", "1720"], "target_options": "1720", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_599_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_600", "question": "When did Poppaea Sabina divorce with Nero the last time", "answer": [{"label": "65", "id": "65"}], "options": ["70", "67", "65", "61"], "target_options": "65", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_600_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_601", "question": "When did Fanny Stevenson divorce with Robert Louis Stevenson the last time", "answer": [{"label": "1894", "id": "1894"}], "options": ["1916", "1919", "1911", "1894"], "target_options": "1894", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_601_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_602", "question": "When did Fanny Stevenson divorce with Robert Louis Stevenson the last time", "answer": [{"label": "1894", "id": "1894"}], "options": ["1894", "1913", "1916", "1918"], "target_options": "1894", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_602_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_603", "question": "When did Mirka Federer marry Roger Federer the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["1998", "2005", "2008", "2009"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_603_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_604", "question": "When did Claudia Octavia divorce with Nero the last time", "answer": [{"label": "62", "id": "62"}], "options": ["65", "64", "62", "57"], "target_options": "62", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_604_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_605", "question": "When did Nadezhda Krupskaya divorce with Vladimir Lenin the last time", "answer": [{"label": "1924", "id": "1924"}], "options": ["1944", "1924", "1932", "1941"], "target_options": "1924", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_605_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_606", "question": "When did Cosima Wagner divorce with Richard Wagner the last time", "answer": [{"label": "1883", "id": "1883"}], "options": ["1935", "1883", "1932", "1922"], "target_options": "1883", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_606_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_607", "question": "When did Statilia Messalina marry Marcus Julius Vestinus Atticus the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "63", "id": "63"}], "options": ["55", "59", "62", "63"], "target_options": "63", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_607_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_608", "question": "When did Paulo Bento become the head coach of the team South Korea national football team the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2018", "2000", "2009", "2010"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_608_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_609", "question": "When did Helenio Herrera become the head coach of the team Inter Milan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1953", "1954", "1960", "1952"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_609_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_610", "question": "When did Stuart Baxter become the head coach of the team Vissel Kobe the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1974", "1973", "1970", "1997"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_610_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_611", "question": "When did Karsten Baumann become the head coach of the team MSV Duisburg the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2009", "2000", "2013", "2007"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_611_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_612", "question": "When did Luciano Spalletti become the head coach of the team FC Zenit Saint Petersburg the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["2009", "1985", "1988", "1978"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_612_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_613", "question": "When did Franco Foda become the head coach of the team Austria national association football team the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2017", "2019", "2014", "2008"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_613_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_614", "question": "When did F√©lix Barderas Sierra become the head coach of the team CF Fuenlabrada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["2008", "2003", "2005", "1998"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_614_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_615", "question": "When did Nariyasu Yasuhara become the head coach of the team FC Kariya the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["1996", "2006", "1997", "1999"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_615_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_616", "question": "When did Martin Schmidt become the head coach of the team VfL Wolfsburg the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2012", "2010", "2000", "2017"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_616_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_617", "question": "When did Jimmy Connors become the head coach of the team Maria Sharapova the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["1999", "1998", "2008", "1993"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_617_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_618", "question": "When did Kurt Gogsch become the head coach of the team FC Erzgebirge Aue the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1946", "1916", "1920", "1919"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_618_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_619", "question": "When did Helenio Herrera become the head coach of the team Inter Milan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1960", "1992", "1993", "1996"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_619_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_620", "question": "When did Phillip Cocu become the head coach of the team PSV Eindhoven the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["1999", "1993", "2014", "1996"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_620_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_621", "question": "When did Jimmy Connors become the head coach of the team Maria Sharapova the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["2007", "2004", "2008", "1995"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_621_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_622", "question": "When did Giovanni Trapattoni become the head coach of the team AC Milan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1961", "1975", "1958", "1957"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_622_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_623", "question": "When did Kurt Gogsch become the head coach of the team FC Erzgebirge Aue the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1932", "1946", "1931", "1924"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_623_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_624", "question": "When did Ralph Hasenh√ºttl become the head coach of the team RB Leipzig the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2016", "1999", "2008", "2011"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_624_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_625", "question": "When did Didier Deschamps become the head coach of the team AS Monaco FC the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["1984", "1991", "2001", "1992"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_625_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_626", "question": "When did Patrick Vieira become the head coach of the team OGC Nice the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2018", "2019", "2017", "2012"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_626_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_627", "question": "When did Stuart Baxter become the head coach of the team Vissel Kobe the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1989", "1997", "1990", "1987"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_627_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_628", "question": "When did Brad Gilbert become the head coach of the team Kei Nishikori the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2006", "2007", "2010", "2002"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_628_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_629", "question": "When did Herv√© Renard become the head coach of the team Saudi Arabia national football team the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2012", "2018", "2017", "2019"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_629_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_630", "question": "When did Jimmy Connors become the head coach of the team Andy Roddick the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["1997", "2000", "1994", "2006"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_630_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_631", "question": "When did Joachim L√∂w become the head coach of the team VfB Stuttgart the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1988", "1996", "1981", "1990"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_631_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_632", "question": "When did Brad Gilbert become the head coach of the team Andy Murray the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2006", "1994", "2002", "2005"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_632_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_633", "question": "When did Arrigo Sacchi become the head coach of the team Italy national association football team the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1987", "1991", "1985", "1986"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_633_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_634", "question": "When did Thierry Laurey become the head coach of the team RC Strasbourg the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2016", "1996", "1988", "1998"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_634_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_635", "question": "When did P√°l D√°rdai become the head coach of the team Hertha BSC the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2012", "2014", "2002", "2015"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_635_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_636", "question": "When did Jupp Heynckes become the head coach of the team FC Bayern Munich the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1987", "id": "1987"}], "options": ["1967", "1987", "1970", "1957"], "target_options": "1987", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_636_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_637", "question": "When did Marc Kienle become the head coach of the team VfB Stuttgart II the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2010", "2018", "2019", "2017"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_637_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_638", "question": "When did P√°l D√°rdai become the head coach of the team Hertha BSC the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["1992", "1984", "1990", "2015"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_638_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_639", "question": "When did Alex Ferguson become the head coach of the team Scotland national football team the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1985", "id": "1985"}], "options": ["1982", "1979", "1985", "1980"], "target_options": "1985", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_639_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_640", "question": "When did Jen≈ë K√°roly become the head coach of the team Juventus FC the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1923", "id": "1923"}], "options": ["1923", "1967", "1968", "1960"], "target_options": "1923", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_640_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_641", "question": "When did P√°l Gilly-Goldberger become the head coach of the team Eintracht Frankfurt the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1911", "id": "1911"}], "options": ["1891", "1893", "1911", "1885"], "target_options": "1911", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_641_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_642", "question": "When did Alex Sans Vega become the head coach of the team Qhubeka Assos the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2015", "1986", "1987", "1976"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_642_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_643", "question": "When did Joachim L√∂w become the head coach of the team VfB Stuttgart the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["2003", "1999", "1996", "2002"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_643_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_644", "question": "When did Franco Foda become the head coach of the team SK Sturm Graz the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["1999", "2004", "2014", "2005"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_644_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_645", "question": "When did P√°l Gilly-Goldberger become the head coach of the team Eintracht Frankfurt the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1911", "id": "1911"}], "options": ["1902", "1901", "1898", "1911"], "target_options": "1911", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_645_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_646", "question": "When did J√≥zef Szkolnikowski become the head coach of the team Poland national association football team the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1921", "id": "1921"}], "options": ["1904", "1901", "1903", "1921"], "target_options": "1921", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_646_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_647", "question": "When did Franco Foda become the head coach of the team Austria national association football team the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2013", "2017", "2002", "2011"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_647_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_648", "question": "When did Hermann Gerland become the head coach of the team Tennis Borussia Berlin the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1996", "1968", "1967", "1963"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_648_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_649", "question": "When did Hermann Gerland become the head coach of the team Tennis Borussia Berlin the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1996", "1983", "1992", "1994"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_649_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_650", "question": "When did Jen≈ë K√°roly become the head coach of the team Juventus FC the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1923", "id": "1923"}], "options": ["1992", "1990", "1981", "1923"], "target_options": "1923", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_650_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_651", "question": "When did Andriy Shevchenko become the head coach of the team Ukraine national association football team the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2007", "2004", "2010", "2016"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_651_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_652", "question": "When did Du≈°an Uhrin become the head coach of the team Czech Republic national association football team the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1988", "1987", "1981", "1993"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_652_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_653", "question": "When did Giovanni Trapattoni become the head coach of the team AC Milan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1966", "1964", "1965", "1975"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_653_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_654", "question": "When did Eduard Markarov become the head coach of the team Armenia national football team the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1972", "1970", "1992", "1960"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_654_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_655", "question": "When did Reinaldo Rueda become the head coach of the team Clube de Regatas do Flamengo the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2017", "2018", "2016", "2007"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_655_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_656", "question": "When did Arrigo Sacchi become the head coach of the team Italy national association football team the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1982", "1981", "1991", "1976"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_656_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_657", "question": "When did Osei Bonsu stop working in monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1824", "id": "1824"}], "options": ["1821", "1828", "1826", "1824"], "target_options": "1824", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_657_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_658", "question": "When did Francesco II Sforza stop working in monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1535", "id": "1535"}], "options": ["1540", "1537", "1535", "1532"], "target_options": "1535", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_658_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_659", "question": "When did Francesco II Sforza stop working in monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1535", "id": "1535"}], "options": ["1535", "1537", "1539", "1529"], "target_options": "1535", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_659_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_660", "question": "When did Reginfrid stop working in monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "814", "id": "814"}], "options": ["813", "819", "816", "814"], "target_options": "814", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_660_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_661", "question": "When did Idris Alooma stop working in monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1617", "id": "1617"}], "options": ["1598", "1589", "1617", "1600"], "target_options": "1617", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_661_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_662", "question": "When did Prempeh II stop working in monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1970", "id": "1970"}], "options": ["1971", "1975", "1972", "1970"], "target_options": "1970", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_662_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_663", "question": "When did Naruhito start working in monarch the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2012", "2019", "2015", "2003"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_663_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_664", "question": "When did Harald Klak stop working in monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "827", "id": "827"}], "options": ["847", "846", "827", "845"], "target_options": "827", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_664_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_665", "question": "When did Harald Klak stop working in monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "827", "id": "827"}], "options": ["843", "827", "848", "846"], "target_options": "827", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_665_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_666", "question": "When did Beatrix of the Netherlands start working in monarch the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1980", "id": "1980"}], "options": ["1977", "1974", "1972", "1980"], "target_options": "1980", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_666_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_667", "question": "When did Henry VIII of England stop working in monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1547", "id": "1547"}], "options": ["1552", "1549", "1547", "1548"], "target_options": "1547", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_667_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_668", "question": "When did Constantine II of Greece start working in monarch the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1964", "id": "1964"}], "options": ["1963", "1960", "1967", "1964"], "target_options": "1964", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_668_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_669", "question": "When did Judith of Bavaria stop working in monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "840", "id": "840"}], "options": ["848", "845", "840", "837"], "target_options": "840", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_669_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_670", "question": "When did Hemming of Denmark stop working in monarch the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "812", "id": "812"}], "options": ["804", "812", "814", "815"], "target_options": "812", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_670_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_671", "question": "When did Harald V of Norway start working in monarch the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1975", "1983", "1986", "1991"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_671_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_672", "question": "When did Osei Tutu stop working in Asantehene the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1717", "id": "1717"}], "options": ["1719", "1710", "1717", "1720"], "target_options": "1717", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_672_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_673", "question": "When did William Herschel stop working in musician the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1781", "id": "1781"}], "options": ["1827", "1824", "1816", "1781"], "target_options": "1781", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_673_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_674", "question": "When did Henri Joseph Anastase Perrotin stop working in astronomer the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1899", "1906", "1908"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_674_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_675", "question": "When did the Tung Chee Hwa become the office holder of Chief Executive of Hong Kong the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1997", "1968", "1959", "1965"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_675_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_676", "question": "When did the Nguy·ªÖn Ph√∫ Tr·ªçng become the office holder of General Secretary of the Communist Party the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2005", "2010", "2011", "2013"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_676_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_677", "question": "When did the Mao Zedong become the office holder of Chairman of the Central Military Commission of the Chinese Communist Party the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1954", "id": "1954"}], "options": ["1896", "1904", "1954", "1902"], "target_options": "1954", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_677_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_678", "question": "When did the Zhang Guangjian become the office holder of mayor of Beijing the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1912", "id": "1912"}], "options": ["1899", "1902", "1912", "1905"], "target_options": "1912", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_678_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_679", "question": "When did the Etienne Constantin de Gerlache become the office holder of Prime Minister of Belgium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1831", "id": "1831"}], "options": ["1817", "1831", "1825", "1822"], "target_options": "1831", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_679_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_680", "question": "When did the Tung Chee Hwa become the office holder of Chief Executive of Hong Kong the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1973", "1997", "1972", "1974"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_680_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_681", "question": "When did the Hu Yaobang become the office holder of General Secretary of the Chinese Communist Party the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1971", "1970", "1982", "1973"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_681_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_682", "question": "When did the Etienne Constantin de Gerlache become the office holder of Prime Minister of Belgium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1831", "id": "1831"}], "options": ["1820", "1831", "1824", "1825"], "target_options": "1831", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_682_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_683", "question": "When did the Leonid Kravchuk become the office holder of President of Ukraine the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1987", "1991", "1990", "1992"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_683_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_684", "question": "When did the Hu Yaobang become the office holder of General Secretary of the Chinese Communist Party the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1964", "1961", "1982", "1952"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_684_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_685", "question": "When did the William Herschel become the office holder of President of the Royal Astronomical Society the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1821", "id": "1821"}], "options": ["1821", "1799", "1796", "1786"], "target_options": "1821", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_685_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_686", "question": "When did the Fritz Sch√§ffer become the office holder of Federal Minister of Finance the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1940", "1949", "1937", "1927"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_686_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_687", "question": "When did the Mao Zedong become the office holder of Chairman of the Central Military Commission of the Chinese Communist Party the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1954", "id": "1954"}], "options": ["1954", "1951", "1953", "1946"], "target_options": "1954", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_687_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_688", "question": "When did the Dir become the office holder of Grand Prince of Kiev the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "864", "id": "864"}], "options": ["865", "863", "861", "864"], "target_options": "864", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_688_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_689", "question": "When did the William Herschel become the office holder of President of the Royal Astronomical Society the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1821", "id": "1821"}], "options": ["1817", "1819", "1810", "1821"], "target_options": "1821", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_689_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_690", "question": "When did the Konrad Adenauer become the office holder of Leader of the Christian Democratic Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1935", "1946", "1926", "1934"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_690_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_691", "question": "When did the Walter Hallstein become the office holder of President of the European Commission the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1958", "id": "1958"}], "options": ["1941", "1938", "1958", "1939"], "target_options": "1958", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_691_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_692", "question": "When did the Huang Fu become the office holder of mayor of Shanghai the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1927", "id": "1927"}], "options": ["1913", "1927", "1916", "1912"], "target_options": "1927", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_692_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_693", "question": "When did the Isaac Newton become the office holder of Lucasian Professor of Mathematics the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1669", "id": "1669"}], "options": ["1966", "1669", "1976", "1978"], "target_options": "1669", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_693_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_694", "question": "When did the Yu Zhengsheng become the office holder of member of the Politburo of the Chinese Communist Party the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["1979", "2002", "1982", "1983"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_694_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_695", "question": "When did the Yu Zhengsheng become the office holder of member of the Politburo of the Chinese Communist Party the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["1986", "1977", "2002", "1987"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_695_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_696", "question": "When did the Huang Fu become the office holder of mayor of Shanghai the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1927", "id": "1927"}], "options": ["1930", "1927", "1925", "1923"], "target_options": "1927", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_696_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_697", "question": "When did the Zhang Guangjian become the office holder of mayor of Beijing the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1912", "id": "1912"}], "options": ["1912", "1896", "1889", "1895"], "target_options": "1912", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_697_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_698", "question": "When did the Herman Van Rompuy become the office holder of President of the European Council the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["2002", "2009", "1998", "2003"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_698_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_699", "question": "When did the Sauli Niinist√∂ become the office holder of President of Finland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2003", "2009", "2012", "2014"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_699_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_700", "question": "When did the Philip III of Spain become the office holder of count of Holland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1598", "id": "1598"}], "options": ["1594", "1592", "1588", "1598"], "target_options": "1598", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_700_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_701", "question": "When did the Michael Suen become the office holder of Secretary for Education the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["1996", "1998", "2007", "1988"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_701_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_702", "question": "When did Walter Gerlach become the director or manager of Fraunhofer Society the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1949", "1945", "1953", "1948"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_702_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_703", "question": "When did Duke Charles of Mecklenburg become the director or manager of Guards Corps the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1814", "id": "1814"}], "options": ["1811", "1812", "1814", "1815"], "target_options": "1814", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_703_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_704", "question": "When did Friedrich Hirzebruch become the director or manager of Max Planck Institute for Mathematics the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1980", "id": "1980"}], "options": ["1971", "1974", "1980", "1968"], "target_options": "1980", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_704_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_705", "question": "When did Wilhelm Canaris cease the director or manager of Abwehr the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1944", "id": "1944"}], "options": ["1947", "1946", "1944", "1948"], "target_options": "1944", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_705_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_706", "question": "When did Edoardo Amaldi become the director or manager of CERN the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1952", "id": "1952"}], "options": ["1952", "1939", "1940", "1932"], "target_options": "1952", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_706_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_707", "question": "When did Hermann Struve cease the director or manager of Koenigsberg Observatory the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1904", "id": "1904"}], "options": ["1939", "1946", "1904", "1948"], "target_options": "1904", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_707_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_708", "question": "When did Egon Bahr become the director or manager of Institute for Peace Research and Security Policy at the University of Hamburg the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1984", "id": "1984"}], "options": ["1980", "1984", "1977", "1976"], "target_options": "1984", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_708_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_709", "question": "When did Otto Heckmann become the director or manager of European Southern Observatory the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1962", "id": "1962"}], "options": ["1957", "1962", "1961", "1966"], "target_options": "1962", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_709_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_710", "question": "When did Helmuth von Moltke the Elder become the director or manager of German General Staff the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1857", "id": "1857"}], "options": ["1857", "1844", "1845", "1843"], "target_options": "1857", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_710_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_711", "question": "When did Joseph Passalacqua become the director or manager of Egyptian Museum of Berlin the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1828", "id": "1828"}], "options": ["1825", "1826", "1828", "1824"], "target_options": "1828", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_711_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_712", "question": "When did Franz Xaver von Zach become the director or manager of Seeberg Observatory the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1787", "id": "1787"}], "options": ["1779", "1778", "1775", "1787"], "target_options": "1787", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_712_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_713", "question": "When did Richard Courant become the director or manager of Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1935", "id": "1935"}], "options": ["1935", "1921", "1931", "1930"], "target_options": "1935", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_713_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_714", "question": "When did W. Michael Blumenthal become the director or manager of Jewish Museum Berlin the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1987", "1997", "1982", "1989"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_714_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_715", "question": "When did Georg Ratzinger become the director or manager of Regensburger Domspatzen the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1964", "id": "1964"}], "options": ["1950", "1964", "1958", "1955"], "target_options": "1964", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_715_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_716", "question": "When did Reinhard Gehlen become the director or manager of Federal Intelligence Service the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1956", "id": "1956"}], "options": ["1940", "1956", "1948", "1947"], "target_options": "1956", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_716_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_717", "question": "When did Robert Koch become the director or manager of Robert Koch Institute the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1891", "id": "1891"}], "options": ["1882", "1880", "1891", "1876"], "target_options": "1891", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_717_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_718", "question": "When did Richard Courant become the director or manager of Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1935", "id": "1935"}], "options": ["1928", "1933", "1935", "1938"], "target_options": "1935", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_718_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_719", "question": "When did Eduard Weiter cease the director or manager of Dachau concentration camp the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1949", "1939", "1945", "1947"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_719_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_720", "question": "When did European Union start sharing a border with Spain the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1957", "id": "1957"}], "options": ["1957", "1954", "1944", "1956"], "target_options": "1957", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_720_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_721", "question": "When did European Union start sharing a border with Spain the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1957", "id": "1957"}], "options": ["1952", "1942", "1955", "1957"], "target_options": "1957", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_721_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_722", "question": "When did Czechoslovakia stop sharing a border with Hungary the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1992", "1995", "1990", "1994"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_722_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_723", "question": "When did Czechoslovakia stop sharing a border with Hungary the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1986", "1992", "1996", "1994"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_723_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_724", "question": "When did Yugoslavia stop sharing a border with Italy the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1997", "1990", "1994", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_724_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_725", "question": "When did Latvia start sharing a border with Poland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1918", "id": "1918"}], "options": ["1908", "1911", "1907", "1918"], "target_options": "1918", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_725_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_726", "question": "When did Arab League start sharing a border with Turkey the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1945", "1932", "1931", "1922"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_726_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_727", "question": "When did Confederate States stop sharing a border with United States of America the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1865", "id": "1865"}], "options": ["1867", "1865", "1858", "1870"], "target_options": "1865", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_727_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_728", "question": "When did Neutral Moresnet stop sharing a border with Belgium the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1920", "id": "1920"}], "options": ["1922", "1919", "1923", "1920"], "target_options": "1920", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_728_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_729", "question": "When did Arab League start sharing a border with Turkey the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1936", "1933", "1945", "1926"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_729_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_730", "question": "When did Turkey start sharing a border with Greece the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1923", "id": "1923"}], "options": ["1915", "1907", "1923", "1918"], "target_options": "1923", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_730_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_731", "question": "When did Estonia start sharing a border with Soviet Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1918", "id": "1918"}], "options": ["1986", "1979", "1918", "1984"], "target_options": "1918", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_731_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_732", "question": "When did Latvia start sharing a border with Poland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1918", "id": "1918"}], "options": ["1981", "1918", "1984", "1973"], "target_options": "1918", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_732_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_733", "question": "When did Turkey start sharing a border with Greece the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1923", "id": "1923"}], "options": ["1918", "1922", "1926", "1923"], "target_options": "1923", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_733_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_734", "question": "When did Germany start sharing a border with Czechoslovakia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1918", "id": "1918"}], "options": ["1900", "1908", "1907", "1918"], "target_options": "1918", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_734_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_735", "question": "When did Virginia start sharing a border with Northwest Territory the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1787", "id": "1787"}], "options": ["1777", "1775", "1778", "1787"], "target_options": "1787", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_735_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_736", "question": "When did Tajikistan start sharing a border with Afghanistan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1885", "id": "1885"}], "options": ["1885", "1873", "1877", "1879"], "target_options": "1885", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_736_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_737", "question": "When did Virginia start sharing a border with Northwest Territory the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1787", "id": "1787"}], "options": ["1786", "1783", "1791", "1787"], "target_options": "1787", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_737_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_738", "question": "When did Estonia start sharing a border with Soviet Union the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1918", "id": "1918"}], "options": ["1918", "1985", "1982", "1975"], "target_options": "1918", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_738_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_739", "question": "When did Constantinople get replaced by Byzantium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "330", "id": "330"}], "options": ["326", "315", "330", "324"], "target_options": "330", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_739_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_740", "question": "When did South Australia get replaced by New South Wales the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1836", "id": "1836"}], "options": ["1836", "1828", "1822", "1830"], "target_options": "1836", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_740_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_741", "question": "When did South Australia get replaced by New South Wales the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1836", "id": "1836"}], "options": ["1829", "1823", "1836", "1831"], "target_options": "1836", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_741_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_742", "question": "When did Nazi Germany get replaced by Weimar Republic the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1944", "2024", "1949", "1947"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_742_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_743", "question": "When did Landespolizei get replaced by Volkspolizei the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1982", "1990", "1979", "1983"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_743_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_744", "question": "When did German Democratic Republic get replaced by Soviet occupation zone of Germany the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1988", "2024", "1991", "1993"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_744_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_745", "question": "When did Viken get replaced by √òstfold the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2020", "id": "2020"}], "options": ["2020", "2009", "2019", "2016"], "target_options": "2020", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_745_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_746", "question": "When did Viken get replaced by √òstfold the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2020", "id": "2020"}], "options": ["2018", "2015", "2017", "2020"], "target_options": "2020", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_746_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_747", "question": "When did canton of France get replaced by canton of France the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2012", "2014", "2008", "2015"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_747_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_748", "question": "When did Hombleux get replaced by Gr√©court the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2011", "2012", "2007", "2019"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_748_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_749", "question": "When did universal time get replaced by Greenwich Mean Time the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1925", "id": "1925"}], "options": ["1919", "1922", "1912", "1925"], "target_options": "1925", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_749_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_750", "question": "When did Scottish council area get replaced by local government area of Scotland 1975 to 1996 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1989", "1988", "1996", "1986"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_750_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_751", "question": "When did Indonesia get replaced by Dutch East Indies the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1945", "1940", "1944", "1942"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_751_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_752", "question": "When did Englon get replaced by Shanghai Maple the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2017", "2024", "2016", "2014"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_752_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_753", "question": "When did Nazi Germany get replaced by Weimar Republic the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1948", "1945", "1947"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_753_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_754", "question": "When did Alfa Romeo Racing get replaced by Sauber the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2009", "2000", "2019", "2011"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_754_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_755", "question": "When did Scuderia AlphaTauri get replaced by Scuderia Toro Rosso the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2020", "id": "2020"}], "options": ["2016", "2010", "2020", "2013"], "target_options": "2020", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_755_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_756", "question": "When did Porvoo get replaced by Porvoo the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1997", "1995", "1992", "1989"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_756_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_757", "question": "When did Jordan get replaced by Mandatory Palestine the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1948", "id": "1948"}], "options": ["1945", "1937", "1946", "1948"], "target_options": "1948", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_757_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_758", "question": "When did International Community Radio Taipei get replaced by American Forces Network the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1976", "1979", "1969", "1981"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_758_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_759", "question": "When did Avranches get replaced by Saint-Martin-des-Champs the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2011", "2002", "2010", "2019"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_759_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_760", "question": "When did Supreme Tribunal of Justice of Venezuela in exile get replaced by Supreme Tribunal of Justice of Venezuela the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1995", "1999", "1994", "1984"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_760_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_761", "question": "When did Charleroi get replaced by Ransart the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1977", "id": "1977"}], "options": ["1960", "1968", "1977", "1971"], "target_options": "1977", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_761_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_762", "question": "When did Viatris get replaced by Mylan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2020", "id": "2020"}], "options": ["2009", "2020", "2012", "2014"], "target_options": "2020", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_762_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_763", "question": "When did British Army of the Rhine get replaced by 21st Army Group the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1986", "1998", "1945", "1996"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_763_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_764", "question": "When did Northern Territory get replaced by South Australia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1911", "id": "1911"}], "options": ["1900", "1911", "1902", "1903"], "target_options": "1911", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_764_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_765", "question": "When did Gustave Eiffel University get replaced by IFSTTAR the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2020", "id": "2020"}], "options": ["2010", "2020", "2017", "2019"], "target_options": "2020", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_765_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_766", "question": "When did Dampierre get replaced by Le Petit-Mercey the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2019", "2010", "2002", "2009"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_766_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_767", "question": "When did Siikalatva get replaced by Kestil√§ the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["1999", "2009", "2008", "2005"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_767_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_768", "question": "When did Sastamala get replaced by Vammala the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["2009", "2004", "2002", "1999"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_768_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_769", "question": "When did Fontain get replaced by Arguel the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2009", "2001", "2019", "2012"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_769_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_770", "question": "When did Sastamala get replaced by Vammala the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["2004", "1998", "2009", "2003"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_770_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_771", "question": "When did Rouillac get replaced by Rouillac the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2016", "2019", "2024", "2020"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_771_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_772", "question": "When did Khanate of Kokand get replaced by Senior juz the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1879", "1878", "1876", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_772_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_773", "question": "When did Nanchez get replaced by Villard-sur-Bienne the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2010", "2019", "2013", "2012"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_773_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_774", "question": "When did BBC News get replaced by BBC World Service Television the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1988", "1992", "1991", "1985"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_774_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_775", "question": "When did Les Belleville get replaced by Saint-Jean-de-Belleville the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2010", "2012", "2019", "2013"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_775_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_776", "question": "When did Soviet Olympic Committee get replaced by Latvian Olympic Committee the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1990", "1989", "1994", "1995"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_776_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_777", "question": "When did Charleroi get replaced by Ransart the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1977", "id": "1977"}], "options": ["1977", "1962", "1967", "1970"], "target_options": "1977", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_777_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_778", "question": "When did Boeing start manufacturing Common Booster Core the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1992", "1982", "1998", "1991"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_778_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_779", "question": "When did Douglas start manufacturing Delta the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1959", "id": "1959"}], "options": ["1959", "1952", "1942", "1949"], "target_options": "1959", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_779_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_780", "question": "When did Mitsubishi Motors start manufacturing Mitsubishi Proudia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["2012", "2010", "2009", "1999"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_780_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_781", "question": "When did Intel start manufacturing Pentium D the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["1999", "2005", "1997", "1993"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_781_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_782", "question": "When did General Dynamics start manufacturing Atlas II the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1985", "1992", "1989", "1991"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_782_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_783", "question": "When did Martin Marietta start manufacturing Atlas IIAS the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1974", "1993", "1979", "1978"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_783_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_784", "question": "When did Isuzu start manufacturing Isuzu Gemini the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1963", "1965", "1959", "1974"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_784_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_785", "question": "When did General Dynamics start manufacturing Atlas IIA the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1979", "1992", "1987", "1990"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_785_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_786", "question": "When did Renault S.A. start manufacturing Mitsubishi ASX the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2023", "id": "2023"}], "options": ["2016", "2010", "2015", "2023"], "target_options": "2023", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_786_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_787", "question": "When did Mitsubishi Motors start manufacturing Mitsubishi Dignity the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["2009", "1999", "2010", "2007"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_787_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_788", "question": "When did Nissan Motor Co. Ltd. start manufacturing Suzuki Landy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["1997", "2007", "2001", "2003"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_788_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_789", "question": "When did Nissan Motor Co. Ltd. start manufacturing Nissan Livina the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["1994", "2006", "1998", "2001"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_789_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_790", "question": "When did Nissan Motor Co. Ltd. start manufacturing Nissan Livina the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["1999", "2001", "1998", "2006"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_790_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_791", "question": "When did Rabat become the capital of French protectorate in Morocco the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1912", "id": "1912"}], "options": ["1899", "1902", "1912", "1901"], "target_options": "1912", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_791_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_792", "question": "When did Manila become the capital of Commonwealth of the Philippines the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1935", "id": "1935"}], "options": ["1972", "1935", "1973", "1969"], "target_options": "1935", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_792_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_793", "question": "When did Zomba become the capital of Malawi the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1880", "id": "1880"}], "options": ["1873", "1863", "1880", "1870"], "target_options": "1880", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_793_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_794", "question": "When did Bujumbura become the capital of Burundi the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1962", "id": "1962"}], "options": ["1958", "1948", "1962", "1960"], "target_options": "1962", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_794_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_795", "question": "When did Abuja become the capital of Nigeria the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1990", "1991", "1984", "1994"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_795_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_796", "question": "When did Manila become the capital of Commonwealth of the Philippines the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1935", "id": "1935"}], "options": ["1935", "1927", "1928", "1931"], "target_options": "1935", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_796_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_797", "question": "When did Brazzaville become the capital of French Equatorial Africa the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1910", "id": "1910"}], "options": ["1892", "1898", "1901", "1910"], "target_options": "1910", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_797_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_798", "question": "When did Taipei become the capital of Taiwan under Japanese rule the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1895", "id": "1895"}], "options": ["1889", "1886", "1883", "1895"], "target_options": "1895", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_798_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_799", "question": "When did Ashgabat become the capital of Askgabat District the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1882", "id": "1882"}], "options": ["1870", "1871", "1882", "1864"], "target_options": "1882", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_799_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_800", "question": "When did Damascus become the capital of Bilad al-Sham the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "636", "id": "636"}], "options": ["1946", "636", "1934", "1944"], "target_options": "636", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_800_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_801", "question": "When did Kinshasa become the capital of Zaire the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1962", "1959", "1954", "1971"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_801_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_802", "question": "When did Aden become the capital of Yemen the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2007", "2005", "2015", "2002"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_802_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_803", "question": "When did Dushanbe become the capital of Emirate of Bukhara the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1921", "id": "1921"}], "options": ["1922", "1921", "1911", "1919"], "target_options": "1921", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_803_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_804", "question": "When did Salem become the capital of Oregon the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1859", "id": "1859"}], "options": ["1859", "1847", "1854", "1852"], "target_options": "1859", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_804_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_805", "question": "When did Riyadh become the capital of Saudi Arabia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1819", "id": "1819"}], "options": ["1819", "1816", "1808", "1815"], "target_options": "1819", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_805_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_806", "question": "When did Jerusalem become the capital of Israel the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1950", "id": "1950"}], "options": ["1950", "1945", "1948", "1939"], "target_options": "1950", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_806_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_807", "question": "When did Ciudad de la Paz become the capital of Equatorial Guinea the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2013", "2015", "2017", "2009"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_807_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_808", "question": "When did Islamabad become the capital of West Pakistan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1965", "id": "1965"}], "options": ["1951", "1960", "1961", "1965"], "target_options": "1965", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_808_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_809", "question": "When did Malabo become the capital of Spanish Guinea the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1926", "id": "1926"}], "options": ["1961", "1963", "1954", "1926"], "target_options": "1926", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_809_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_810", "question": "When did Gitega become the capital of Burundi the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2019", "2014", "2012", "2007"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_810_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_811", "question": "When did Nicosia become the capital of Kingdom of Cyprus the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1192", "id": "1192"}], "options": ["1953", "1957", "1960", "1192"], "target_options": "1192", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_811_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_812", "question": "When did Riga become the capital of Riga governorate the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1713", "id": "1713"}], "options": ["1986", "1992", "1989", "1713"], "target_options": "1713", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_812_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_813", "question": "When did Ljubljana become the capital of Illyrian Provinces the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1809", "id": "1809"}], "options": ["1984", "1978", "1809", "1987"], "target_options": "1809", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_813_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_814", "question": "When did Tokyo become the capital of Empire of Japan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1868", "id": "1868"}], "options": ["1848", "1850", "1842", "1868"], "target_options": "1868", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_814_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_815", "question": "When did Bern become the capital of Switzerland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1848", "id": "1848"}], "options": ["1840", "1848", "1838", "1832"], "target_options": "1848", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_815_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_816", "question": "When did Edo cease to be the capital of Japan the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1868", "id": "1868"}], "options": ["1870", "1865", "1873", "1868"], "target_options": "1868", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_816_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_817", "question": "When did Berlin become the capital of Germany the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1986", "1987", "1976", "1990"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_817_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_818", "question": "When did Cahaba become the capital of Alabama the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1820", "id": "1820"}], "options": ["1815", "1820", "1818", "1822"], "target_options": "1820", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_818_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_819", "question": "When did Turin become the capital of Kingdom of Sardinia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1720", "id": "1720"}], "options": ["1810", "1811", "1720", "1804"], "target_options": "1720", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_819_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_820", "question": "When did Vichy become the capital of France the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1940", "id": "1940"}], "options": ["1940", "1929", "1936", "1934"], "target_options": "1940", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_820_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_821", "question": "When did Accra become the capital of Gold Coast Colony the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1877", "id": "1877"}], "options": ["1876", "1870", "1877", "1881"], "target_options": "1877", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_821_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_822", "question": "When did Tokyo Prefecture cease to be the capital of Japan the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1943", "id": "1943"}], "options": ["1943", "1945", "1937", "1946"], "target_options": "1943", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_822_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_823", "question": "When did Montevideo become the capital of Uruguay the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1828", "id": "1828"}], "options": ["1819", "1826", "1825", "1828"], "target_options": "1828", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_823_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_824", "question": "When did Ankara become the capital of Turkey the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1923", "id": "1923"}], "options": ["1915", "1921", "1922", "1923"], "target_options": "1923", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_824_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_825", "question": "When did Annapolis become the capital of Province of Maryland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1694", "id": "1694"}], "options": ["1689", "1694", "1690", "1681"], "target_options": "1694", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_825_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_826", "question": "When did Coimbra become the capital of Portugal the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1129", "id": "1129"}], "options": ["1125", "1122", "1116", "1129"], "target_options": "1129", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_826_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_827", "question": "When did Bonn become the capital of Electorate of Cologne the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1289", "id": "1289"}], "options": ["1289", "1933", "1941", "1940"], "target_options": "1289", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_827_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_828", "question": "When did Tuscaloosa become the capital of Alabama the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1826", "id": "1826"}], "options": ["1821", "1826", "1814", "1823"], "target_options": "1826", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_828_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_829", "question": "When did Quebec City become the capital of Quebec the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1867", "id": "1867"}], "options": ["1867", "1855", "1865", "1863"], "target_options": "1867", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_829_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_830", "question": "When did Rio de Janeiro become the capital of Brazil the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1763", "id": "1763"}], "options": ["1763", "1759", "1762", "1760"], "target_options": "1763", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_830_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_831", "question": "When did Tokyo City cease to be the capital of Japan the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1943", "id": "1943"}], "options": ["1943", "1947", "1944", "1945"], "target_options": "1943", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_831_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_832", "question": "When did Helsinki become the capital of Grand Principality of Finland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1809", "id": "1809"}], "options": ["1809", "1793", "1798", "1801"], "target_options": "1809", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_832_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_833", "question": "When did Vallejo become the capital of California the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1852", "id": "1852"}], "options": ["1850", "1849", "1848", "1852"], "target_options": "1852", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_833_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_834", "question": "When did Prague become the capital of Duchy of Bohemia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "895", "id": "895"}], "options": ["1913", "1910", "895", "1902"], "target_options": "895", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_834_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_835", "question": "When did New York City become the capital of United States of America the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1785", "id": "1785"}], "options": ["1785", "1777", "1773", "1779"], "target_options": "1785", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_835_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_836", "question": "When did Belfast become the capital of Northern Ireland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1921", "id": "1921"}], "options": ["1911", "1914", "1907", "1921"], "target_options": "1921", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_836_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_837", "question": "When did Dublin become the capital of Ireland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1801", "id": "1801"}], "options": ["1786", "1784", "1776", "1801"], "target_options": "1801", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_837_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_838", "question": "When did Kyoto become the capital of Japan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "794", "id": "794"}], "options": ["794", "784", "788", "790"], "target_options": "794", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_838_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_839", "question": "When did San Jose become the capital of California the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1850", "id": "1850"}], "options": ["1831", "1850", "1840", "1843"], "target_options": "1850", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_839_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_840", "question": "When did Philadelphia become the capital of United States of America the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1790", "id": "1790"}], "options": ["1784", "1786", "1782", "1790"], "target_options": "1790", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_840_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_841", "question": "When did Budapest become the capital of Kingdom of Hungary the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1920", "id": "1920"}], "options": ["1919", "1911", "1922", "1920"], "target_options": "1920", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_841_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_842", "question": "When did Kutaisi become the capital of Georgia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2012", "2009", "2013", "2000"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_842_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_843", "question": "When did Stockholm become the capital of Sweden the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1436", "id": "1436"}], "options": ["1427", "1430", "1432", "1436"], "target_options": "1436", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_843_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_844", "question": "When did Auckland become the capital of New Zealand the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1841", "id": "1841"}], "options": ["1839", "1835", "1841", "1838"], "target_options": "1841", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_844_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_845", "question": "When did Ngerulmud become the capital of Palau the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2002", "2000", "2005", "2006"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_845_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_846", "question": "When did Quito become the capital of Ecuador the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1830", "id": "1830"}], "options": ["1822", "1820", "1830", "1824"], "target_options": "1830", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_846_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_847", "question": "When did New Delhi become the capital of British Raj the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1911", "id": "1911"}], "options": ["1896", "1888", "1898", "1911"], "target_options": "1911", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_847_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_848", "question": "When did Pyongyang become the capital of Goguryeo the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "37", "id": "37"}], "options": ["1938", "1945", "37", "1946"], "target_options": "37", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_848_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_849", "question": "When did Tegucigalpa become the capital of Honduras the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1880", "id": "1880"}], "options": ["1867", "1875", "1880", "1872"], "target_options": "1880", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_849_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_850", "question": "When did Augusta become the capital of Maine the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1832", "id": "1832"}], "options": ["1824", "1821", "1832", "1822"], "target_options": "1832", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_850_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_851", "question": "When did Kolonia become the capital of Federated States of Micronesia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1976", "1968", "1979", "1980"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_851_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_852", "question": "When did Melbourne become the capital of Port Phillip District the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1836", "id": "1836"}], "options": ["1809", "1814", "1836", "1811"], "target_options": "1836", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_852_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_853", "question": "When did Dakar Rally start being located in Africa the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1979", "1976", "1972", "1981"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_853_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_854", "question": "When did United Rugby Championship start being located in Scotland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["2001", "1999", "2002", "1994"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_854_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_855", "question": "When did Dakar Rally start being located in Africa the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1979", "1972", "1969", "1966"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_855_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_856", "question": "When did Central Group of Forces start being located in Hungary the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1941", "1945", "1933", "1944"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_856_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_857", "question": "When did United Rugby Championship start being located in Scotland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["1978", "2001", "1979", "1969"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_857_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_858", "question": "When did Central Group of Forces start being located in Hungary the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1930", "1945", "1935", "1938"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_858_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_859", "question": "When did Wiki Education Foundation start being located in San Francisco the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2004", "1997", "2006", "2013"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_859_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_860", "question": "When did Black Death start being located in Asia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1338", "id": "1338"}], "options": ["1332", "1338", "1327", "1333"], "target_options": "1338", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_860_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_861", "question": "When did Songs of David Byrne and Brian Eno Tour start being located in North America the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["2004", "2002", "1996", "2008"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_861_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_862", "question": "When did Goddard Institute for Space Studies start being located in New York City the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1961", "id": "1961"}], "options": ["1961", "1956", "1954", "1953"], "target_options": "1961", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_862_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_863", "question": "When did Songs of David Byrne and Brian Eno Tour start being located in North America the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["1993", "2000", "1999", "2008"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_863_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_864", "question": "When did Normandy Format start being located in Milan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2013", "2014", "2015", "2010"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_864_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_865", "question": "When did European Union start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Belgium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1958", "id": "1958"}], "options": ["1958", "1940", "1937", "1929"], "target_options": "1958", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_865_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_866", "question": "When did European Union start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Belgium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1958", "id": "1958"}], "options": ["1950", "1945", "1953", "1958"], "target_options": "1958", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_866_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_867", "question": "When did German Confederation stop acquiring the administrative territorial entity Luxembourg the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1866", "id": "1866"}], "options": ["1864", "1869", "1868", "1866"], "target_options": "1866", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_867_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_868", "question": "When did United Kingdom start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Northern Ireland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1921", "id": "1921"}], "options": ["1920", "1921", "1915", "1919"], "target_options": "1921", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_868_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_869", "question": "When did United States of America start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Delaware the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1787", "id": "1787"}], "options": ["1786", "1789", "1787", "1779"], "target_options": "1787", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_869_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_870", "question": "When did United States of America start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Delaware the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1787", "id": "1787"}], "options": ["1787", "1763", "1761", "1759"], "target_options": "1787", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_870_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_871", "question": "When did Confederate States stop acquiring the administrative territorial entity Alabama the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1865", "id": "1865"}], "options": ["1865", "1867", "1859", "1870"], "target_options": "1865", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_871_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_872", "question": "When did District of Columbia start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Alexandria the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1790", "id": "1790"}], "options": ["1770", "1778", "1790", "1776"], "target_options": "1790", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_872_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_873", "question": "When did Germany start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Baden-W√ºrttemberg the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1952", "id": "1952"}], "options": ["1930", "1952", "1936", "1935"], "target_options": "1952", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_873_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_874", "question": "When did District of Columbia start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Alexandria the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1790", "id": "1790"}], "options": ["1777", "1790", "1787", "1785"], "target_options": "1790", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_874_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_875", "question": "When did Yvelines start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Bois-d'Arcy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1968", "id": "1968"}], "options": ["1959", "1968", "1958", "1948"], "target_options": "1968", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_875_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_876", "question": "When did Lille metropolis start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Lille the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1967", "1959", "1962", "1963"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_876_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_877", "question": "When did Yvelines start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Bois-d'Arcy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1968", "id": "1968"}], "options": ["1953", "1963", "1968", "1966"], "target_options": "1968", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_877_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_878", "question": "When did German Confederation stop acquiring the administrative territorial entity Luxembourg the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1866", "id": "1866"}], "options": ["1871", "1866", "1868", "1859"], "target_options": "1866", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_878_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_879", "question": "When did West Sumatra start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Bukittinggi the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1957", "id": "1957"}], "options": ["1957", "1941", "1950", "1949"], "target_options": "1957", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_879_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_880", "question": "When did West Sumatra start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Bukittinggi the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1957", "id": "1957"}], "options": ["1949", "1957", "1952", "1954"], "target_options": "1957", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_880_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_881", "question": "When did Kuusiokunnat start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Alavus the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1988", "1994", "1985", "1986"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_881_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_882", "question": "When did Kuusiokunnat start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Alavus the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1989", "1994", "1990", "1991"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_882_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_883", "question": "When did Suupohja start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Karijoki the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1987", "1992", "1997", "1994"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_883_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_884", "question": "When did Suupohja start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Karijoki the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1989", "1994", "1984", "1988"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_884_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_885", "question": "When did West Germany stop acquiring the administrative territorial entity Bavaria the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1992", "1993", "1986", "1990"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_885_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_886", "question": "When did Germany start acquiring the administrative territorial entity Baden-W√ºrttemberg the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1952", "id": "1952"}], "options": ["1953", "1952", "1949", "1939"], "target_options": "1952", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_886_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_887", "question": "When did West Germany stop acquiring the administrative territorial entity Bavaria the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1988", "1990", "1992", "1993"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_887_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_888", "question": "When did Gian Piero Ventura start coaching Associazione Calcistica Dilettantistica Rapallo Ruentes 1914 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1981", "id": "1981"}], "options": ["1969", "1981", "1972", "1959"], "target_options": "1981", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_888_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_889", "question": "When did Peter Bosz start coaching AFC Ajax the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2012", "2006", "2011", "2016"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_889_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_890", "question": "When did Ottavio Bianchi start coaching ACR Siena 1904 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1978", "id": "1978"}], "options": ["1953", "1949", "1952", "1978"], "target_options": "1978", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_890_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_891", "question": "When did Marco Giampaolo start coaching Ascoli Calcio 1898 F.C. the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["1958", "2004", "1955", "1961"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_891_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_892", "question": "When did Andrea Pirlo start coaching Juventus FC the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2020", "id": "2020"}], "options": ["2014", "2020", "2007", "2015"], "target_options": "2020", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_892_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_893", "question": "When did Arrigo Sacchi start coaching Rimini F.C. the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1963", "1982", "1964", "1956"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_893_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_894", "question": "When did Dino Zoff start coaching Italy national under-23 football team the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1986", "1973", "1982", "1979"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_894_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_895", "question": "When did Marcello Lippi start coaching U.C. Sampdoria under-19 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1970", "1982", "1968", "1963"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_895_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_896", "question": "When did Antonio Conte start coaching S.S. Arezzo the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["1996", "1985", "2006", "1993"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_896_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_897", "question": "When did Eugenio Bersellini stop coaching U.S.D. Lavagnese 1919 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2019", "2021", "2006", "2016"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_897_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_898", "question": "When did Giuseppe Meazza stop coaching Inter Milan the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1957", "id": "1957"}], "options": ["1982", "1957", "1971", "1981"], "target_options": "1957", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_898_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_899", "question": "When did Laurent Blanc start coaching FC Girondins de Bordeaux the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2005", "2007", "1997", "2003"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_899_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_900", "question": "When did Arrigo Sacchi start coaching Rimini F.C. the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1969", "1961", "1968", "1982"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_900_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_901", "question": "When did Antonio Conte start coaching S.S. Arezzo the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["1998", "2001", "2003", "2006"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_901_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_902", "question": "When did Walter Zenga start coaching FC Progresul Bucure»ôti the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["1995", "1998", "2002", "1993"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_902_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_903", "question": "When did Didier Deschamps start coaching AS Monaco FC the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["1978", "1985", "2001", "1988"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_903_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_904", "question": "When did Eugenio Bersellini stop coaching U.S.D. Lavagnese 1919 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2006", "2022", "2010", "2019"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_904_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_905", "question": "When did Fabio Capello start coaching A.C. Milan Primavera the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1968", "1982", "1964", "1967"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_905_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_906", "question": "When did Armando Castellazzi stop coaching Inter Milan the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1938", "id": "1938"}], "options": ["1962", "1972", "1970", "1938"], "target_options": "1938", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_906_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_907", "question": "When did Simone Inzaghi start coaching S.S. Lazio the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2011", "2016", "2007", "2013"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_907_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_908", "question": "When did Helenio Herrera stop coaching FC Barcelona the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1981", "id": "1981"}], "options": ["1999", "1981", "2001", "1995"], "target_options": "1981", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_908_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_909", "question": "When did Carlo Ancelotti start coaching A.C. Reggiana 1919 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1995", "id": "1995"}], "options": ["1995", "1972", "1969", "1959"], "target_options": "1995", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_909_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_910", "question": "When did Stefano Pioli start coaching U.S. Salernitana 1919 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["1981", "1969", "2003", "1979"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_910_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_911", "question": "When did Luciano Spalletti start coaching Empoli F.C. the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1990", "1994", "1989", "1993"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_911_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_912", "question": "When did Claudio Ranieri start coaching Vigor Lamezia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1970", "1964", "1986", "1968"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_912_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_913", "question": "When did Giovanni Trapattoni start coaching AC Milan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1975", "1972", "1967", "1970"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_913_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_914", "question": "When did Roberto Mancini start coaching ACF Fiorentina the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["1982", "1980", "1973", "2001"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_914_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_915", "question": "When did Claudio Ranieri start coaching Vigor Lamezia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1986", "1980", "1975", "1983"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_915_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_916", "question": "When did Walter Mazzarri start coaching A.S.D. Acireale Calcio 1946 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["2001", "1983", "1977", "1986"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_916_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_917", "question": "When did Luciano Spalletti start coaching Empoli F.C. the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1992", "1986", "1994", "1989"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_917_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_918", "question": "When did Marcello Lippi start coaching U.C. Sampdoria under-19 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1963", "1964", "1957", "1982"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_918_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_919", "question": "When did Eusebio Di Francesco start coaching Lanciano Calcio 1920 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["1989", "1988", "1992", "2008"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_919_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_920", "question": "When did Andrea Pirlo start coaching Juventus FC the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2020", "id": "2020"}], "options": ["1993", "1987", "2020", "1996"], "target_options": "2020", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_920_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_921", "question": "When did Massimiliano Allegri start coaching Societ√† Polisportiva Ars et Labor the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["2004", "1978", "1987", "1986"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_921_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_922", "question": "When did Luigi Simoni stop coaching A.S. Gubbio 1910 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2019", "2022", "2017", "2012"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_922_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_923", "question": "When did Angelo Alessio start coaching Juventus FC the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2008", "2010", "2004", "2012"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_923_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_924", "question": "When did Frank de Boer start coaching AFC Ajax the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2002", "2010", "1994", "1999"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_924_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_925", "question": "When did Sylvinho start coaching Olympique Lyonnais the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2006", "2010", "2019", "2012"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_925_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_926", "question": "When did Massimiliano Allegri start coaching Societ√† Polisportiva Ars et Labor the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["1992", "1991", "2004", "1990"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_926_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_927", "question": "When did Fabio Grosso start coaching SSC Bari the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2015", "2017", "2014", "2010"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_927_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_928", "question": "When did Giuseppe Meazza stop coaching Inter Milan the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1957", "id": "1957"}], "options": ["1982", "1979", "1981", "1957"], "target_options": "1957", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_928_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_929", "question": "When did Helenio Herrera stop coaching FC Barcelona the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1981", "id": "1981"}], "options": ["1981", "1992", "2001", "1999"], "target_options": "1981", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_929_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_930", "question": "When did Roy Hodgson start coaching Halmstads BK the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1976", "id": "1976"}], "options": ["1976", "1962", "1974", "1971"], "target_options": "1976", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_930_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_931", "question": "When did Giovanni Trapattoni start coaching AC Milan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1958", "1975", "1956", "1957"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_931_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_932", "question": "When did Luigi Radice stop coaching AC Monza the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1997", "2019", "2015", "2020"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_932_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_933", "question": "When did Fabrizio Ravanelli start coaching Juventus FC the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2009", "2007", "2002", "2011"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_933_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_934", "question": "When did Maurizio Sarri start coaching A.C. Sansovino the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["1991", "2000", "1982", "1989"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_934_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_935", "question": "When did Vincenzo Montella start coaching Catania F.C. the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2008", "2011", "1995", "2005"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_935_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_936", "question": "When did Roberto Mancini start coaching ACF Fiorentina the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["2001", "1985", "1974", "1984"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_936_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_937", "question": "When did Roy Hodgson start coaching Halmstads BK the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1976", "id": "1976"}], "options": ["1930", "1932", "1976", "1921"], "target_options": "1976", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_937_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_938", "question": "When did Walter Mazzarri start coaching A.S.D. Acireale Calcio 1946 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["1991", "1979", "2001", "1989"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_938_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_939", "question": "When did Thiago Motta start coaching Genoa CFC the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2002", "2012", "2011", "2019"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_939_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_940", "question": "When did Thiago Motta start coaching Genoa CFC the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2015", "2009", "2019", "2017"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_940_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_941", "question": "When did Rolando Maran start coaching Associazione Sportiva Cittadella the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["1985", "1997", "2002", "1995"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_941_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_942", "question": "When did Ottavio Bianchi start coaching ACR Siena 1904 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1978", "id": "1978"}], "options": ["1978", "1967", "1958", "1968"], "target_options": "1978", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_942_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_943", "question": "When did Andriy Shevchenko start coaching Ukraine national association football team the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2004", "2016", "2006", "2007"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_943_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_944", "question": "When did Vincenzo Montella start coaching Catania F.C. the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2009", "2011", "2008", "1999"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_944_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_945", "question": "When did Luigi Radice stop coaching AC Monza the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["2020", "1997", "2017", "2015"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_945_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_946", "question": "When did Nedo Sonetti start coaching Viareggio Calcio the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1966", "1974", "1965", "1961"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_946_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_947", "question": "When did Andrea Mandorlini start coaching U.S. Triestina Calcio 1918 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1998", "1975", "1974", "1976"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_947_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_948", "question": "When did Nedo Sonetti start coaching Viareggio Calcio the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1975", "1972", "1974", "1965"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_948_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_949", "question": "When did Aldo Agroppi start coaching Delfino Pescara 1936 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1980", "id": "1980"}], "options": ["1954", "1964", "1980", "1961"], "target_options": "1980", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_949_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_950", "question": "When did Stefano Pioli start coaching U.S. Salernitana 1919 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2003", "1975", "1979", "1980"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_950_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_951", "question": "When did Diego Pablo Simeone start coaching Estudiantes de La Plata the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2006", "1970", "1968", "1958"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_951_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_952", "question": "When did Franco Scoglio stop coaching S.S.C. Napoli the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2010", "1999", "2007", "2003"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_952_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_953", "question": "When did Franco Scoglio stop coaching S.S.C. Napoli the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2003", "2007", "2009", "2002"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_953_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_954", "question": "When did Rolando Maran start coaching Associazione Sportiva Cittadella the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["2002", "1988", "1992", "1995"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_954_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_955", "question": "When did Aurelio Andreazzoli start coaching Genoa CFC the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2009", "2019", "2004", "2012"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_955_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_956", "question": "When did the notable work The Simpsons stop being published by Russi Taylor the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2020", "2016", "2019", "2021"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_956_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_957", "question": "When did the notable work Saturday Night Live published by Leslie Jones the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2001", "2014", "2011", "2010"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_957_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_958", "question": "When did the notable work United States Capitol stop being published by Benjamin Henry Latrobe the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1815", "1824", "1822", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_958_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_959", "question": "When did the notable work Night at the Museum published by Owen Wilson the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["1999", "2001", "2006", "1998"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_959_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_960", "question": "When did the notable work 21 Jump Street published by Holly Robinson Peete the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1987", "id": "1987"}], "options": ["1979", "1973", "1982", "1987"], "target_options": "1987", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_960_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_961", "question": "When did the notable work Today published by Savannah Guthrie the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2010", "2008", "2011", "1999"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_961_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_962", "question": "When did the notable work Today published by Al Roker the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1996", "1993", "1988", "1992"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_962_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_963", "question": "When did the notable work Today published by Barbara Walters the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1962", "id": "1962"}], "options": ["1962", "1956", "1950", "1954"], "target_options": "1962", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_963_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_964", "question": "When did the notable work Today published by Tamron Hall the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2014", "2017", "2012", "2005"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_964_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_965", "question": "When did the notable work Today published by Katie Couric the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1986", "1982", "1991", "1987"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_965_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_966", "question": "When did the notable work Today stop being published by Frank McGee the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1976", "1966", "1979", "1974"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_966_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_967", "question": "When did the notable work West 57th published by Meredith Vieira the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1985", "id": "1985"}], "options": ["1985", "1956", "1962", "1965"], "target_options": "1985", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_967_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_968", "question": "When did the notable work The Lion King published by Seth Rogen the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["1997", "2019", "2007", "2004"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_968_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_969", "question": "When did the notable work Today published by Hoda Kotb the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["2002", "1999", "2008", "1997"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_969_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_970", "question": "When did the notable work The Lion King published by James Earl Jones the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1997", "1983", "1992", "1994"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_970_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_971", "question": "When did the notable work The Cleveland Show published by Arianna Huffington the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["2005", "1998", "2008", "2004"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_971_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_972", "question": "When did the notable work Doctor Who published by Russell T Davies the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["1993", "1999", "1997", "2005"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_972_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_973", "question": "When did the notable work Nashville published by Lennon Stella the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2007", "2010", "2012", "2014"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_973_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_974", "question": "When did the notable work Green-Wood Cemetery stop being published by David Bates Douglass the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1853", "2024", "1851", "1843"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_974_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_975", "question": "When did the notable work The Big Bang Theory published by Sara Gilbert the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2001", "2004", "2007", "2000"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_975_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_976", "question": "When did the notable work The Magic Pudding published by John Cleese the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["1994", "2000", "1987", "1991"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_976_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_977", "question": "When did the notable work The Suite Life of Zack & Cody published by Dylan Sprouse the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["1995", "1987", "1997", "2005"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_977_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_978", "question": "When did the notable work The Suite Life of Zack & Cody published by Cole Sprouse the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["2005", "1999", "1997", "1998"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_978_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_979", "question": "When did the notable work Shine published by Geoffrey Rush the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1995", "1994", "1992", "1996"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_979_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_980", "question": "When did the notable work Thiel Gallery stop being published by Ferdinand Boberg the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1943", "1948", "2024", "1949"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_980_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_981", "question": "When did the notable work T. J. Hooker published by Heather Locklear the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1982", "1992", "1994", "1987"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_981_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_982", "question": "When did the notable work Spin City published by Connie Britton the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1993", "1998", "1989", "1996"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_982_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_983", "question": "When did the notable work Ellen published by Ellen DeGeneres the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1996", "1992", "1994", "1993"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_983_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_984", "question": "When did the notable work 60 Minutes stop being published by Morley Safer the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2020", "2016", "2018", "2015"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_984_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_985", "question": "When did the notable work 60 Minutes stop being published by Mike Wallace the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["2006", "2014", "2008", "2016"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_985_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_986", "question": "When did the notable work West 57th published by Meredith Vieira the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1985", "id": "1985"}], "options": ["1970", "1979", "1980", "1985"], "target_options": "1985", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_986_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_987", "question": "When did the notable work Our House published by Shannen Doherty the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1981", "1983", "1977", "1986"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_987_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_988", "question": "When did the notable work General Hospital published by Vanessa Marcil the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1972", "1992", "1970", "1969"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_988_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_989", "question": "When did the notable work America's Next Top Model published by Tyra Banks the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["1995", "1987", "1994", "2003"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_989_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_990", "question": "When did the notable work Star Trek series published by William Shatner the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1977", "1966", "1976", "1978"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_990_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_991", "question": "When did the notable work T. J. Hooker published by Heather Locklear the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1976", "1985", "1981", "1982"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_991_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_992", "question": "When did the notable work Today published by Barbara Walters the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1962", "id": "1962"}], "options": ["1962", "1947", "1949", "1946"], "target_options": "1962", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_992_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_993", "question": "When did the notable work √Ñu√üeres Burgtor stop being published by Luigi Cagnola the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1835", "1836", "1834", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_993_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_994", "question": "When did the notable work K≈çhaku Uta Gassen published by NHK the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1951", "id": "1951"}], "options": ["1951", "1945", "1953", "1949"], "target_options": "1951", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_994_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_995", "question": "When did the notable work Keeping Up with the Kardashians published by Kourtney Kardashian the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2006", "2000", "2007", "2005"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_995_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_996", "question": "When did the notable work Palace Bridge stop being published by Andrzej Pszenicki the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1916", "id": "1916"}], "options": ["1916", "1938", "1943", "1945"], "target_options": "1916", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_996_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_997", "question": "When did the notable work Keeping Up with the Kardashians published by Rob Kardashian the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2006", "2003", "2007", "2008"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_997_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_998", "question": "When did the notable work Pinacoteca di Brera stop being published by Piero Portaluppi the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1925", "id": "1925"}], "options": ["1925", "1969", "1968", "1971"], "target_options": "1925", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_998_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_999", "question": "When did the notable work Glee stop being published by Naya Rivera the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2017", "2021", "2015", "2022"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_999_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1000", "question": "When did the notable work Keeping Up with the Kardashians published by Kris Jenner the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["1998", "2007", "2000", "1992"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1000_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1001", "question": "When did the notable work Keeping Up with the Kardashians published by Scott Disick the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2002", "2007", "2000", "1994"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1001_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1002", "question": "When did the notable work Melrose Place published by Alyssa Milano the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1995", "1988", "1994", "1997"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1002_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1003", "question": "When did the notable work Charmed published by Holly Marie Combs the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1998", "1988", "1997", "1999"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1003_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1004", "question": "When did the notable work Charmed published by Rose McGowan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["1991", "1994", "1997", "2001"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1004_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1005", "question": "When did the notable work Scooby-Doo published by Frank Welker the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1969", "id": "1969"}], "options": ["1973", "1969", "1968", "1966"], "target_options": "1969", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1005_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1006", "question": "When did the notable work Bones published by Tamara Taylor the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["1999", "2001", "1990", "2006"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1006_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1007", "question": "When did the notable work Scooby-Doo stop being published by Don Messick the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["2001", "1990", "1996", "1999"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1007_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1008", "question": "When did the notable work Scooby-Doo published by Matthew Lillard the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["2004", "2008", "2002", "2010"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1008_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1009", "question": "When did the notable work Messiah stop being published by Charles Jennens the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1742", "id": "1742"}], "options": ["1773", "1775", "1742", "1778"], "target_options": "1742", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1009_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1010", "question": "When did the notable work A.N.T. Farm published by China Anne McClain the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2011", "2005", "2003", "1998"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1010_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1011", "question": "When did the notable work Murphy Brown published by Candice Bergen the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1988", "id": "1988"}], "options": ["1999", "1988", "2000", "2003"], "target_options": "1988", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1011_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1012", "question": "When did the notable work Shake It Up published by Zendaya the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2000", "2010", "2003", "1990"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1012_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1013", "question": "When did the notable work Sukhoi Su-34 stop being published by Rollan Martirosov the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2019", "2022", "2017", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1013_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1014", "question": "When did the notable work diffusion of innovations stop being published by Everett Rogers the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2007", "2005", "2024", "2006"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1014_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1015", "question": "When did the notable work All Night Nippon published by Nippon Broadcasting System the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1968", "1967", "1966", "1960"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1015_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1016", "question": "When did the occupation of Stadio Olimpico Grande Torino by Juventus FC start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1933", "id": "1933"}], "options": ["1918", "1916", "1917", "1933"], "target_options": "1933", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1016_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1017", "question": "When did the occupation of Stadio Olimpico Grande Torino by Juventus FC start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1933", "id": "1933"}], "options": ["1917", "1923", "1926", "1933"], "target_options": "1933", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1017_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1018", "question": "When did the occupation of Giuseppe Meazza Stadium by AC Milan start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1926", "id": "1926"}], "options": ["1920", "1912", "1918", "1926"], "target_options": "1926", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1018_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1019", "question": "When did the occupation of Stadio Olimpico by S.S. Lazio start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1953", "id": "1953"}], "options": ["1951", "1941", "1950", "1953"], "target_options": "1953", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1019_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1020", "question": "When did the occupation of Stadio Olimpico by S.S. Lazio start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1953", "id": "1953"}], "options": ["1947", "1949", "1938", "1953"], "target_options": "1953", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1020_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1021", "question": "When did the occupation of Stadio delle Alpi by Torino Football Club end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2011", "2005", "2012", "2006"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1021_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1022", "question": "When did the occupation of Stadio delle Alpi by Torino Football Club end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2001", "2006", "2011", "2012"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1022_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1023", "question": "When did the occupation of Stadio Flaminio by Rugby Roma start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1970", "id": "1970"}], "options": ["1970", "1971", "1961", "1969"], "target_options": "1970", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1023_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1024", "question": "When did the occupation of Stadio Flaminio by Rugby Roma start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1970", "id": "1970"}], "options": ["1904", "1913", "1910", "1970"], "target_options": "1970", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1024_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1025", "question": "When did the occupation of Giuseppe Meazza Stadium by AC Milan start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1926", "id": "1926"}], "options": ["1926", "1921", "1918", "1922"], "target_options": "1926", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1025_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1026", "question": "When did the occupation of One Times Square by The New York Times start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1905", "id": "1905"}], "options": ["1896", "1895", "1905", "1893"], "target_options": "1905", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1026_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1027", "question": "When did the occupation of Birthplace of Richard Nixon by Richard Nixon start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1913", "id": "1913"}], "options": ["1914", "1912", "1909", "1913"], "target_options": "1913", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1027_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1028", "question": "When did the occupation of RAF Burtonwood by United States Army end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1991", "1999", "1996", "1994"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1028_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1029", "question": "When did the occupation of Arsenal Stadium by Arsenal F.C. end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2008", "2006", "2009", "2012"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1029_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1030", "question": "When did the occupation of Barnet Copthall by London Broncos start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1993", "2000", "2010", "2009"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1030_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1031", "question": "When did the occupation of MEK Compound by People's Mojahedin Organization of Iran start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1986", "1983", "1978", "1998"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1031_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1032", "question": "When did the occupation of Fort Frederiksborg by Denmark‚ÄìNorway start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1661", "id": "1661"}], "options": ["1637", "1661", "1647", "1649"], "target_options": "1661", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1032_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1033", "question": "When did the occupation of Marlborough House by Commonwealth of Nations start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1965", "id": "1965"}], "options": ["1959", "1965", "1960", "1955"], "target_options": "1965", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1033_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1034", "question": "When did the occupation of Eurotower by Bank f√ºr Gemeinwirtschaft start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1977", "id": "1977"}], "options": ["1977", "1961", "1964", "1954"], "target_options": "1977", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1034_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1035", "question": "When did the occupation of Cape Coast Castle by Swedish overseas colonies start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1650", "id": "1650"}], "options": ["1650", "1648", "1637", "1645"], "target_options": "1650", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1035_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1036", "question": "When did the occupation of Montjuic Olympic Stadium by Barcelona Dragons start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1984", "1978", "1987", "1991"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1036_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1037", "question": "When did the occupation of Royal Palace of Amsterdam by Louis Bonaparte start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1808", "id": "1808"}], "options": ["1807", "1812", "1808", "1806"], "target_options": "1808", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1037_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1038", "question": "When did the occupation of Stadio Alberto Braglia by U.S. Sassuolo Calcio start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["2008", "2004", "1999", "2001"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1038_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1039", "question": "When did the occupation of Rembrandt House Museum by Saskia van Uylenburgh start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1639", "id": "1639"}], "options": ["1631", "1639", "1634", "1637"], "target_options": "1639", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1039_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1040", "question": "When did the occupation of Anfield by Everton F.C. start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1884", "id": "1884"}], "options": ["1884", "1882", "1885", "1873"], "target_options": "1884", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1040_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1041", "question": "When did the occupation of Braunes Haus by Nazi Party end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1950", "1937", "2024", "1947"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1041_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1042", "question": "When did the occupation of Montjuic Olympic Stadium by Barcelona Dragons start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["2016", "2015", "2007", "1991"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1042_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1043", "question": "When did the occupation of Charlottenhof Palace by Alexander von Humboldt start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1835", "id": "1835"}], "options": ["1827", "1835", "1820", "1825"], "target_options": "1835", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1043_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1044", "question": "When did the occupation of Einsteinhaus by Albert Einstein start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1903", "id": "1903"}], "options": ["1891", "1895", "1894", "1903"], "target_options": "1903", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1044_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1045", "question": "When did the occupation of Bolshiye Gorki by Vladimir Lenin start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1918", "id": "1918"}], "options": ["1908", "1905", "1918", "1910"], "target_options": "1918", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1045_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1046", "question": "When did the occupation of Berghof by Adolf Hitler end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1944", "1954", "1955"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1046_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1047", "question": "When did World Union for Progressive Judaism establish its headquarters in London the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1926", "id": "1926"}], "options": ["1908", "1906", "1926", "1911"], "target_options": "1926", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1047_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1048", "question": "When did Fawcett Publications establish its headquarters in Minneapolis the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1919", "id": "1919"}], "options": ["1914", "1917", "1904", "1919"], "target_options": "1919", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1048_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1049", "question": "When did Automobile Manufacturers Association move its headquarters from Detroit the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["2001", "1992", "2005", "2003"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1049_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1050", "question": "When did Erie Railroad move its headquarters from Cleveland the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1967", "1960", "1965", "1962"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1050_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1051", "question": "When did College Art Association establish its headquarters in New York City the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2011", "2007", "2010", "2012"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1051_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1052", "question": "When did Fleischer Studios move its headquarters from Florida the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1942", "id": "1942"}], "options": ["1937", "1944", "1945", "1942"], "target_options": "1942", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1052_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1053", "question": "When did Foot Locker establish its headquarters in New York City the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2015", "2004", "2011", "2014"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1053_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1054", "question": "When did Doghouse Records establish its headquarters in Toledo the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1988", "id": "1988"}], "options": ["1988", "1984", "1980", "1986"], "target_options": "1988", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1054_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1055", "question": "When did American Petroleum Institute establish its headquarters in New York City the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1919", "id": "1919"}], "options": ["1917", "1919", "1914", "1918"], "target_options": "1919", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1055_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1056", "question": "When did Standard Oil move its headquarters from New York City the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1911", "id": "1911"}], "options": ["1916", "1918", "1911", "1913"], "target_options": "1911", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1056_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1057", "question": "When did Nickelodeon Animation Studio establish its headquarters in Studio City the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1983", "1990", "1980", "1973"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1057_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1058", "question": "When did MetLife establish its headquarters in New York City the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1909", "id": "1909"}], "options": ["1904", "1902", "1903", "1909"], "target_options": "1909", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1058_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1059", "question": "When did American Association for Justice establish its headquarters in Washington, D.C. the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1977", "id": "1977"}], "options": ["1977", "1972", "1974", "1963"], "target_options": "1977", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1059_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1060", "question": "When did United Aircraft and Transport Corporation move its headquarters from New York City the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1936", "1939", "2024", "1928"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1060_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1061", "question": "When did United States Census Bureau establish its headquarters in Washington, D.C. the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1902", "id": "1902"}], "options": ["1897", "1895", "1902", "1887"], "target_options": "1902", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1061_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1062", "question": "When did American Petroleum Institute establish its headquarters in New York City the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1919", "id": "1919"}], "options": ["1907", "1917", "1920", "1919"], "target_options": "1919", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1062_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1063", "question": "When did Code for America establish its headquarters in San Francisco the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2005", "2007", "2009", "2012"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1063_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1064", "question": "When did Code for America establish its headquarters in San Francisco the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2009", "2011", "2014", "2012"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1064_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1065", "question": "When did Port Authority of New York and New Jersey establish its headquarters in New York City the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1973", "id": "1973"}], "options": ["1973", "1967", "1966", "1957"], "target_options": "1973", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1065_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1066", "question": "When did Port Authority of New York and New Jersey establish its headquarters in New York City the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1973", "id": "1973"}], "options": ["1973", "1970", "1960", "1968"], "target_options": "1973", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1066_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1067", "question": "When did Air Force Global Strike Command establish its headquarters in Washington, D.C. the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1944", "id": "1944"}], "options": ["1945", "1939", "1943", "1944"], "target_options": "1944", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1067_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1068", "question": "When did United States Department of Commerce establish its headquarters in Washington, D.C. the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1932", "id": "1932"}], "options": ["1925", "1932", "1918", "1923"], "target_options": "1932", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1068_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1069", "question": "When did Supreme Court of the United States establish its headquarters in Old Senate Chamber the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1860", "id": "1860"}], "options": ["1860", "1844", "1851", "1849"], "target_options": "1860", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1069_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1070", "question": "When did Gallup establish its headquarters in Washington, D.C. the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["1994", "1996", "1998", "2000"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1070_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1071", "question": "When did Washington Spirit establish its headquarters in Germantown the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2009", "2002", "2010", "2012"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1071_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1072", "question": "When did Mozilla Corporation establish its headquarters in San Francisco the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2021", "id": "2021"}], "options": ["2023", "2019", "2021", "2012"], "target_options": "2021", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1072_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1073", "question": "When did China Zhi Gong Party establish its headquarters in San Francisco the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1925", "id": "1925"}], "options": ["1926", "1925", "1924", "1922"], "target_options": "1925", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1073_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1074", "question": "When did SVB Financial Group establish its headquarters in San Jose the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1983", "id": "1983"}], "options": ["1966", "1960", "1964", "1983"], "target_options": "1983", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1074_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1075", "question": "When did The Baffler establish its headquarters in Charlottesville the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1988", "id": "1988"}], "options": ["1970", "1972", "1971", "1988"], "target_options": "1988", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1075_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1076", "question": "When did the performaner of M by Bernard Lee start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1962", "id": "1962"}], "options": ["1986", "1962", "1990", "1993"], "target_options": "1962", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1076_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1077", "question": "When did the performaner of M by Bernard Lee start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1962", "id": "1962"}], "options": ["1964", "1954", "1961", "1962"], "target_options": "1962", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1077_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1078", "question": "When did the performaner of Lord Voldemort by Eddie Izzard end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2017", "1999", "2000", "2003"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1078_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1079", "question": "When did the performaner of Shaggy Rogers by Casey Kasem start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1969", "id": "1969"}], "options": ["1938", "1932", "1969", "1937"], "target_options": "1969", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1079_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1080", "question": "When did the performaner of Q by Peter Burton start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1962", "id": "1962"}], "options": ["1958", "1962", "1948", "1956"], "target_options": "1962", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1080_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1081", "question": "When did the performaner of Princess Protection Program by Demi Lovato start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["2009", "2008", "2013", "2003"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1081_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1082", "question": "When did the performaner of Another Cinderella Story by Selena Gomez start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["1995", "2000", "2008", "1999"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1082_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1083", "question": "When did the performaner of Greg Heffley by Zachary Gordon start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2008", "2001", "2006", "2010"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1083_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1084", "question": "When did the performaner of Linda Perry by 4 Non Blondes start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1989", "1979", "1982", "1969"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1084_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1085", "question": "When did the performaner of Lord Voldemort by Eddie Izzard end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["1991", "2001", "2000", "2017"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1085_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1086", "question": "When did the performaner of Lola Bunny by Kath Soucie start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1991", "1988", "1978", "1996"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1086_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1087", "question": "When did the performaner of Hello Kitty by Megumi Hayashibara start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1985", "1992", "1990", "1988"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1087_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1088", "question": "When did the performaner of Winnie the Pooh by Sterling Holloway start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1981", "1980", "1975", "1966"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1088_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1089", "question": "When did the performaner of Mickey Mouse by Chris Diamantopoulos start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2013", "1995", "2005", "2007"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1089_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1090", "question": "When did the performaner of Gopher by Howard Morris start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1958", "1966", "1962", "1965"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1090_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1091", "question": "When did the performaner of Q by Peter Burton start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1962", "id": "1962"}], "options": ["1962", "2004", "2006", "2003"], "target_options": "1962", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1091_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1092", "question": "When did the performaner of Donald Duck by Clarence Nash start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1934", "id": "1934"}], "options": ["1930", "1933", "1925", "1934"], "target_options": "1934", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1092_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1093", "question": "When did the performaner of Lola Bunny by Kath Soucie start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1979", "1978", "1980", "1996"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1093_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1094", "question": "When did the performaner of Gomez Addams by John Astin start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1964", "id": "1964"}], "options": ["1963", "1958", "1964", "1965"], "target_options": "1964", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1094_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1095", "question": "When did the performaner of Mac Tonight by Doug Jones start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1986", "1977", "1979", "1981"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1095_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1096", "question": "When did the performaner of Oscar the Grouch by Caroll Spinney start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1969", "id": "1969"}], "options": ["1961", "1957", "1969", "1964"], "target_options": "1969", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1096_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1097", "question": "When did the performaner of Scooter by Richard Hunt start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1976", "id": "1976"}], "options": ["1973", "1976", "1969", "1970"], "target_options": "1976", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1097_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1098", "question": "When did the performaner of Luigi by Charles Martinet start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1981", "1983", "1982", "1992"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1098_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1099", "question": "When did the performaner of Doctor Eggman by Long John Baldry start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1985", "1978", "1984", "1993"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1099_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1100", "question": "When did the performaner of Winnie the Pooh by Sterling Holloway start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1957", "1946", "1956", "1966"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1100_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1101", "question": "When did the performaner of Donald Duck by Clarence Nash start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1934", "id": "1934"}], "options": ["1934", "1902", "1906", "1905"], "target_options": "1934", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1101_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1102", "question": "When did the performaner of Pluto by Pinto Colvig start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1931", "id": "1931"}], "options": ["1921", "1931", "1924", "1925"], "target_options": "1931", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1102_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1103", "question": "When did Jeongja Station become the adjacent station of Pangyo Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2011", "2014", "2010", "2000"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1103_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1104", "question": "When did Ori Station become the adjacent station of Migeum Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1994", "1981", "1985", "1988"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1104_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1105", "question": "When did Cheongnyangni Station become the adjacent station of Wangsimni Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1911", "id": "1911"}], "options": ["1891", "1911", "1900", "1897"], "target_options": "1911", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1105_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1106", "question": "When did Cheongnyangni Station become the adjacent station of Wangsimni Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1911", "id": "1911"}], "options": ["1904", "1910", "1911", "1915"], "target_options": "1911", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1106_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1107", "question": "When did Sha Tin station become the adjacent station of Tai Po Kau railway station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1910", "id": "1910"}], "options": ["1905", "1909", "1908", "1910"], "target_options": "1910", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1107_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1108", "question": "When did Nonhyeon Station become the adjacent station of Sinnonhyeon Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2017", "2022", "2016", "2014"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1108_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1109", "question": "When did Migeum Station become the adjacent station of Ori Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1987", "1984", "1994", "1975"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1109_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1110", "question": "When did Nambu Bus Terminal Station become the adjacent station of Yangjae Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1985", "id": "1985"}], "options": ["1974", "1985", "1975", "1972"], "target_options": "1985", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1110_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1111", "question": "When did Ori Station become the adjacent station of Bojeong Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["2004", "2007", "1994", "2003"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1111_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1112", "question": "When did Migeum Station become the adjacent station of Ori Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1972", "1981", "1984", "1994"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1112_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1113", "question": "When did Bojeong Station become the adjacent station of Jukjeon Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["1999", "2004", "2007", "2006"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1113_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1114", "question": "When did Sunae Station become the adjacent station of Jeongja Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1994", "1986", "1984", "1989"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1114_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1115", "question": "When did Sunae Station become the adjacent station of Jeongja Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1985", "1988", "1994", "1990"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1115_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1116", "question": "When did Suji-gu Office Station become the adjacent station of Dongcheon Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2016", "2009", "2000", "2010"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1116_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1117", "question": "When did Jeongja Station become the adjacent station of Pangyo Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2008", "2004", "2010", "2011"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1117_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1118", "question": "When did Yatap Station become the adjacent station of Imae Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["1994", "2005", "2002", "2004"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1118_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1119", "question": "When did Yatap Station become the adjacent station of Imae Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["1991", "2004", "1994", "1997"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1119_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1120", "question": "When did Seoul National University of Education Station become the adjacent station of Gangnam Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1982", "1949", "1942", "1950"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1120_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1121", "question": "When did Sinnonhyeon Station become the adjacent station of Nonhyeon Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2015", "2004", "2012", "2022"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1121_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1122", "question": "When did Toei Subway Shinjuku Station become the adjacent station of Yoyogi Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["1990", "2000", "2001", "1999"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1122_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1123", "question": "When did Liujiayao station become the adjacent station of Songjiazhuang station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2004", "2006", "2007", "1999"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1123_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1124", "question": "When did Jamsillaru Station become the adjacent station of Jamsil Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1980", "id": "1980"}], "options": ["1980", "1973", "1964", "1972"], "target_options": "1980", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1124_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1125", "question": "When did Jamsillaru Station become the adjacent station of Jamsil Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1980", "id": "1980"}], "options": ["1964", "1967", "1980", "1957"], "target_options": "1980", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1125_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1126", "question": "When did Wanshou Lu station become the adjacent station of Gongzhufen station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1971", "1958", "1970", "1967"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1126_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1127", "question": "When did Chedaogou station become the adjacent station of Cishou Si station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2014", "2011", "2004", "2012"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1127_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1128", "question": "When did Keisei ≈åkubo Station become the adjacent station of Keisei Tsudanuma Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1926", "id": "1926"}], "options": ["1917", "1920", "1919", "1926"], "target_options": "1926", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1128_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1129", "question": "When did Sinnonhyeon Station become the adjacent station of Nonhyeon Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2022", "2017", "2019", "2021"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1129_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1130", "question": "When did Nambu Bus Terminal Station become the adjacent station of Yangjae Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1985", "id": "1985"}], "options": ["1968", "1978", "1981", "1985"], "target_options": "1985", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1130_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1131", "question": "When did Seoul National University of Education Station become the adjacent station of Gangnam Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1974", "1975", "1964", "1982"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1131_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1132", "question": "When did Bucheon Stadium Station become the adjacent station of Sosa Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2023", "id": "2023"}], "options": ["2017", "2015", "2023", "2005"], "target_options": "2023", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1132_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1133", "question": "When did Nonhyeon Station become the adjacent station of Sinsa Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2013", "2022", "2012", "2011"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1133_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1134", "question": "When did Nonhyeon Station become the adjacent station of Sinnonhyeon Station start the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2022", "2016", "2005", "2015"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1134_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1135", "question": "When did Shawn Michaels become the presenter of WWE NXT the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2014", "2017", "2022", "2018"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1135_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1136", "question": "When did Jeremy Clarkson become the presenter of Robot Wars the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1991", "1989", "1998", "1987"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1136_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1137", "question": "When did Stephen Colbert become the presenter of The Late Show with Stephen Colbert the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["1998", "2008", "2015", "2009"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1137_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1138", "question": "When did Craig Kilborn become the presenter of The Daily Show Mondays with Jon Stewart the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1996", "1997", "1990", "1994"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1138_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1139", "question": "When did Stephen Colbert become the presenter of The Colbert Report the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["2001", "1998", "2002", "2005"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1139_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1140", "question": "When did Craig Kilborn become the presenter of The Daily Show Mondays with Jon Stewart the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1996", "1986", "1993", "1994"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1140_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1141", "question": "When did Jason Dawe become the presenter of Top Gear the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["1996", "1993", "2002", "1988"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1141_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1142", "question": "When did Arnim Basche become the presenter of Sportschau the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1964", "id": "1964"}], "options": ["1952", "1959", "1961", "1964"], "target_options": "1964", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1142_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1143", "question": "When did Arnim Basche become the presenter of Sportschau the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1964", "id": "1964"}], "options": ["1961", "1964", "1952", "1962"], "target_options": "1964", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1143_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1144", "question": "When did Wolf von Lojewski become the presenter of Tagesthemen the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1978", "id": "1978"}], "options": ["1978", "1974", "1975", "1969"], "target_options": "1978", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1144_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1145", "question": "When did Dave Garroway become the presenter of Today the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1952", "id": "1952"}], "options": ["1948", "1936", "1945", "1952"], "target_options": "1952", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1145_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1146", "question": "When did Bud Collyer become the presenter of To Tell the Truth the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1956", "id": "1956"}], "options": ["1956", "2015", "2018", "2006"], "target_options": "1956", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1146_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1147", "question": "When did Jason Dawe become the presenter of Top Gear the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["1994", "2000", "2002", "2001"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1147_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1148", "question": "When did Joel McHale become the presenter of Card Sharks the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2019", "2010", "2014", "2011"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1148_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1149", "question": "When did Steve Allen become the presenter of The Tonight Show the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1954", "id": "1954"}], "options": ["1954", "1931", "1930", "1928"], "target_options": "1954", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1149_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1150", "question": "When did Steve Allen become the presenter of The Tonight Show the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1954", "id": "1954"}], "options": ["1943", "1940", "1931", "1954"], "target_options": "1954", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1150_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1151", "question": "When did Stefan G√∂dde become the presenter of The Voice of Germany the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2011", "2010", "2000", "2009"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1151_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1152", "question": "When did Wolf von Lojewski become the presenter of Tagesthemen the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1978", "id": "1978"}], "options": ["1978", "1961", "1958", "1962"], "target_options": "1978", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1152_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1153", "question": "When did Tom Snyder become the presenter of The Late Late Show with James Corden the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1995", "id": "1995"}], "options": ["1969", "1971", "1961", "1995"], "target_options": "1995", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1153_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1154", "question": "When did Emile Guillemin stop being exhibited in Louvre Museum the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1899", "id": "1899"}], "options": ["1912", "1903", "1909", "1899"], "target_options": "1899", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1154_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1155", "question": "When did Madonna of Jacob Floreins start being exhibited in Louvre Museum the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1986", "1989", "1978", "1983"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1155_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1156", "question": "When did Antonio Rotta stop being exhibited in arts association the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1897", "1906", "1905", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1156_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1157", "question": "When did The Return of the Prodigal Son start being exhibited in Hermitage Museum the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1767", "id": "1767"}], "options": ["1767", "1766", "1757", "1770"], "target_options": "1767", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1157_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1158", "question": "When did Boxer at Rest start being exhibited in Metropolitan Museum of Art the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2013", "2003", "2008", "2007"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1158_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1159", "question": "When did nihonium start being named after Japan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2012", "2011", "2010", "2016"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1159_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1160", "question": "When did Washington start being named after George Washington the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1837", "id": "1837"}], "options": ["1830", "1837", "1832", "1835"], "target_options": "1837", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1160_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1161", "question": "When did Lincoln start being named after Abraham Lincoln the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1867", "id": "1867"}], "options": ["1867", "1853", "1859", "1857"], "target_options": "1867", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1161_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1162", "question": "When did Pariser Platz start being named after Paris the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1814", "id": "1814"}], "options": ["1797", "1807", "1814", "1809"], "target_options": "1814", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1162_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1163", "question": "When did Lincoln start being named after Abraham Lincoln the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1853", "id": "1853"}], "options": ["1847", "1854", "1853", "1850"], "target_options": "1853", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1163_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1164", "question": "When did Central do Brasil start being named after Pedro II of Brazil the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1898", "id": "1898"}], "options": ["1875", "1883", "1882", "1898"], "target_options": "1898", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1164_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1165", "question": "When did hydrogen start being named after water the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1783", "id": "1783"}], "options": ["1774", "1781", "1782", "1783"], "target_options": "1783", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1165_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1166", "question": "When did Chornomorsk start being named after Vladimir Lenin the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1952", "id": "1952"}], "options": ["1944", "1952", "1947", "1934"], "target_options": "1952", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1166_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1167", "question": "When did Niels stop holding the noble title king the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1134", "id": "1134"}], "options": ["1137", "1134", "1130", "1136"], "target_options": "1134", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1167_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1168", "question": "When did Tristan stop holding the noble title king the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["589", "578", "2024", "587"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1168_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1169", "question": "When did George I of Great Britain stop holding the noble title king the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1727", "id": "1727"}], "options": ["1730", "1724", "1729", "1727"], "target_options": "1727", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1169_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1170", "question": "When did Saban start holding the noble title king the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "234", "id": "234"}], "options": ["222", "230", "234", "231"], "target_options": "234", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1170_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1171", "question": "When did Christian IX of Denmark stop holding the noble title king the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1906", "id": "1906"}], "options": ["1909", "1908", "1898", "1906"], "target_options": "1906", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1171_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1172", "question": "When did Daru stop holding the noble title king the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "77", "id": "77"}], "options": ["79", "81", "72", "77"], "target_options": "77", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1172_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1173", "question": "When did Giru stop holding the noble title king the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "128", "id": "128"}], "options": ["128", "132", "130", "125"], "target_options": "128", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1173_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1174", "question": "When did Gaeru stop holding the noble title king the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "166", "id": "166"}], "options": ["166", "169", "165", "168"], "target_options": "166", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1174_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1175", "question": "When did Goi stop holding the noble title king the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "286", "id": "286"}], "options": ["285", "286", "288", "289"], "target_options": "286", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1175_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1176", "question": "When did Gusu stop holding the noble title king the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "234", "id": "234"}], "options": ["239", "234", "236", "233"], "target_options": "234", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1176_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1177", "question": "When did Chogo stop holding the noble title king the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "214", "id": "214"}], "options": ["214", "216", "213", "217"], "target_options": "214", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1177_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1178", "question": "When did Rudolf Duala Manga Bell stop holding the noble title king the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1914", "id": "1914"}], "options": ["1907", "1916", "1914", "1917"], "target_options": "1914", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1178_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1179", "question": "When did Ndumbe Lobe Bell stop holding the noble title king the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1897", "id": "1897"}], "options": ["1895", "1900", "1897", "1899"], "target_options": "1897", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1179_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1180", "question": "When did Stotzas stop holding the noble title king the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["537", "547", "550", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1180_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1181", "question": "When did Rasoherina I of Madagascar stop holding the noble title queen regnant the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1868", "id": "1868"}], "options": ["1868", "1861", "1871", "1870"], "target_options": "1868", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1181_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1182", "question": "When did Ranavalona II of Madagascar stop holding the noble title queen regnant the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1883", "id": "1883"}], "options": ["1883", "1885", "1878", "1888"], "target_options": "1883", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1182_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1183", "question": "When did Rudrama Devi stop holding the noble title queen regnant the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1289", "id": "1289"}], "options": ["1289", "1281", "1293", "1291"], "target_options": "1289", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1183_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1184", "question": "When did Margrethe II of Denmark start holding the noble title princess the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1940", "id": "1940"}], "options": ["1937", "1942", "1938", "1940"], "target_options": "1940", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1184_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1185", "question": "When did Frederick William von Hessenstein stop holding the noble title Prince of the Holy Roman Empire the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1812", "1810", "1804", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1185_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1186", "question": "When did Otto Magnus von Stackelberg stop holding the noble title graf the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1802", "1801", "1805"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1186_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1187", "question": "When did Florent van Ertborn stop holding the noble title knight the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1844", "1837", "2024", "1842"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1187_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1188", "question": "When did Emperor Norton stop holding the noble title Protector the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1882", "1884", "1875", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1188_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1189", "question": "When did Emperor Zhenzong of Song stop holding the noble title emperor the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1026", "1024", "1020", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1189_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1190", "question": "When did Liu Shan stop holding the noble title gong the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "271", "id": "271"}], "options": ["269", "271", "276", "273"], "target_options": "271", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1190_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1191", "question": "When did Kharak Singh stop holding the noble title emperor the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1840", "id": "1840"}], "options": ["1844", "1840", "1834", "1842"], "target_options": "1840", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1191_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1192", "question": "When did Charles I of Bourbon stop holding the noble title graf the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1456", "id": "1456"}], "options": ["1458", "1456", "1452", "1460"], "target_options": "1456", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1192_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1193", "question": "When did Raymond Ceulemans start holding the noble title knight the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["1996", "2002", "2004", "2001"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1193_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1194", "question": "When did William Alexander Smith stop holding the noble title knight the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1916", "2024", "1918", "1911"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1194_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1195", "question": "When did Ashton Lever stop holding the noble title knight the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1790", "1792", "1780"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1195_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1196", "question": "When did Rheinische Zeitung stop being edited by Karl Marx the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1848", "1845", "1841"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1196_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1197", "question": "When did Sovremennik stop being edited by Alexander Pushkin the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1837", "id": "1837"}], "options": ["1864", "1837", "1868", "1869"], "target_options": "1837", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1197_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1198", "question": "When did Great Soviet Encyclopedia start being edited by Otto Schmidt the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1924", "id": "1924"}], "options": ["1956", "1924", "1967", "1964"], "target_options": "1924", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1198_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1199", "question": "When did Playboy start being edited by Hugh Hefner the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1953", "id": "1953"}], "options": ["1953", "1946", "1948", "1949"], "target_options": "1953", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1199_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1200", "question": "When did Byzantinische Zeitschrift start being edited by Karl Krumbacher the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1892", "id": "1892"}], "options": ["1888", "1892", "1878", "1891"], "target_options": "1892", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1200_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1201", "question": "When did Byzantinische Zeitschrift start being edited by Karl Krumbacher the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1892", "id": "1892"}], "options": ["1882", "1892", "1879", "1885"], "target_options": "1892", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1201_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1202", "question": "When did Ken Block start participating in Rally America the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["2005", "2000", "2004", "2008"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1202_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1203", "question": "When did John Franklin stop participating in Franklin's lost expedition the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1848", "id": "1848"}], "options": ["1844", "1848", "1851", "1849"], "target_options": "1848", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1203_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1204", "question": "When did Romain Grosjean start participating in Formula One the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["1997", "1999", "2009", "2001"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1204_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1205", "question": "When did Felipe Massa start participating in Formula Renault Eurocup the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["1996", "1991", "1999", "2000"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1205_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1206", "question": "When did George Russell start participating in Formula Renault the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2014", "2010", "2011", "2007"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1206_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1207", "question": "When did Jens Fiedler start participating in 1992 Summer Olympics the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1988", "1983", "1992", "1990"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1207_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1208", "question": "When did Maria Sole Ferrieri Caputi start participating in Coppa Italia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2007", "2001", "1994", "1999"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1208_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1209", "question": "When did Leo Franco start participating in 2006 FIFA World Cup the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["1997", "1998", "2006", "2001"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1209_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1210", "question": "When did Abraham Pomerantz stop participating in Nuremberg trials the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1947", "id": "1947"}], "options": ["1984", "1947", "1982", "1985"], "target_options": "1947", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1210_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1211", "question": "When did Clarence Campbell stop participating in Nuremberg trials the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1981", "1946", "1987", "1986"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1211_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1212", "question": "When did Eberhard Godt stop participating in Nuremberg trials the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1947", "id": "1947"}], "options": ["1989", "1947", "1997", "1999"], "target_options": "1947", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1212_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1213", "question": "When did Vladimir Putin start participating in Second Chechen War the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1987", "1989", "1990", "1999"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1213_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1214", "question": "When did Holger Rune start participating in Davis Cup the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2015", "2018", "2007", "2014"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1214_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1215", "question": "When did Arthur Rinderknech start participating in Davis Cup the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2021", "id": "2021"}], "options": ["2021", "2013", "2011", "2001"], "target_options": "2021", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1215_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1216", "question": "When did George Russell start participating in Formula Renault the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2016", "2011", "2014", "2002"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1216_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1217", "question": "When did Eirik Kristoffersen start participating in United Nations Interim Force in Lebanon the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1991", "1985", "1988", "1990"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1217_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1218", "question": "When did Maria Sole Ferrieri Caputi start participating in Coppa Italia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2007", "1998", "2006", "2010"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1218_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1219", "question": "When did XIV Corps stop being commanded by Friedrich von Gontard the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1919", "id": "1919"}], "options": ["1916", "1922", "1919", "1921"], "target_options": "1919", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1219_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1220", "question": "When did Mediterranean Division stop being commanded by Wilhelm Souchon the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1914", "id": "1914"}], "options": ["1914", "1906", "1919", "1916"], "target_options": "1914", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1220_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1221", "question": "When did Admiral Scheer start being commanded by Wilhelm Marschall the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1934", "id": "1934"}], "options": ["1910", "1906", "1909", "1934"], "target_options": "1934", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1221_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1222", "question": "When did Guards Cavalry Division stop being commanded by Heinrich Hofmann the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1918", "id": "1918"}], "options": ["1919", "1918", "1921", "1924"], "target_options": "1918", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1222_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1223", "question": "When did Guards Cavalry Division stop being commanded by Heinrich Hofmann the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1918", "id": "1918"}], "options": ["1917", "1921", "1918", "1923"], "target_options": "1918", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1223_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1224", "question": "When did Admiral Scheer start being commanded by Wilhelm Marschall the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1934", "id": "1934"}], "options": ["1932", "1934", "1931", "1921"], "target_options": "1934", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1224_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1225", "question": "When did German battleship Scharnhorst start being commanded by Kurt-Caesar Hoffmann the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1939", "id": "1939"}], "options": ["1937", "1939", "1925", "1935"], "target_options": "1939", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1225_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1226", "question": "When did Warsaw Pact stop being commanded by Pyotr Lushev the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1993", "1996", "1987", "1991"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1226_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1227", "question": "When did Jeroen van der Veer become the chief executive officer of Shell the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["1997", "2005", "2007", "2003"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1227_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1228", "question": "When did Hermann M√ºnch become the chief executive officer of Volkswagen Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1946", "1937", "1944", "1943"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1228_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1229", "question": "When did Ted Halstead become the chief executive officer of New America the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1985", "1992", "1989", "1999"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1229_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1230", "question": "When did Marco Tronchetti Provera become the chief executive officer of Pirelli the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1977", "1984", "1986", "1987"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1230_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1231", "question": "When did Franz Fehrenbach become the chief executive officer of Robert Bosch the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2000", "2003", "1998", "2002"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1231_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1232", "question": "When did Nicolas Hayek become the chief executive officer of The Swatch Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1972", "1969", "1975", "1986"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1232_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1233", "question": "When did Sergio Ermotti become the chief executive officer of UBS the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2011", "2004", "2005", "2000"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1233_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1234", "question": "When did Camille Gutt become the chief executive officer of International Monetary Fund the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1941", "1936", "1946", "1938"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1234_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1235", "question": "When did Stefano Domenicali become the chief executive officer of Formula One the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2021", "id": "2021"}], "options": ["2021", "2020", "2018", "2016"], "target_options": "2021", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1235_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1236", "question": "When did Tom Buhrow become the chief executive officer of Westdeutscher Rundfunk the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2013", "2012", "2011", "2003"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1236_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1237", "question": "When did Bill Gates become the chief executive officer of Microsoft the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1963", "1964", "1962", "1975"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1237_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1238", "question": "When did Karlheinz Kaske become the chief executive officer of Siemens the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1981", "id": "1981"}], "options": ["1970", "1964", "1967", "1981"], "target_options": "1981", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1238_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1239", "question": "When did Pavel Durov become the chief executive officer of Telegram the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2004", "2010", "2012", "2013"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1239_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1240", "question": "When did Karlheinz Kaske become the chief executive officer of Siemens the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1981", "id": "1981"}], "options": ["1957", "1981", "1961", "1963"], "target_options": "1981", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1240_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1241", "question": "When did Adam Sandler become the chief executive officer of Happy Madison Productions the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1997", "1993", "2002", "1999"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1241_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1242", "question": "When did Ferdinand Pi√´ch become the chief executive officer of Audi AG the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1988", "id": "1988"}], "options": ["1990", "1988", "2001", "1998"], "target_options": "1988", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1242_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1243", "question": "When did Nicky Hilton become the chief executive officer of Hilton Worldwide the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2006", "2012", "2022", "2013"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1243_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1244", "question": "When did Nicolas Hayek become the chief executive officer of The Swatch Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1981", "1982", "1986", "1984"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1244_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1245", "question": "When did Walter Seipp become the chief executive officer of Commerzbank AG the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1981", "id": "1981"}], "options": ["1981", "1947", "1954", "1956"], "target_options": "1981", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1245_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1246", "question": "When did Ernst Fuhrmann become the chief executive officer of Porsche the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1972", "id": "1972"}], "options": ["1942", "1972", "1951", "1950"], "target_options": "1972", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1246_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1247", "question": "When did Rob Friend become the chief executive officer of Pacific FC the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2018", "2004", "2009", "2008"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1247_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1248", "question": "When did Abigail Johnson become the chief executive officer of Fidelity Investments the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2011", "2016", "2004", "2014"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1248_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1249", "question": "When did Hironobu Sakaguchi become the chief executive officer of Mistwalker the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["2005", "2004", "2002", "1997"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1249_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1250", "question": "When did Freddy Heineken become the chief executive officer of Heineken the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1971", "1967", "1958", "1968"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1250_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1251", "question": "When did Camille Gutt become the chief executive officer of International Monetary Fund the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1936", "1946", "1934", "1935"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1251_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1252", "question": "When did Sergey Kiriyenko cease the chief executive officer of Federal Agency on Atomic Energy the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2007", "2010", "2013", "2000"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1252_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1253", "question": "When did John S. Gray become the chief executive officer of Ford Motor Company the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1903", "id": "1903"}], "options": ["1889", "1892", "1882", "1903"], "target_options": "1903", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1253_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1254", "question": "When did Jeroen van der Veer become the chief executive officer of Shell the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["1998", "2005", "2000", "1995"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1254_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1255", "question": "When did Walt Disney become the chief executive officer of The Walt Disney Company the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1923", "id": "1923"}], "options": ["1915", "1923", "1905", "1918"], "target_options": "1923", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1255_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1256", "question": "When did Michael Scott become the chief executive officer of Apple the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1977", "id": "1977"}], "options": ["1972", "1977", "1968", "1971"], "target_options": "1977", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1256_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1257", "question": "When did Owen D. Young become the chief executive officer of General Electric the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1919", "id": "1919"}], "options": ["1980", "1977", "1979", "1919"], "target_options": "1919", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1257_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1258", "question": "When did Miles D. White become the chief executive officer of Abbott Laboratories the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1999", "1995", "1998", "1987"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1258_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1259", "question": "When did D. Wayne Calloway become the chief executive officer of PepsiCo the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1986", "1965", "1958", "1966"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1259_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1260", "question": "When did Jeremy Hunt become the chief executive officer of HM Treasury the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2022", "2016", "2020", "2019"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1260_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1261", "question": "When did Jeff Bezos become the chief executive officer of Amazon the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1986", "1985", "1988", "1996"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1261_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1262", "question": "When did Kristalina Georgieva become the chief executive officer of International Bank for Reconstruction and Development the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2007", "2017", "2001", "2009"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1262_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1263", "question": "When did Subway become the chief executive officer of Suzanne Greco the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2015", "2014", "2012", "2011"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1263_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1264", "question": "When did Robert Noyce become the chief executive officer of Intel the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1968", "id": "1968"}], "options": ["1947", "1949", "1968", "1946"], "target_options": "1968", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1264_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1265", "question": "When did William F. Talbot become the chief executive officer of SRI International the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1947", "id": "1947"}], "options": ["1941", "1930", "1940", "1947"], "target_options": "1947", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1265_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1266", "question": "When did William Purves become the chief executive officer of HSBC the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1986", "1979", "1975", "1980"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1266_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1267", "question": "When did Anas Farouki become the chief executive officer of TotalEnergies the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1924", "id": "1924"}], "options": ["1924", "1915", "1923", "1921"], "target_options": "1924", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1267_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1268", "question": "When did Lee Raymond become the chief executive officer of ExxonMobil the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1994", "1993", "1999", "1990"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1268_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1269", "question": "When did Meg Whitman become the chief executive officer of eBay the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1978", "1998", "1991", "1988"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1269_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1270", "question": "When did Kristalina Georgieva become the chief executive officer of International Development Association the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2003", "2013", "2017", "2012"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1270_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1271", "question": "When did Adolfo Nicol√°s become the chief executive officer of Society of Jesus the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["2002", "2008", "2006", "2005"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1271_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1272", "question": "When did Jensen Huang become the chief executive officer of Nvidia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1993", "id": "1993"}], "options": ["1993", "1986", "1973", "1983"], "target_options": "1993", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1272_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1273", "question": "When did ESPCI Paris, PSL University become the subsidiary of PSL University the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2015", "2008", "2007", "2001"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1273_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1274", "question": "When did New Line Cinema end the subsidiary of Turner Broadcasting System the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["2020", "1996", "2016", "2021"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1274_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1275", "question": "When did Peugeot-Citro√´n Argentina become the subsidiary of Groupe PSA the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1990", "1993", "1987", "1998"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1275_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1276", "question": "When did Peugeot become the subsidiary of Stellantis the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2021", "id": "2021"}], "options": ["2019", "2018", "2021", "2014"], "target_options": "2021", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1276_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1277", "question": "When did Sistema Globo de R√°dio become the subsidiary of Grupo Globo the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1944", "id": "1944"}], "options": ["1935", "1945", "1944", "1941"], "target_options": "1944", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1277_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1278", "question": "When did Jean Moulin University - Lyon 3 become the subsidiary of University of Lyon the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2004", "2010", "2009", "2015"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1278_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1279", "question": "When did Jean Moulin University - Lyon 3 become the subsidiary of University of Lyon the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2015", "2005", "2011", "2014"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1279_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1280", "question": "When did Peugeot become the subsidiary of Stellantis the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2021", "id": "2021"}], "options": ["2013", "2020", "2018", "2021"], "target_options": "2021", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1280_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1281", "question": "When did NBC end the subsidiary of RCA Corporation the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1988", "1986", "1989", "1993"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1281_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1282", "question": "When did Panavision become the subsidiary of Saban Capital Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2008", "2018", "2010", "2002"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1282_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1283", "question": "When did Bordeaux Montaigne University end the subsidiary of Community of universities and higher education institutions of Aquitaine the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2022", "2019", "2024", "2017"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1283_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1284", "question": "When did Bordeaux Montaigne University end the subsidiary of Community of universities and higher education institutions of Aquitaine the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2020", "2017", "2024", "2022"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1284_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1285", "question": "When did University of La Rochelle become the subsidiary of Leonardo da Vinci consolidated University the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2015", "2009", "2001", "2010"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1285_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1286", "question": "When did United States Air Force become the subsidiary of United States Department of the Air Force the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1947", "id": "1947"}], "options": ["1942", "1947", "1944", "1936"], "target_options": "1947", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1286_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1287", "question": "When did Chinese Communist Party end the subsidiary of Communist International the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1943", "id": "1943"}], "options": ["1936", "1945", "1943", "1946"], "target_options": "1943", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1287_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1288", "question": "When did Radio France Internationale become the subsidiary of Radio France the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1972", "1971", "1974", "1965"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1288_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1289", "question": "When did Pierce-Arrow end the subsidiary of Studebaker the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1971", "1969", "1961"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1289_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1290", "question": "When did Universal Music Group become the subsidiary of Pershing Square Holdings the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2021", "id": "2021"}], "options": ["2012", "2019", "2021", "2022"], "target_options": "2021", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1290_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1291", "question": "When did Paramount Television Studios end the subsidiary of CBS Corporation the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2006", "2017", "2021", "2019"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1291_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1292", "question": "When did ABB Oy become the subsidiary of ABB Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1988", "id": "1988"}], "options": ["1988", "1986", "1984", "1978"], "target_options": "1988", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1292_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1293", "question": "When did Land Rover become the subsidiary of Tata Motors Ltd the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["2010", "2008", "2007", "2000"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1293_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1294", "question": "When did American Airlines end the subsidiary of AMR Corporation the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2013", "2012", "2015", "2018"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1294_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1295", "question": "When did Audi AG become the subsidiary of Volkswagen Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1966", "1965", "1962", "1953"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1295_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1296", "question": "When did Audi AG become the subsidiary of Volkswagen Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1957", "1966", "1956", "1951"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1296_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1297", "question": "When did Cathay Dragon become the subsidiary of Cathay Pacific the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["2004", "2002", "2005", "2001"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1297_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1298", "question": "When did Rockstar Toronto become the subsidiary of Rockstar Games the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1999", "1995", "1998", "1992"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1298_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1299", "question": "When did Standard Life become the subsidiary of Phoenix Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2018", "2006", "2013", "2011"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1299_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1300", "question": "When did PayPal become the subsidiary of eBay the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["2002", "1998", "1992", "1995"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1300_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1301", "question": "When did International Rectifier become the subsidiary of Infineon Technologies the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2001", "2012", "2015", "2011"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1301_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1302", "question": "When did Lille University of Health and Law end the subsidiary of Lille North of France University the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2017", "2021", "2014", "2020"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1302_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1303", "question": "When did La Redoute become the subsidiary of Kering the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1992", "1973", "1974", "1972"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1303_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1304", "question": "When did Qurate Retail Group become the subsidiary of Liberty Media the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1983", "1987", "1998", "1990"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1304_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1305", "question": "When did McLaren become the subsidiary of McLaren Technology Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1963", "id": "1963"}], "options": ["1964", "1957", "1960", "1963"], "target_options": "1963", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1305_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1306", "question": "When did M√§rklin become the subsidiary of Simba Dickie Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2006", "1997", "2013", "2005"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1306_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1307", "question": "When did Cyryl Kozaczewski start serving as an ambassador in Permanent Mission of the Republic of Poland to NATO the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["2001", "2019", "2013", "2022"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1307_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1308", "question": "When did Cyryl Kozaczewski start serving as an ambassador in Permanent Mission of the Republic of Poland to NATO the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["2005", "2001", "2007", "2008"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1308_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1309", "question": "When did Seine cease to replaced by Paris the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1962", "2024", "1970", "1969"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1309_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1310", "question": "When did Horch cease to replaced by Auto Union the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1969", "id": "1969"}], "options": ["1969", "1944", "1937", "1942"], "target_options": "1969", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1310_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1311", "question": "When did Zeevang cease to replaced by Edam-Volendam the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "2020", "2016", "2017"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1311_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1312", "question": "When was Kirnitzschtal replaced by Sebnitz the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2006", "2007", "2008", "2012"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1312_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1313", "question": "When did Spanish Sahara cease to replaced by Mauritania the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1980", "1968", "1979", "1978"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1313_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1314", "question": "When was Joutseno replaced by Lappeenranta the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["2009", "2001", "2011", "2006"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1314_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1315", "question": "When did Seine cease to replaced by Paris the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1972", "1965", "2024", "1969"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1315_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1316", "question": "When was Landeszentralbank replaced by Deutsche Bundesbank the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["1999", "1997", "2002", "1998"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1316_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1317", "question": "When did Horch cease to replaced by Auto Union the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1969", "id": "1969"}], "options": ["1969", "1932", "1944", "1942"], "target_options": "1969", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1317_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1318", "question": "When did Perreuse cease to replaced by Treigny the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2018", "1969", "1975", "1974"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1318_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1319", "question": "When was Entertainment and Leisure Software Publishers Association replaced by Pan European Game Information the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["1995", "1997", "1998", "2003"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1319_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1320", "question": "When was Waterloo International railway station replaced by St Pancras railway station the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2000", "1992", "2007", "2003"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1320_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1321", "question": "When did Soviet Olympic Committee cease to replaced by Estonian Olympic Committee the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1986", "1995", "2024", "1994"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1321_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1322", "question": "When was Rijksmuseum van Natuurlijke Historie replaced by Naturalis Biodiversity Center the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1996", "1991", "1998", "1993"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1322_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1323", "question": "When did University of Library and Information Science cease to replaced by University of Tsukuba the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2006", "2024", "2008", "2004"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1323_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1324", "question": "When did Bagneux cease to replaced by Argenton-l'√âglise the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["1972", "1974", "2018", "1976"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1324_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1325", "question": "When was Shirokiya replaced by Tokyu Department Store the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1949", "1967", "1960", "1957"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1325_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1326", "question": "When was Eisenhower dollar replaced by Susan B. Anthony dollar the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1973", "1979", "1965", "1976"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1326_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1327", "question": "When did Soviet Olympic Committee cease to replaced by Estonian Olympic Committee the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1996", "1986", "1994"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1327_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1328", "question": "When did USC Gould School of Law start its affiliation with University of Southern California the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1900", "id": "1900"}], "options": ["1898", "1897", "1896", "1900"], "target_options": "1900", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1328_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1329", "question": "When did Pedro Szekely start its affiliation with Information Sciences Institute the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1988", "id": "1988"}], "options": ["1977", "1988", "1979", "1982"], "target_options": "1988", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1329_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1330", "question": "When did Wikimedia France start its affiliation with Wikimedia Foundation the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["1995", "2004", "2007", "2008"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1330_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1331", "question": "When did Tokuro Fujiwara start its affiliation with Konami the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1970", "1982", "1980", "1978"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1331_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1332", "question": "When did Tokuro Fujiwara start its affiliation with Konami the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1973", "1966", "1975", "1982"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1332_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1333", "question": "When did Daran Zheng start its affiliation with University of Hong Kong the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2009", "2006", "2010", "2005"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1333_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1334", "question": "When did Qun Zhang end its affiliation with University of Hong Kong the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1995", "id": "1995"}], "options": ["2003", "2002", "1995", "1997"], "target_options": "1995", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1334_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1335", "question": "When did Daran Zheng start its affiliation with University of Hong Kong the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["1991", "2010", "1985", "1988"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1335_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1336", "question": "When did Gerhard Bigalk end its affiliation with 24th U-boat Flotilla the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1940", "id": "1940"}], "options": ["1935", "1944", "1945", "1940"], "target_options": "1940", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1336_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1337", "question": "When did Ethan Vishniac start its affiliation with Princeton University the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1980", "id": "1980"}], "options": ["1971", "1980", "1964", "1973"], "target_options": "1980", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1337_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1338", "question": "When did Warsaw cease to be the capital of South Prussia the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1807", "id": "1807"}], "options": ["1806", "1807", "1812", "1809"], "target_options": "1807", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1338_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1339", "question": "When did Warsaw become the capital Poland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1795", "id": "1795"}], "options": ["1785", "1795", "1791", "1790"], "target_options": "1795", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1339_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1340", "question": "When did Ottawa cease to be the capital of Province of Canada the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1867", "id": "1867"}], "options": ["1860", "1867", "1872", "1869"], "target_options": "1867", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1340_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1341", "question": "When did Warsaw cease to be the capital of South Prussia the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1807", "id": "1807"}], "options": ["1811", "1807", "1809", "1806"], "target_options": "1807", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1341_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1342", "question": "When did City of Brussels cease to be the capital of Military Administration in Belgium and Northern France the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1944", "id": "1944"}], "options": ["1948", "1946", "1944", "1945"], "target_options": "1944", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1342_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1343", "question": "When did Turin become the capital Italy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1861", "id": "1861"}], "options": ["1938", "1937", "1861", "1927"], "target_options": "1861", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1343_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1344", "question": "When did Ottawa cease to be the capital of Province of Canada the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1867", "id": "1867"}], "options": ["1869", "1865", "1867", "1871"], "target_options": "1867", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1344_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1345", "question": "When did City of Brussels cease to be the capital of Habsburg Netherlands the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1581", "id": "1581"}], "options": ["1584", "1583", "1581", "1579"], "target_options": "1581", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1345_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1346", "question": "When did Rome cease to be the capital of Kingdom of Italy the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1941", "1946", "1949", "1948"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1346_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1347", "question": "When did Trakai cease to be the capital of Grand Duchy of Lithuania the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1323", "id": "1323"}], "options": ["1800", "1797", "1796", "1323"], "target_options": "1323", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1347_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1348", "question": "When did Berlin cease to be the capital of Province of Brandenburg the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1949", "1941", "1946", "1951"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1348_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1349", "question": "When did Bern become the capital Switzerland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1848", "id": "1848"}], "options": ["1846", "1838", "1848", "1847"], "target_options": "1848", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1349_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1350", "question": "When did New York City become the capital United States of America the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1785", "id": "1785"}], "options": ["1772", "1785", "1771", "1764"], "target_options": "1785", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1350_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1351", "question": "When did Cairo cease to be the capital of Abbasid Caliphate the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1517", "id": "1517"}], "options": ["1256", "1517", "1260", "1261"], "target_options": "1517", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1351_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1352", "question": "When did Cairo cease to be the capital of Egyptian Fatimid Caliphate the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1171", "id": "1171"}], "options": ["1167", "1175", "1171", "1173"], "target_options": "1171", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1352_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1353", "question": "When did Aachen cease to be the capital of Francia the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "843", "id": "843"}], "options": ["843", "846", "840", "845"], "target_options": "843", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1353_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1354", "question": "When did Washington, D.C. become the capital District of Columbia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1790", "id": "1790"}], "options": ["1788", "1790", "1784", "1792"], "target_options": "1790", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1354_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1355", "question": "When did Berlin cease to be the capital of Province of Brandenburg the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1944", "1951", "1946", "1949"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1355_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1356", "question": "When did Bonn become the capital Germany the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1943", "1949", "1944", "1942"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1356_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1357", "question": "When did Bonn become the capital Germany the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1935", "1949", "1927", "1932"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1357_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1358", "question": "When did New York City become the capital United States of America the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1785", "id": "1785"}], "options": ["1784", "1785", "1783", "1773"], "target_options": "1785", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1358_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1359", "question": "When did Poissy become the capital canton of Poissy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2011", "2014", "2015", "2007"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1359_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1360", "question": "When did Lyon cease to be the capital of Kingdom of the Burgundians the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "534", "id": "534"}], "options": ["539", "534", "529", "536"], "target_options": "534", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1360_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1361", "question": "When did Oslo cease to be the capital of Kalmar Union the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1523", "id": "1523"}], "options": ["1527", "1525", "1523", "1529"], "target_options": "1523", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1361_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1362", "question": "When did Rome cease to be the capital of Kingdom of Italy the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1948", "1950", "1942", "1946"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1362_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1363", "question": "When did Coimbra become the capital Portugal the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1129", "id": "1129"}], "options": ["1385", "1383", "1382", "1129"], "target_options": "1129", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1363_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1364", "question": "When did Turin become the capital Italy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1861", "id": "1861"}], "options": ["1856", "1848", "1858", "1861"], "target_options": "1861", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1364_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1365", "question": "When did Scoot start being operated by Boeing 777 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2011", "2012", "2008", "2007"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1365_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1366", "question": "When did Japan Airlines start being operated by Boeing 767 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1985", "id": "1985"}], "options": ["1985", "1975", "1978", "1980"], "target_options": "1985", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1366_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1367", "question": "When did Japan Airlines start being operated by Boeing 767 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1985", "id": "1985"}], "options": ["1981", "1973", "1980", "1985"], "target_options": "1985", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1367_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1368", "question": "When did Swiss Global Air Lines stop being operated by Embraer ERJ 145 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2015", "2007", "2017", "2020"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1368_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1369", "question": "When did All Nippon Airways start being operated by Boeing 767 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1983", "id": "1983"}], "options": ["1908", "1983", "1911", "1898"], "target_options": "1983", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1369_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1370", "question": "When did Air Italy stop being operated by Boeing 767 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2022", "2024", "2021", "2017"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1370_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1371", "question": "When did All Nippon Airways start being operated by Boeing 767 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1983", "id": "1983"}], "options": ["1972", "1975", "1967", "1983"], "target_options": "1983", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1371_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1372", "question": "When did Scoot start being operated by Boeing 777 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["1987", "1978", "1988", "2012"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1372_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1373", "question": "When did Air Italy stop being operated by Boeing 767 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2021", "2024", "2017", "2022"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1373_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1374", "question": "When did Yemenia start being operated by Airbus A310 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1995", "1996", "1988", "1994"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1374_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1375", "question": "When did British Overseas Airways Corporation stop being operated by Boeing 707 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1974", "1975", "1976", "1979"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1375_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1376", "question": "When did German Air Force start being operated by Noratlas the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1956", "id": "1956"}], "options": ["1920", "1956", "1925", "1924"], "target_options": "1956", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1376_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1377", "question": "When did Braathens stop being operated by Boeing 737 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["2001", "2004", "2007", "2006"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1377_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1378", "question": "When did Braathens stop being operated by Boeing 737 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["2009", "2006", "2004", "1996"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1378_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1379", "question": "When did Alyemda stop being operated by Boeing 707 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["2001", "1995", "1996", "1998"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1379_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1380", "question": "When did Meta Platforms start being operated by Facebook the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["2006", "2004", "2003", "1994"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1380_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1381", "question": "When did Kalstar Aviation stop being operated by ATR 42 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2011", "2019", "2024", "2020"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1381_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1382", "question": "When did Japan Air Commuter start being operated by Saab 340 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1986", "1984", "1994", "1977"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1382_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1383", "question": "When did Japan Air Commuter start being operated by Saab 340 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1994", "1989", "1991", "1979"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1383_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1384", "question": "When did Hokkaido Air System start being operated by Saab 340 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1998", "1993", "1991", "1990"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1384_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1385", "question": "When did East Japan Railway Company start being operated by Hachik≈ç Line the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1987", "id": "1987"}], "options": ["1969", "1977", "1979", "1987"], "target_options": "1987", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1385_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1386", "question": "When did British Overseas Airways Corporation stop being operated by Boeing 707 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1974", "1976", "1970", "1977"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1386_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1387", "question": "When did Germania stop being operated by Fokker 100 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["2020", "2016", "2008", "2021"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1387_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1388", "question": "When did East Japan Railway Company start being operated by Hachik≈ç Line the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1987", "id": "1987"}], "options": ["1984", "1987", "1982", "1981"], "target_options": "1987", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1388_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1389", "question": "When did Austrian Airlines start being operated by Airbus A321-111 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1995", "id": "1995"}], "options": ["1995", "1963", "1951", "1961"], "target_options": "1995", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1389_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1390", "question": "When did Jim Watkins start being operated by 2channel the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2010", "2006", "2009", "2014"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1390_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1391", "question": "When did German Air Force start being operated by Noratlas the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1956", "id": "1956"}], "options": ["1956", "1952", "1941", "1949"], "target_options": "1956", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1391_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1392", "question": "When did Central Japan Railway Company start being operated by Gotemba Line the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1987", "id": "1987"}], "options": ["1985", "1987", "1980", "1989"], "target_options": "1987", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1392_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1393", "question": "When did Swiss International Air Lines start being operated by Airbus A330 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["1996", "2002", "1997", "1998"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1393_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1394", "question": "When did Finnair start being operated by F.13 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1924", "id": "1924"}], "options": ["1922", "1919", "1925", "1924"], "target_options": "1924", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1394_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1395", "question": "When did Cornell University Library start being operated by arXiv the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["1987", "1998", "1996", "2001"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1395_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1396", "question": "When did Rostec owned by Kamaz the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2008", "2016", "2017", "2015"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1396_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1397", "question": "When did Seoul Metropolitan Government owned by Seoul Metro Corporation the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1981", "id": "1981"}], "options": ["1979", "1977", "1981", "1978"], "target_options": "1981", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1397_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1398", "question": "When did Josh Harris owned by Philadelphia 76ers the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["1988", "2011", "1991", "1979"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1398_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1399", "question": "When did Mike Ashley owned by Newcastle United F.C. the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2007", "2000", "1996", "1998"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1399_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1400", "question": "When did Westinghouse Electric Corporation stop owned by CBS the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1994", "2024", "2001", "2004"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1400_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1401", "question": "When did Ronald Wayne owned by Apple the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1976", "id": "1976"}], "options": ["1976", "1977", "1968", "1975"], "target_options": "1976", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1401_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1402", "question": "When did Bernard Tapie owned by La Vie Claire the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1980", "id": "1980"}], "options": ["1973", "1970", "1980", "1966"], "target_options": "1980", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1402_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1403", "question": "When did Elon Musk owned by X the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2019", "2022", "2018", "2015"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1403_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1404", "question": "When did Josh Harris owned by Philadelphia 76ers the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2011", "2008", "2006", "2000"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1404_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1405", "question": "When did Bernard Tapie owned by La Vie Claire the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1980", "id": "1980"}], "options": ["1966", "1967", "1980", "1965"], "target_options": "1980", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1405_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1406", "question": "When did LVMH owned by Connaissance des arts the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1952", "id": "1952"}], "options": ["1945", "1952", "1937", "1944"], "target_options": "1952", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1406_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1407", "question": "When did General Electric owned by Tungsram the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1983", "1989", "1979", "1986"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1407_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1408", "question": "When did Michael Kors owned by Versace the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2013", "2010", "2001", "2018"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1408_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1409", "question": "When did Otto von Bismarck stop owned by Warcino the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1900", "2024", "1899", "1903"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1409_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1410", "question": "When did CoStar Group owned by LoopNet the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["1958", "1967", "1965", "2012"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1410_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1411", "question": "When did Ford Motor Company owned by Lincoln Motor Company the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1922", "id": "1922"}], "options": ["1915", "1908", "1922", "1917"], "target_options": "1922", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1411_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1412", "question": "When did United Artists Corporation stop owned by Pioneer Corporation the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["2020", "2000", "2021", "2016"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1412_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1413", "question": "When did Exor owned by The Economist Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2015", "2008", "1998", "2010"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1413_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1414", "question": "When did Francisco Franco become the president of Spain the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1936", "id": "1936"}], "options": ["1921", "1930", "1936", "1928"], "target_options": "1936", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1414_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1415", "question": "When did Boles≈Çaw I the Brave stop the president of Civitas Schinesghe the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1025", "id": "1025"}], "options": ["1017", "1027", "1029", "1025"], "target_options": "1025", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1415_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1416", "question": "When did Elizabeth II become the president of Saint Lucia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1975", "1971", "1973", "1979"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1416_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1417", "question": "When did Wojciech Jaruzelski become the president of Poland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1982", "1992", "1989", "1987"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1417_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1418", "question": "When did Sukarno become the president of Indonesia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1930", "1945", "1939", "1938"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1418_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1419", "question": "When did Wojciech Jaruzelski become the president of Poland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1977", "1989", "1981", "1982"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1419_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1420", "question": "When did Syngman Rhee become the president of South Korea the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1948", "id": "1948"}], "options": ["1945", "1947", "1952", "1948"], "target_options": "1948", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1420_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1421", "question": "When did Zviad Gamsakhurdia become the president of Georgia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1985", "1983", "1980", "1991"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1421_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1422", "question": "When did Mustafa Kemal Atat√ºrk become the president of Turkey the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1923", "id": "1923"}], "options": ["1903", "1914", "1912", "1923"], "target_options": "1923", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1422_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1423", "question": "When did John Dramani Mahama become the president of Ghana the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2010", "2000", "2012", "2013"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1423_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1424", "question": "When did Elizabeth II become the president of New Zealand the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1952", "id": "1952"}], "options": ["1952", "1929", "1937", "1934"], "target_options": "1952", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1424_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1425", "question": "When did Elizabeth II become the president of Tuvalu the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1978", "id": "1978"}], "options": ["1963", "1960", "1964", "1978"], "target_options": "1978", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1425_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1426", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of Jersey the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2021", "2019", "2022", "2012"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1426_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1427", "question": "When did Fernando Collor de Mello become the president of Brazil the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1990", "1958", "1955", "1946"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1427_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1428", "question": "When did Bashar al-Assad become the president of Syria the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["1991", "2000", "1999", "1996"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1428_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1429", "question": "When did Zviad Gamsakhurdia become the president of Georgia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1976", "1971", "1991", "1973"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1429_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1430", "question": "When did Alexandru Ioan Cuza become the president of Romania the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1862", "id": "1862"}], "options": ["1831", "1862", "1841", "1838"], "target_options": "1862", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1430_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1431", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of Solomon Islands the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2013", "2022", "2016", "2018"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1431_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1432", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of Saint Vincent and the Grenadines the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2020", "2018", "2022", "2016"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1432_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1433", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of Saint Kitts and Nevis the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2022", "2012", "2015", "2004"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1433_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1434", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of Papua New Guinea the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2022", "2011", "2013", "2012"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1434_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1435", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of Antigua and Barbuda the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2022", "2019", "2007", "2016"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1435_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1436", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of Nova Scotia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2017", "2020", "2022", "2016"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1436_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1437", "question": "When did Kim Il-sung become the president of North Korea the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1948", "id": "1948"}], "options": ["1940", "1944", "1947", "1948"], "target_options": "1948", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1437_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1438", "question": "When did Charles XIV John of Sweden become the president of Sweden the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1818", "id": "1818"}], "options": ["1818", "1813", "1816", "1817"], "target_options": "1818", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1438_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1439", "question": "When did Rajendra Prasad become the president of India the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1950", "id": "1950"}], "options": ["1950", "1914", "1911", "1903"], "target_options": "1950", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1439_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1440", "question": "When did Franjo Tuƒëman become the president of Croatia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1976", "1979", "1978", "1990"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1440_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1441", "question": "When did Charles XIV John of Sweden become the president of Sweden the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1818", "id": "1818"}], "options": ["1793", "1818", "1798", "1801"], "target_options": "1818", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1441_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1442", "question": "When did Mustafa Kemal Atat√ºrk become the president of Turkey the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1923", "id": "1923"}], "options": ["1906", "1923", "1901", "1907"], "target_options": "1923", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1442_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1443", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of Jamaica the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2018", "2022", "2017", "2011"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1443_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1444", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of The Bahamas the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2013", "2014", "2005", "2022"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1444_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1445", "question": "When did Amangkurat IV of Mataram stop the president of Mataram Sultanate the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1726", "id": "1726"}], "options": ["1751", "1757", "1760", "1726"], "target_options": "1726", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1445_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1446", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of Belize the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2022", "2015", "2017", "2020"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1446_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1447", "question": "When did Bill McKell become the president of Australia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1947", "id": "1947"}], "options": ["1949", "1946", "1947", "1940"], "target_options": "1947", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1447_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1448", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of Saskatchewan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2013", "2022", "2002", "2012"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1448_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1449", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of Grenada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2014", "2022", "2015", "2006"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1449_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1450", "question": "When did Elizabeth II become the president of Gibraltar the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1952", "id": "1952"}], "options": ["1952", "1950", "1951", "1945"], "target_options": "1952", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1450_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1451", "question": "When did Boles≈Çaw I the Brave stop the president of Civitas Schinesghe the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1025", "id": "1025"}], "options": ["1027", "1025", "1030", "1017"], "target_options": "1025", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1451_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1452", "question": "When did Alexandru Ioan Cuza become the president of Romania the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1862", "id": "1862"}], "options": ["1862", "1854", "1860", "1861"], "target_options": "1862", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1452_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1453", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of Isle of Man the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2012", "2015", "2022", "2013"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1453_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1454", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of Falkland Islands the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2022", "2021", "2019", "2018"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1454_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1455", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of England the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2015", "2022", "2019", "2021"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1455_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1456", "question": "When did Pius XI become the president of Vatican City the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1929", "id": "1929"}], "options": ["1924", "1929", "1920", "1925"], "target_options": "1929", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1456_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1457", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of Bailiwick of Guernsey the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2012", "2019", "2022", "2021"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1457_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1458", "question": "When did Mikhail Gorbachev stop the president of Soviet Union the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1991", "1993", "1997", "1995"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1458_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1459", "question": "When did Otto I the Great stop the president of East Francia the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "962", "id": "962"}], "options": ["964", "967", "962", "955"], "target_options": "962", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1459_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1460", "question": "When did Elizabeth II become the president of Cook Islands the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1952", "id": "1952"}], "options": ["1939", "1952", "1933", "1942"], "target_options": "1952", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1460_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1461", "question": "When did Ruhollah Khomeini become the president of Iran the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1971", "1979", "1972", "1964"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1461_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1462", "question": "When did Petar Mladenov become the president of Bulgaria the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1972", "1990", "1962", "1973"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1462_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1463", "question": "When did Kim Il-sung become the president of North Korea the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1948", "id": "1948"}], "options": ["1938", "1948", "1939", "1937"], "target_options": "1948", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1463_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1464", "question": "When did Charles III of the United Kingdom become the president of Niue the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2015", "2022", "2013", "2017"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1464_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1465", "question": "When did Edward VII become the president of Alberta the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1905", "id": "1905"}], "options": ["1891", "1905", "1899", "1902"], "target_options": "1905", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1465_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1466", "question": "When did Ra√∫l Castro become the president of Cuba the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["2008", "2004", "1994", "2001"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1466_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1467", "question": "When did Paul von Hindenburg stop the president of Weimar Republic the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1934", "id": "1934"}], "options": ["1938", "1926", "1934", "1935"], "target_options": "1934", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1467_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1468", "question": "When did Theodor Heuss become the president of Germany the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1946", "1938", "1947", "1949"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1468_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1469", "question": "When did Emilio Aguinaldo become the president of Philippines the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1899", "id": "1899"}], "options": ["1928", "1899", "1926", "1929"], "target_options": "1899", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1469_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1470", "question": "When did Enrico de Nicola become the president of Italy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1930", "1939", "1937", "1946"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1470_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1471", "question": "When did Theodor Heuss become the president of Germany the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1938", "1949", "1941", "1942"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1471_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1472", "question": "When did Michael Hainisch become the president of Austria the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1920", "id": "1920"}], "options": ["1904", "1920", "1911", "1914"], "target_options": "1920", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1472_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1473", "question": "When did Vincent Auriol become the president of France the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1947", "id": "1947"}], "options": ["1941", "1947", "1949", "1945"], "target_options": "1947", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1473_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1474", "question": "When did Patricio Aylwin become the president of Chile the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1975", "1990", "1963", "1973"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1474_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1475", "question": "When did Emilio Aguinaldo become the president of Philippines the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1899", "id": "1899"}], "options": ["1899", "1931", "1933", "1935"], "target_options": "1899", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1475_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1476", "question": "When did Augusto Pinochet stop the president of Military dictatorship of Chile the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1990", "1988", "1992", "1994"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1476_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1477", "question": "When did Vincent Auriol become the president of France the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1947", "id": "1947"}], "options": ["1947", "1924", "1919", "1921"], "target_options": "1947", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1477_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1478", "question": "When did Patricio Aylwin become the president of Chile the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1992", "1989", "1990", "1987"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1478_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1479", "question": "When did monarch stop the president of Kingdom of Bosnia the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1465", "2024", "1464", "1467"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1479_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1480", "question": "When did Pius XI become the president of Vatican City the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1929", "id": "1929"}], "options": ["1917", "1920", "1909", "1929"], "target_options": "1929", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1480_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1481", "question": "When did Enrico de Nicola become the president of Italy the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1924", "1935", "1934", "1946"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1481_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1482", "question": "When did Toghon Tem√ºr stop the president of Mongol Empire the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1368", "id": "1368"}], "options": ["1370", "1372", "1364", "1368"], "target_options": "1368", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1482_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1483", "question": "When did Wilhelm II stop the president of German Empire the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1918", "id": "1918"}], "options": ["1918", "1923", "1920", "1916"], "target_options": "1918", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1483_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1484", "question": "When did Napoleon stop the president of First French Empire the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1815", "id": "1815"}], "options": ["1816", "1819", "1815", "1820"], "target_options": "1815", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1484_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1485", "question": "When did Nokia become the parent organization of Qt Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["2006", "2008", "2007", "2001"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1485_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1486", "question": "When did AT&T become the parent organization of Bell Labs the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1925", "id": "1925"}], "options": ["1909", "1910", "1905", "1925"], "target_options": "1925", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1486_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1487", "question": "When did Boeing become the parent organization of Jeppesen the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["1991", "2000", "1994", "1988"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1487_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1488", "question": "When did Boeing cease to be the parent organization the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["2005", "2007", "2010", "2003"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1488_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1489", "question": "When did Google become the parent organization of DoubleClick the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["1997", "2007", "2008", "2004"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1489_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1490", "question": "When did Google become the parent organization of Fitbit the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2021", "id": "2021"}], "options": ["2014", "2007", "2016", "2021"], "target_options": "2021", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1490_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1491", "question": "When did Google become the parent organization of Google DeepMind the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2008", "1999", "2010", "2014"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1491_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1492", "question": "When did Google become the parent organization of Motorola Mobility the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2008", "2001", "2012", "2006"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1492_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1493", "question": "When did Google become the parent organization of Niantic the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2010", "2005", "2012", "2007"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1493_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1494", "question": "When did McDonnell Douglas become the parent organization of MD Helicopters the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1984", "id": "1984"}], "options": ["1963", "1956", "1962", "1984"], "target_options": "1984", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1494_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1495", "question": "When did Google become the parent organization of Boston Dynamics the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2007", "2008", "2013", "2001"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1495_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1496", "question": "When did Intel become the parent organization of Mobileye the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2009", "2004", "2011", "2017"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1496_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1497", "question": "When did Meta Platforms become the parent organization of Reality Labs the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2005", "2006", "2000", "2014"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1497_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1498", "question": "When did Intel become the parent organization of Wind River Systems the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["1997", "2008", "2007", "2009"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1498_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1499", "question": "When did Meta Platforms become the parent organization of Mapillary AB the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2020", "id": "2020"}], "options": ["2007", "2019", "2020", "2017"], "target_options": "2020", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1499_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1500", "question": "When did Fandom become the parent organization of Gamepedia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2017", "2008", "2014", "2018"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1500_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1501", "question": "When did Electronic Arts cease to be the parent organization the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2020", "2015", "2016", "2013"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1501_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1502", "question": "When did University of Lyon become the parent organization of Jean Monnet University the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2007", "1988", "1994", "1995"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1502_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1503", "question": "When did Nazi Party cease to be the parent organization the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1950", "1943", "2024", "1947"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1503_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1504", "question": "When did United Technologies Corporation become the parent organization of Sikorsky Aircraft Corporation the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1929", "id": "1929"}], "options": ["1881", "1876", "1883", "1929"], "target_options": "1929", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1504_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1505", "question": "When did Starbucks become the parent organization of Tazo the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1994", "1999", "1989", "1995"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1505_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1506", "question": "When did Northeastern University become the parent organization of Mills College at Northeastern the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2014", "2017", "2022", "2005"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1506_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1507", "question": "When did IBM cease to be the parent organization the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1948", "1954", "1951"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1507_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1508", "question": "When did DreamWorks cease to be the parent organization the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2006", "2008", "2003", "2001"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1508_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1509", "question": "When did IBM become the parent organization of Red Hat the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2019", "2014", "2008", "2015"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1509_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1510", "question": "When did Japan Okinawa Development Agency become the parent organization of Okinawa General Bureau the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1972", "id": "1972"}], "options": ["1960", "1964", "1972", "1967"], "target_options": "1972", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1510_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1511", "question": "When did Renault S.A. become the parent organization of Dacia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1999", "1995", "1996", "1993"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1511_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1512", "question": "When did Renault S.A. cease to be the parent organization the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1980", "2024", "1973", "1981"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1512_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1513", "question": "When did Prime Minister's Office become the parent organization of Imperial Household Agency the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1948", "1947", "1949", "1945"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1513_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1514", "question": "When did PPG Industries become the parent organization of Glidden the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2016", "2012", "2002", "2013"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1514_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1515", "question": "When did Sofirad become the parent organization of Monte Carlo Doualiya the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1972", "id": "1972"}], "options": ["1972", "1949", "1962", "1959"], "target_options": "1972", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1515_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1516", "question": "When did Samsung Electronics become the parent organization of Harman International Industries the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2015", "2017", "2018", "2013"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1516_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1517", "question": "When did United States Department of Transportation become the parent organization of Transportation Security Administration the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["1990", "2001", "1999", "1998"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1517_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1518", "question": "When did United States Department of Defense cease to be the parent organization the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1962", "id": "1962"}], "options": ["1965", "1962", "1955", "1964"], "target_options": "1962", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1518_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1519", "question": "When did United States Department of the Treasury become the parent organization of Federal Law Enforcement Training Center the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1970", "id": "1970"}], "options": ["1970", "1961", "1958", "1949"], "target_options": "1970", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1519_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1520", "question": "When did Sony Interactive Entertainment become the parent organization of Bungie the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2022", "2019", "2020", "2009"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1520_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1521", "question": "When did Major League Soccer become the parent organization of FC Cincinnati the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2008", "2019", "2015", "2014"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1521_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1522", "question": "When did AT&T become the parent organization of Indiana Bell the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1920", "id": "1920"}], "options": ["1912", "1920", "1911", "1907"], "target_options": "1920", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1522_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1523", "question": "When did Design Museum use for school the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1895", "id": "1895"}], "options": ["1898", "1884", "1895", "1894"], "target_options": "1895", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1523_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1524", "question": "When did Hospital train use for World War I the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1914", "id": "1914"}], "options": ["1911", "1912", "1903", "1914"], "target_options": "1914", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1524_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1525", "question": "When did Rimnersvallen use for athletics the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1958", "id": "1958"}], "options": ["1951", "1942", "1958", "1954"], "target_options": "1958", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1525_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1526", "question": "When did AFC Bournemouth start playing in Premier League the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2004", "2005", "1997", "2015"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1526_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1527", "question": "When did AFC Bournemouth start playing in Premier League the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2012", "2015", "2011", "2010"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1527_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1528", "question": "When did Vincent Kompany start playing in Belgian First Division A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["1979", "1987", "2003", "1988"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1528_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1529", "question": "When did Jonatan Johansson start playing in Premier League the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["2000", "1996", "1993", "1985"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1529_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1530", "question": "When did Romelu Lukaku start playing in Belgian First Division A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["1992", "1983", "1995", "2009"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1530_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1531", "question": "When did Romelu Lukaku start playing in Belgian First Division A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["1992", "2003", "2001", "2009"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1531_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1532", "question": "When did Gareth Bale start playing in Premier League the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2005", "1999", "2006", "2007"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1532_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1533", "question": "When did Erik Lamela start playing in Argentine Primera Divisi√≥n the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["2006", "2000", "2005", "2009"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1533_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1534", "question": "When did Leon Bailey start playing in Bundesliga the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2017", "2014", "2002", "2011"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1534_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1535", "question": "When did Christian Pulisic start playing in Bundesliga the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2016", "2015", "2013", "2007"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1535_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1536", "question": "When did Spezia Calcio start playing in Serie B the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2012", "2001", "2003", "1995"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1536_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1537", "question": "When did Juventus FC start playing in Serie A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1929", "id": "1929"}], "options": ["1929", "1913", "1924", "1923"], "target_options": "1929", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1537_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1538", "question": "When did Inter Milan start playing in Serie A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1929", "id": "1929"}], "options": ["1924", "1928", "1929", "1930"], "target_options": "1929", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1538_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1539", "question": "When did Udinese Calcio start playing in Serie A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1995", "id": "1995"}], "options": ["1988", "1989", "1995", "1982"], "target_options": "1995", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1539_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1540", "question": "When did Atalanta BC start playing in Serie A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["1999", "2011", "2005", "2002"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1540_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1541", "question": "When did Cagliari Calcio start playing in Serie A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2016", "2010", "2007", "2006"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1541_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1542", "question": "When did Torino Football Club start playing in Serie A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2010", "2007", "2004", "2012"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1542_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1543", "question": "When did Juventus FC start playing in Serie A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1929", "id": "1929"}], "options": ["1923", "1926", "1917", "1929"], "target_options": "1929", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1543_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1544", "question": "When did Dor Peretz start playing in Israeli Premier League the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2014", "1998", "1987", "1995"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1544_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1545", "question": "When did ACF Fiorentina start playing in Serie B the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["1994", "2003", "1992", "1996"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1545_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1546", "question": "When did Genoa CFC start playing in Lega Pro Prima Divisione the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["1998", "2000", "2005", "2002"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1546_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1547", "question": "When did Brescia Calcio start playing in Serie A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2009", "2013", "2012", "2019"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1547_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1548", "question": "When did AC Milan start playing in Serie A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1983", "id": "1983"}], "options": ["1966", "1973", "1983", "1974"], "target_options": "1983", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1548_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1549", "question": "When did AC Monza start playing in Serie A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2012", "2022", "2019", "2020"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1549_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1550", "question": "When did David Beckham start playing in Major League Soccer the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2003", "2000", "2007", "2002"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1550_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1551", "question": "When did Jeff Agoos start playing in Major League Soccer the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1996", "1986", "1988", "1980"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1551_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1552", "question": "When did Celtic Warriors stop playing in United Rugby Championship the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["2004", "2006", "2007", "2002"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1552_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1553", "question": "When did Oyonnax Rugby start playing in Pro D2 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["1998", "1996", "2003", "1988"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1553_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1554", "question": "When did Oyonnax Rugby start playing in Pro D2 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2001", "1999", "2003", "2000"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1554_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1555", "question": "When did ASM Clermont Auvergne start playing in Top 14 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1925", "id": "1925"}], "options": ["1916", "1923", "1922", "1925"], "target_options": "1925", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1555_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1556", "question": "When did Cobi Jones start playing in Premier League the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1983", "1994", "1986", "1978"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1556_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1557", "question": "When did Philadelphia Union start playing in Major League Soccer the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2010", "1995", "2003", "2004"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1557_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1558", "question": "When did Cobi Jones start playing in Premier League the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1994", "id": "1994"}], "options": ["1990", "1994", "1989", "1981"], "target_options": "1994", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1558_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1559", "question": "When did Cagliari Calcio start playing in Serie A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2012", "2017", "2016", "2015"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1559_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1560", "question": "When did Benevento Calcio start playing in Serie A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2020", "id": "2020"}], "options": ["2008", "2020", "2011", "2014"], "target_options": "2020", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1560_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1561", "question": "When did Tajon Buchanan start playing in Belgian First Division A the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2022", "2018", "2017", "2016"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1561_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1562", "question": "When did Erik Lamela start playing in Argentine Primera Divisi√≥n the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["2004", "2009", "2007", "1995"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1562_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1563", "question": "When did Cristiano Ronaldo start playing in Liga Portugal the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["2001", "1981", "1984", "1972"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1563_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1564", "question": "When did Elif Elmas start playing in First Macedonian Football League the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2014", "2017", "2015", "2007"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1564_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1565", "question": "When did Genoa CFC start playing in Lega Pro Prima Divisione the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["2005", "2002", "2003", "1993"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1565_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1566", "question": "When did Olympique Lyonnais start using the home venue in Stade de Gerland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1950", "id": "1950"}], "options": ["1951", "1946", "1949", "1950"], "target_options": "1950", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1566_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1567", "question": "When did France national association football team start using the home venue in Stade de France the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1997", "1994", "1995", "1998"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1567_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1568", "question": "When did Heracles Almelo start using the home venue in Erve Asito the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1999", "1898", "1897", "1890"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1568_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1569", "question": "When did France national rugby union team start using the home venue in Yves du Manoir Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1908", "id": "1908"}], "options": ["1876", "1908", "1881", "1884"], "target_options": "1908", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1569_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1570", "question": "When did Olympique Lyonnais start using the home venue in Stade de Gerland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1950", "id": "1950"}], "options": ["1923", "1913", "1921", "1950"], "target_options": "1950", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1570_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1571", "question": "When did Cagliari Calcio start using the home venue in Stallaggio Meloni the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1920", "id": "1920"}], "options": ["1906", "1920", "1899", "1903"], "target_options": "1920", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1571_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1572", "question": "When did AFC Wimbledon start using the home venue in Kingsmeadow the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2002", "id": "2002"}], "options": ["1991", "1987", "1992", "2002"], "target_options": "2002", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1572_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1573", "question": "When did Jokerit start using the home venue in Hartwall Arena the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1994", "1998", "1991", "1997"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1573_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1574", "question": "When did Ermis Aradippou FC start using the home venue in Aradippou Municipal Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1958", "id": "1958"}], "options": ["1958", "1946", "1957", "1956"], "target_options": "1958", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1574_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1575", "question": "When did Nea Salamis Famagusta FC start using the home venue in Famagusta Municipal Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1952", "id": "1952"}], "options": ["1951", "1945", "1952", "1950"], "target_options": "1952", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1575_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1576", "question": "When did Nea Salamis Famagusta FC start using the home venue in Famagusta Municipal Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1952", "id": "1952"}], "options": ["1952", "1937", "1939", "1935"], "target_options": "1952", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1576_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1577", "question": "When did Anorthosis Famagusta FC start using the home venue in GSE Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1934", "id": "1934"}], "options": ["1934", "1927", "1929", "1920"], "target_options": "1934", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1577_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1578", "question": "When did Golden State Warriors start using the home venue in Philadelphia Arena the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1942", "1946", "1940", "1935"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1578_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1579", "question": "When did Washington Mystics start using the home venue in Capital One Arena the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1980", "1988", "1998", "1991"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1579_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1580", "question": "When did FC Girondins de Bordeaux start using the home venue in Stade Chaban-Delmas the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1938", "id": "1938"}], "options": ["1929", "1927", "1938", "1924"], "target_options": "1938", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1580_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1581", "question": "When did Washington Wizards start using the home venue in International Amphitheatre the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1961", "id": "1961"}], "options": ["1962", "1959", "1961", "1955"], "target_options": "1961", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1581_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1582", "question": "When did ADO Den Haag start using the home venue in Zuiderpark Stadion the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1925", "id": "1925"}], "options": ["1918", "1917", "1925", "1915"], "target_options": "1925", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1582_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1583", "question": "When did Los Angeles Rams start using the home venue in Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1941", "1946", "1931", "1943"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1583_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1584", "question": "When did Vancouver Canucks start using the home venue in Pacific Coliseum the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1970", "id": "1970"}], "options": ["1927", "1935", "1932", "1970"], "target_options": "1970", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1584_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1585", "question": "When did Vancouver Grizzlies stop using the home venue in Rogers Arena the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["2005", "2003", "1997", "2001"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1585_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1586", "question": "When did Washington Nationals start using the home venue in Jarry Park Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1969", "id": "1969"}], "options": ["1950", "1959", "1969", "1956"], "target_options": "1969", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1586_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1587", "question": "When did Montreal Canadiens start using the home venue in Montreal Forum the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1926", "id": "1926"}], "options": ["1876", "1879", "1881", "1926"], "target_options": "1926", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1587_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1588", "question": "When did Catalans Dragons start using the home venue in Saint-Michel stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2010", "1997", "2005", "2006"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1588_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1589", "question": "When did Minnesota Timberwolves start using the home venue in Hubert H. Humphrey Metrodome the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1989", "1980", "1977", "1982"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1589_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1590", "question": "When did Sporting CP start using the home venue in Est√°dio Jos√© Alvalade (1956) the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1956", "id": "1956"}], "options": ["1937", "1945", "1956", "1948"], "target_options": "1956", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1590_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1591", "question": "When did Washington Nationals start using the home venue in Jarry Park Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1969", "id": "1969"}], "options": ["1945", "1969", "1947", "1946"], "target_options": "1969", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1591_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1592", "question": "When did Montreal Expos start using the home venue in Jarry Park Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1969", "id": "1969"}], "options": ["1933", "1925", "1969", "1932"], "target_options": "1969", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1592_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1593", "question": "When did RCD Mallorca start using the home venue in Llu√≠s Sitjar stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1932", "1945", "1937", "1934"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1593_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1594", "question": "When did FC Porto start using the home venue in Est√°dio das Antas the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1952", "id": "1952"}], "options": ["1938", "1952", "1947", "1946"], "target_options": "1952", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1594_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1595", "question": "When did Barcelona Dragons stop using the home venue in Mini Estadi the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2006", "2001", "2005", "2003"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1595_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1596", "question": "When did Kansas City Chiefs start using the home venue in Municipal Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1963", "id": "1963"}], "options": ["1963", "1953", "1957", "1960"], "target_options": "1963", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1596_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1597", "question": "When did Sporting Kansas City start using the home venue in Arrowhead Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1995", "id": "1995"}], "options": ["1995", "1987", "1999", "1994"], "target_options": "1995", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1597_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1598", "question": "When did Indiana Fever start using the home venue in Gainbridge Fieldhouse the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["2000", "1998", "1988", "2002"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1598_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1599", "question": "When did Indiana Pacers start using the home venue in Indiana Farmers Coliseum the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1964", "1955", "1967", "1961"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1599_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1600", "question": "When did Indiana Fever start using the home venue in Gainbridge Fieldhouse the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["2000", "1984", "1986", "1975"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1600_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1601", "question": "When did Portland Trail Blazers start using the home venue in Veterans Memorial Coliseum the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1970", "id": "1970"}], "options": ["1967", "1970", "1959", "1964"], "target_options": "1970", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1601_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1602", "question": "When did Los Angeles Lakers start using the home venue in Minneapolis Auditorium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1947", "id": "1947"}], "options": ["1929", "1939", "1936", "1947"], "target_options": "1947", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1602_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1603", "question": "When did Chicago Bulls start using the home venue in International Amphitheatre the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1956", "1958", "1957", "1966"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1603_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1604", "question": "When did Chicago Blackhawks start using the home venue in Chicago Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1929", "id": "1929"}], "options": ["1924", "1927", "1929", "1930"], "target_options": "1929", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1604_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1605", "question": "When did Chicago White Sox start using the home venue in Guaranteed Rate Field the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1975", "1991", "1985", "1986"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1605_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1606", "question": "When did Valencia CF start using the home venue in Mestalla Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1923", "id": "1923"}], "options": ["1921", "1923", "1920", "1917"], "target_options": "1923", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1606_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1607", "question": "When did Juventus FC start using the home venue in Stadio delle Alpi the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1985", "1982", "1990", "1979"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1607_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1608", "question": "When did AFC Ajax start using the home venue in Het Houten Stadion the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1907", "id": "1907"}], "options": ["1910", "1907", "1906", "1899"], "target_options": "1907", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1608_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1609", "question": "When did Detroit Pistons start using the home venue in North Side High School Gym the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1948", "id": "1948"}], "options": ["1925", "1927", "1924", "1948"], "target_options": "1948", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1609_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1610", "question": "When did Juventus FC start using the home venue in Stadio delle Alpi the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1969", "1970", "1990", "1960"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1610_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1611", "question": "When did FC Bayern Munich start using the home venue in Olympic Stadium of Munich the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1972", "id": "1972"}], "options": ["1946", "1945", "1937", "1972"], "target_options": "1972", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1611_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1612", "question": "When did Catalans Dragons start using the home venue in Saint-Michel stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["1995", "2006", "1994", "1987"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1612_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1613", "question": "When did Edmonton Elks start using the home venue in Clarke Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1949", "id": "1949"}], "options": ["1937", "1949", "1931", "1935"], "target_options": "1949", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1613_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1614", "question": "When did Israel national football team start using the home venue in Bloomfield Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1964", "id": "1964"}], "options": ["1957", "1964", "1955", "1946"], "target_options": "1964", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1614_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1615", "question": "When did FC Bayern Munich start using the home venue in Olympic Stadium of Munich the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1972", "id": "1972"}], "options": ["1964", "1967", "1972", "1960"], "target_options": "1972", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1615_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1616", "question": "When did Erie SeaWolves start using the home venue in UPMC Park the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1995", "id": "1995"}], "options": ["1989", "1995", "1986", "1991"], "target_options": "1995", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1616_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1617", "question": "When did Orix Buffaloes start using the home venue in Hankyu Nishinomiya Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1937", "id": "1937"}], "options": ["1918", "1922", "1937", "1924"], "target_options": "1937", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1617_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1618", "question": "When did Real Madrid Baloncesto start using the home venue in Raimundo Saporta Pavilion the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1947", "1966", "1948", "1937"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1618_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1619", "question": "When did Brooklyn Nets start using the home venue in Teaneck Armory the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1951", "1940", "1950", "1967"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1619_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1620", "question": "When did Real Madrid Baloncesto start using the home venue in Raimundo Saporta Pavilion the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1966", "1950", "1955", "1958"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1620_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1621", "question": "When did San Antonio Spurs start using the home venue in Kay Bailey Hutchison Convention Center the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1952", "1953", "1947", "1967"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1621_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1622", "question": "When did AZ Alkmaar start using the home venue in Alkmaarderhout the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1948", "id": "1948"}], "options": ["1934", "1941", "1948", "1940"], "target_options": "1948", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1622_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1623", "question": "When did Chiba Lotte Marines start using the home venue in Korakuen Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1950", "id": "1950"}], "options": ["1924", "1950", "1926", "1927"], "target_options": "1950", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1623_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1624", "question": "When did Orlando Magic start using the home venue in Amway Arena the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1983", "1989", "1977", "1985"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1624_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1625", "question": "When did Orlando Magic start using the home venue in Amway Arena the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1986", "1985", "1989", "1991"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1625_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1626", "question": "When did Roda JC Kerkrade start using the home venue in Parkstad Limburg Stadion the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["1993", "2000", "1991", "1995"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1626_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1627", "question": "When did France national rugby union team start using the home venue in Yves du Manoir Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1908", "id": "1908"}], "options": ["1904", "1906", "1902", "1908"], "target_options": "1908", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1627_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1628", "question": "When did San Diego State Aztecs football start using the home venue in Balboa Stadium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1921", "id": "1921"}], "options": ["1919", "1918", "1921", "1915"], "target_options": "1921", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1628_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1629", "question": "When did Los Angeles Chargers start using the home venue in Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1960", "id": "1960"}], "options": ["1960", "1957", "1959", "1948"], "target_options": "1960", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1629_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1630", "question": "When did Golden State Warriors start using the home venue in Philadelphia Arena the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1946", "1900", "1905", "1902"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1630_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1631", "question": "When did Memphis Grizzlies start using the home venue in Pyramid Arena the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["1999", "2004", "2001", "1993"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1631_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1632", "question": "When did Nikolay Nekrasov stop publishing Sovremennik the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1866", "id": "1866"}], "options": ["1864", "1869", "1866", "1868"], "target_options": "1866", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1632_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1633", "question": "When did Sony Interactive Entertainment start publishing Crash Bandicoot the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1991", "1996", "1994", "1990"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1633_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1634", "question": "When did Socialist Unity Party of Germany start publishing Neues Deutschland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1946", "1937", "1948", "1943"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1634_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1635", "question": "When did B. G. Teubner Verlag start publishing Byzantinische Zeitschrift the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1892", "id": "1892"}], "options": ["1888", "1891", "1883", "1892"], "target_options": "1892", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1635_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1636", "question": "When did Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers start publishing IEEE Annals of the History of Computing the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1992", "id": "1992"}], "options": ["1992", "1986", "1979", "1985"], "target_options": "1992", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1636_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1637", "question": "When did Joseph Pulitzer stop publishing New York World the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1911", "id": "1911"}], "options": ["1911", "1933", "1936", "1932"], "target_options": "1911", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1637_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1638", "question": "When did Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers stop publishing IBM Journal of Research and Development the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2019", "2024", "2022", "2017"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1638_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1639", "question": "When did Infocom start publishing Zork the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1979", "id": "1979"}], "options": ["1962", "1960", "1954", "1979"], "target_options": "1979", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1639_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1640", "question": "When did Springer Science+Business Media start publishing Tumor Biology the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["1993", "2006", "2010", "2003"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1640_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1641", "question": "When did OCLC, Inc. start publishing Virtual International Authority File the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2008", "2009", "2001", "2010"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1641_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1642", "question": "When did Sony Interactive Entertainment start publishing Crash Bandicoot the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1991", "1982", "1989", "1996"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1642_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1643", "question": "When did the narrative of SimCity start at Dullsville the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1900", "id": "1900"}], "options": ["1888", "1898", "1900", "1896"], "target_options": "1900", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1643_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1644", "question": "When did the narrative of SimCity start at Dullsville the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1900", "id": "1900"}], "options": ["1888", "1885", "1900", "1883"], "target_options": "1900", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1644_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1645", "question": "When did the narrative of The Tin Drum start at Paris the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1943", "id": "1943"}], "options": ["1939", "1937", "1943", "1935"], "target_options": "1943", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1645_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1646", "question": "When did the narrative of Khovanshchina start at Moscow the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1682", "id": "1682"}], "options": ["1680", "1670", "1682", "1679"], "target_options": "1682", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1646_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1647", "question": "When did the narrative of Anne of the Island start at Nova Scotia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1883", "id": "1883"}], "options": ["1883", "1877", "1878", "1871"], "target_options": "1883", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1647_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1648", "question": "When did the narrative of Anne of Green Gables start at Prince Edward Island the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1976", "id": "1976"}], "options": ["1976", "1962", "1970", "1971"], "target_options": "1976", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1648_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1649", "question": "When did the narrative of Anne of the Island start at Nova Scotia the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1883", "id": "1883"}], "options": ["1885", "1872", "1882", "1883"], "target_options": "1883", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1649_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1650", "question": "When did the narrative of Naked Among Wolves start at Buchenwald concentration camp the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1945", "1944", "1938", "1949"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1650_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1651", "question": "When did the narrative of Robinson Crusoe start at Sal√© the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1651", "id": "1651"}], "options": ["1651", "1641", "1647", "1649"], "target_options": "1651", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1651_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1652", "question": "When did the narrative of The Tin Drum start at Paris the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1943", "id": "1943"}], "options": ["1943", "1936", "1944", "1940"], "target_options": "1943", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1652_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1653", "question": "When did Wendell Ford stop serving in Kentucky National Guard the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1962", "id": "1962"}], "options": ["2017", "2010", "1962", "2019"], "target_options": "1962", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1653_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1654", "question": "When did Alvin York stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1919", "id": "1919"}], "options": ["1968", "1919", "1964", "1966"], "target_options": "1919", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1654_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1655", "question": "When did Hal Moore stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1977", "id": "1977"}], "options": ["2022", "2019", "1977", "2016"], "target_options": "1977", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1655_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1656", "question": "When did Colonel Sanders stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1907", "id": "1907"}], "options": ["1984", "1979", "1982", "1907"], "target_options": "1907", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1656_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1657", "question": "When did Douglas MacArthur stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1951", "id": "1951"}], "options": ["1968", "1951", "1965", "1966"], "target_options": "1951", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1657_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1658", "question": "When did Frank Lautenberg stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1946", "2010", "2015", "2018"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1658_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1659", "question": "When did Norman Mineta start serving in United States Army the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1953", "id": "1953"}], "options": ["1946", "1940", "1953", "1949"], "target_options": "1953", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1659_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1660", "question": "When did David Glantz start serving in United States Army the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1963", "id": "1963"}], "options": ["1958", "1963", "1955", "1947"], "target_options": "1963", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1660_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1661", "question": "When did Ted Kennedy stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1953", "id": "1953"}], "options": ["1953", "2012", "2004", "2011"], "target_options": "1953", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1661_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1662", "question": "When did Theodore Roosevelt stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1886", "id": "1886"}], "options": ["1922", "1915", "1886", "1921"], "target_options": "1886", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1662_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1663", "question": "When did Nipsey Russell stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["2007", "2000", "1945", "2010"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1663_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1664", "question": "When did Rodney Frelinghuysen start serving in United States Army the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1969", "id": "1969"}], "options": ["1967", "1966", "1969", "1972"], "target_options": "1969", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1664_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1665", "question": "When did Greg Steube start serving in United States Army the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["2004", "1985", "1998", "1995"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1665_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1666", "question": "When did Robert Duvall start serving in United States Army the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1953", "id": "1953"}], "options": ["1953", "1948", "1949", "1952"], "target_options": "1953", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1666_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1667", "question": "When did James Joseph Dresnok stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1962", "id": "1962"}], "options": ["2018", "1962", "2014", "2020"], "target_options": "1962", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1667_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1668", "question": "When did Ronald Reagan stop serving in Air Force Reserve Command the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1953", "id": "1953"}], "options": ["2006", "1953", "2009", "2004"], "target_options": "1953", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1668_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1669", "question": "When did Adam Clymer stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1962", "id": "1962"}], "options": ["2016", "1962", "2018", "2020"], "target_options": "1962", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1669_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1670", "question": "When did William Roth stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["2006", "2005", "1999", "1946"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1670_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1671", "question": "When did Rob Simmons start serving in United States Army the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1965", "id": "1965"}], "options": ["1962", "1954", "1966", "1965"], "target_options": "1965", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1671_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1672", "question": "When did John Conyers stop serving in United States Army Reserve the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1957", "id": "1957"}], "options": ["2020", "1957", "2021", "2016"], "target_options": "1957", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1672_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1673", "question": "When did Wint Smith stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1979", "1977", "1945", "1978"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1673_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1674", "question": "When did Doug Bereuter start serving in United States Army the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1963", "id": "1963"}], "options": ["1958", "1957", "1947", "1963"], "target_options": "1963", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1674_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1675", "question": "When did Henry Wharton Conway stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1829", "1821", "1830", "2024"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1675_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1676", "question": "When did Wint Smith stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1945", "id": "1945"}], "options": ["1970", "1978", "1981", "1945"], "target_options": "1945", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1676_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1677", "question": "When did Tim Conway stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1958", "id": "1958"}], "options": ["2021", "1958", "2020", "2016"], "target_options": "1958", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1677_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1678", "question": "When did Allen West start serving in United States Army the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1980", "1982", "1977", "1978"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1678_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1679", "question": "When did Emanuel Celler stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1944", "id": "1944"}], "options": ["1983", "1986", "1979", "1944"], "target_options": "1944", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1679_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1680", "question": "When did Malcolm Forbes stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1992", "1993", "1991"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1680_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1681", "question": "When did Joe Medicine Crow stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["2018", "1946", "2008", "2020"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1681_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1682", "question": "When did Ty Carter start serving in United States Marine Corps the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1972", "1998", "1974", "1973"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1682_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1683", "question": "When did Truman Smith stop serving in United States Army the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1939", "id": "1939"}], "options": ["1973", "1969", "1939", "1972"], "target_options": "1939", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1683_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1684", "question": "When did the Hermann Dersch become the rector of Humboldt University of Berlin the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1947", "id": "1947"}], "options": ["1992", "1947", "1989", "1983"], "target_options": "1947", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1684_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1685", "question": "When did the Johannes Hoops become the rector of Heidelberg University the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1920", "id": "1920"}], "options": ["1909", "1920", "1917", "1922"], "target_options": "1920", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1685_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1686", "question": "When did the Johannes Hoops become the rector of Heidelberg University the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1920", "id": "1920"}], "options": ["1896", "1897", "1920", "1891"], "target_options": "1920", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1686_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1687", "question": "When did the conflict involving Hans Beimler with Bavarian Soviet Republic end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1919", "id": "1919"}], "options": ["1941", "1919", "1933", "1938"], "target_options": "1919", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1687_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1688", "question": "When did the conflict involving Constantin Cristescu with World War I end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1918", "id": "1918"}], "options": ["1930", "1925", "1926", "1918"], "target_options": "1918", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1688_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1689", "question": "When did the conflict involving Constantin Prezan with World War I end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1918", "id": "1918"}], "options": ["1946", "1938", "1945", "1918"], "target_options": "1918", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1689_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1690", "question": "When did the conflict involving Karl Gebhardt with World War I end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1919", "id": "1919"}], "options": ["1951", "1950", "1919", "1940"], "target_options": "1919", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1690_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1691", "question": "When did the conflict involving Aristide Razu with World War I end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1918", "id": "1918"}], "options": ["1918", "1952", "1949", "1954"], "target_options": "1918", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1691_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1692", "question": "When did the conflict involving Wilhelm Leuschner with World War I end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1918", "id": "1918"}], "options": ["1949", "1918", "1937", "1946"], "target_options": "1918", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1692_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1693", "question": "When did the terminus of Vindobona in Villach Hauptbahnhof end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2011", "2016", "2014", "2018"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1693_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1694", "question": "When did the terminus of Istanbul Express in Skopje begin the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1987", "1991", "1984", "1980"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1694_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1695", "question": "When did the terminus of Capitol Limited in Central Railroad of New Jersey Terminal end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1958", "id": "1958"}], "options": ["1974", "1958", "1973", "1971"], "target_options": "1958", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1695_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1696", "question": "When did the terminus of Vindobona in Villach Hauptbahnhof end the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2017", "2016", "2012", "2014"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1696_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1697", "question": "When did the terminus of Seibu Shinjuku Line in Kokubunji Station begin the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1894", "id": "1894"}], "options": ["1893", "1894", "1890", "1881"], "target_options": "1894", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1697_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1698", "question": "When did the terminus of Seoul Metropolitan Subway Seohae Line in Ilsan Station begin the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2009", "2018", "2024", "2017"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1698_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1699", "question": "When did the terminus of Nasuno in JR East Tokyo Station begin the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1995", "id": "1995"}], "options": ["1995", "1988", "1991", "1979"], "target_options": "1995", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1699_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1700", "question": "When did TV Globo begin broadcasting The Little Lulu Show the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["2000", "1996", "1986", "1998"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1700_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1701", "question": "When did Facebook begin broadcasting YOUniverse the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2009", "2018", "2013", "2014"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1701_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1702", "question": "When did Facebook begin broadcasting YOUniverse the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2012", "2018", "2006", "2015"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1702_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1703", "question": "When did Facebook begin broadcasting Go On Girl Star Search the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2014", "2016", "2006", "2018"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1703_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1704", "question": "When did Facebook begin broadcasting Go On Girl Star Search the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2018", "1999", "2009", "2008"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1704_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1705", "question": "When did YouTube begin broadcasting BlackBoxTV Presents the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2000", "2010", "2004", "2007"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1705_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1706", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Parenthood the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2002", "2001", "1991", "2010"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1706_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1707", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Knight Rider the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1982", "1975", "1976", "1979"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1707_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1708", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting ALF the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1973", "1980", "1986", "1977"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1708_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1709", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Fame the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1974", "1982", "1965", "1972"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1709_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1710", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Scrubs the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["2001", "1988", "1996", "1994"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1710_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1711", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Medical Investigation the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["2002", "1998", "1999", "2004"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1711_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1712", "question": "When did Nickelodeon begin broadcasting National Geographic Explorer the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1985", "id": "1985"}], "options": ["1993", "1992", "1983", "1985"], "target_options": "1985", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1712_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1713", "question": "When did MSNBC begin broadcasting Imus in the Morning the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1991", "1993", "1996", "1988"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1713_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1714", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Las Vegas the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2002", "1999", "1989", "2003"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1714_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1715", "question": "When did CBS begin broadcasting Alfred Hitchcock Presents the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1955", "id": "1955"}], "options": ["1955", "1956", "1953", "1951"], "target_options": "1955", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1715_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1716", "question": "When did CBS begin broadcasting Alfred Hitchcock Presents the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1955", "id": "1955"}], "options": ["1931", "1955", "1933", "1923"], "target_options": "1955", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1716_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1717", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Medium the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["2001", "2004", "1991", "2005"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1717_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1718", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Holocaust the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1978", "id": "1978"}], "options": ["1976", "1978", "1973", "1963"], "target_options": "1978", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1718_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1719", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting The Office the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["2008", "2005", "2003", "1999"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1719_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1720", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Deal or No Deal the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["1995", "1998", "1999", "2005"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1720_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1721", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Blindspot the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2009", "2006", "2015", "2002"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1721_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1722", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting The Player the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2010", "2003", "2012", "2015"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1722_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1723", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Best Time Ever with Neil Patrick Harris the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2015", "1995", "2006", "2005"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1723_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1724", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Late Night with Seth Meyers the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2014", "2005", "2007", "2006"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1724_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1725", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Truth Be Told the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2011", "2013", "2004", "2015"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1725_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1726", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Heroes Reborn the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2015", "2007", "2010", "2000"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1726_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1727", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting JAG the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1995", "id": "1995"}], "options": ["1983", "1988", "1986", "1995"], "target_options": "1995", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1727_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1728", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting The Phantom of the Opera the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1990", "id": "1990"}], "options": ["1980", "1982", "1990", "1976"], "target_options": "1990", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1728_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1729", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Constantine the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2008", "2001", "2014", "2005"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1729_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1730", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2006", "2014", "2013", "2016"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1730_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1731", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Silver Spoons the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1971", "1978", "1982", "1976"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1731_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1732", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Knight Rider the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["2008", "1998", "2007", "2004"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1732_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1733", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Hazel the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1961", "id": "1961"}], "options": ["1943", "1961", "1955", "1953"], "target_options": "1961", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1733_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1734", "question": "When did American Broadcasting Company begin broadcasting Taxi the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1978", "id": "1978"}], "options": ["1952", "1978", "1957", "1960"], "target_options": "1978", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1734_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1735", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Friday Night Lights the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2003", "2006", "2002", "1997"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1735_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1736", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Little House on the Prairie the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1974", "id": "1974"}], "options": ["1974", "1966", "1958", "1968"], "target_options": "1974", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1736_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1737", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting The High Chaparral the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1967", "id": "1967"}], "options": ["1968", "1964", "1958", "1967"], "target_options": "1967", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1737_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1738", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Late Night with Jimmy Fallon the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["1999", "2009", "2011", "2007"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1738_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1739", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Marco Polo the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1966", "1982", "1974", "1975"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1739_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1740", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting In the Heat of the Night the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1988", "id": "1988"}], "options": ["1983", "1980", "1975", "1988"], "target_options": "1988", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1740_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1741", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting The West Wing the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1992", "1994", "1999", "1984"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1741_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1742", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Santa Barbara the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1984", "id": "1984"}], "options": ["1986", "1975", "1984", "1983"], "target_options": "1984", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1742_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1743", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Meet the Press the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1947", "id": "1947"}], "options": ["1942", "1947", "1943", "1932"], "target_options": "1947", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1743_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1744", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Saved by the Bell the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1989", "id": "1989"}], "options": ["1987", "1989", "1992", "1977"], "target_options": "1989", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1744_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1745", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Saturday Night Live the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1975", "1968", "1965", "1959"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1745_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1746", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Ed the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2000", "id": "2000"}], "options": ["2000", "1993", "1991", "1988"], "target_options": "2000", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1746_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1747", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting V the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1984", "id": "1984"}], "options": ["1978", "1975", "1984", "1968"], "target_options": "1984", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1747_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1748", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting The Apprentice the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2004", "id": "2004"}], "options": ["1994", "2004", "1997", "1984"], "target_options": "2004", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1748_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1749", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting American Odyssey the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2009", "2007", "2015", "2010"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1749_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1750", "question": "When did MSNBC begin broadcasting Hardball with Chris Matthews the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1993", "1984", "1999", "1990"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1750_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1751", "question": "When did MSNBC begin broadcasting Morning Joe the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2008", "1999", "2004", "2007"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1751_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1752", "question": "When did American Broadcasting Company begin broadcasting All My Children the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1970", "id": "1970"}], "options": ["2012", "1970", "2013", "2009"], "target_options": "1970", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1752_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1753", "question": "When did MSNBC begin broadcasting Countdown with Keith Olbermann the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2003", "1992", "1999", "1996"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1753_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1754", "question": "When did MSNBC begin broadcasting Countdown with Keith Olbermann the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["1975", "1976", "2003", "1965"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1754_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1755", "question": "When did NBC begin broadcasting Aquarius the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2006", "2001", "2008", "2015"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1755_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1756", "question": "When did Panther Chan sign with Warner Music Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2019", "2007", "2017", "2014"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1756_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1757", "question": "When did Chris Martin sign with Fierce Panda Records the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1991", "1998", "1997", "1996"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1757_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1758", "question": "When did Alan Stivell sign with Mouez Breiz the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1959", "id": "1959"}], "options": ["1959", "1952", "1947", "1953"], "target_options": "1959", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1758_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1759", "question": "When did Mon Laferte sign with Warner Music Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["1995", "1996", "2003", "1986"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1759_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1760", "question": "When did Rip Slyme sign with File Records the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1995", "id": "1995"}], "options": ["1971", "1995", "1970", "1968"], "target_options": "1995", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1760_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1761", "question": "When did Three Days Grace sign with Jive Records the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2003", "1995", "1999", "2000"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1761_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1762", "question": "When did Mike Oldfield sign with Virgin Music the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1973", "id": "1973"}], "options": ["1961", "1959", "1960", "1973"], "target_options": "1973", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1762_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1763", "question": "When did Shiga Lin sign with Warner Music Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["1999", "2010", "2002", "2000"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1763_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1764", "question": "When did Alec Benjamin sign with Columbia Records the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2010", "2007", "2004", "2014"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1764_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1765", "question": "When did David Guetta sign with Warner Music Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2013", "id": "2013"}], "options": ["2014", "2004", "2013", "2012"], "target_options": "2013", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1765_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1766", "question": "When did Lady Gaga sign with Def Jam Recordings the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["2003", "2005", "2007", "2002"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1766_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1767", "question": "When did Chris Martin sign with Fierce Panda Records the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1998", "id": "1998"}], "options": ["1998", "1968", "1978", "1975"], "target_options": "1998", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1767_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1768", "question": "When did Miki Imai sign with For Life Music the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1986", "id": "1986"}], "options": ["1986", "1960", "1964", "1963"], "target_options": "1986", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1768_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1769", "question": "When did Lady Gaga sign with Def Jam Recordings the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["2005", "2000", "1992", "1998"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1769_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1770", "question": "When did SG Lewis sign with PMR Records the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2013", "2007", "2011", "2014"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1770_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1771", "question": "When did Kaija Koo sign with Warner Music Finland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1985", "id": "1985"}], "options": ["1972", "1974", "1971", "1985"], "target_options": "1985", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1771_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1772", "question": "When did Passpo sign with Universal Music Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["2008", "2011", "1996", "2005"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1772_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1773", "question": "When did Olavi Uusivirta sign with Universal Music Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["1999", "2003", "2004", "2000"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1773_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1774", "question": "When did Martin Garrix sign with Spinnin' Records the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["1990", "1984", "2012", "1993"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1774_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1775", "question": "When did Cecilia Cheung sign with Universal Music Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1999", "id": "1999"}], "options": ["1985", "1995", "1999", "1997"], "target_options": "1999", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1775_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1776", "question": "When did Loreen sign with Warner Music Sweden the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2011", "id": "2011"}], "options": ["1997", "1995", "2011", "2000"], "target_options": "2011", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1776_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1777", "question": "When did Kei sign with Woollim Entertainment the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2014", "2008", "2009", "2007"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1777_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1778", "question": "When did Ismael Serrano sign with PolyGram the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1997", "1994", "1991", "1986"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1778_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1779", "question": "When did Nina Nesbitt sign with Universal Music Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2004", "2012", "1994", "2006"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1779_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1780", "question": "When did Mon Laferte sign with Warner Music Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["1998", "2004", "2003", "2001"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1780_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1781", "question": "When did Lee Jaijin sign with DSP Media the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1997", "2006", "2005", "2008"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1781_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1782", "question": "When did CL sign with YG Entertainment the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["2009", "1999", "2008", "2007"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1782_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1783", "question": "When did Mura Masa sign with Universal Music Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2004", "2014", "2015", "2013"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1783_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1784", "question": "When did Lee Hi sign with YG Entertainment the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["1999", "2012", "2009", "2008"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1784_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1785", "question": "When did Annie Cordy leave Sony Group the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2022", "2018", "2014", "2020"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1785_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1786", "question": "When did John Cale sign with Columbia Records the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1970", "id": "1970"}], "options": ["1961", "1970", "1974", "1969"], "target_options": "1970", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1786_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1787", "question": "When did Selena Gomez sign with Walt Disney Records the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["1997", "2007", "2000", "2002"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1787_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1788", "question": "When did Sechs Kies sign with DSP Media the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1997", "2009", "2007", "2006"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1788_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1789", "question": "When did One sign with YG Entertainment the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2003", "2015", "2013", "2014"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1789_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1790", "question": "When did Hilary Duff sign with Walt Disney Records the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["1995", "2001", "2000", "2005"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1790_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1791", "question": "When did Jang Su Won sign with DSP Media the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["2000", "2011", "1997", "2010"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1791_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1792", "question": "When did Kim Jaeduck sign with DSP Media the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1997", "2012", "2003", "2015"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1792_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1793", "question": "When did Kang Sung Hun sign with DSP Media the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["2014", "1997", "2012", "2009"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1793_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1794", "question": "When did MC Solaar sign with Polydor Records the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1982", "1985", "1976", "1991"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1794_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1795", "question": "When did Borknagar sign with Century Media Records the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1996", "id": "1996"}], "options": ["1998", "1996", "1986", "1994"], "target_options": "1996", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1795_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1796", "question": "When did Mura Masa sign with Universal Music Group the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2014", "id": "2014"}], "options": ["2005", "2007", "2002", "2014"], "target_options": "2014", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1796_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1797", "question": "When did Bee Gees sign with Leedon the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1963", "id": "1963"}], "options": ["1938", "1937", "1963", "1928"], "target_options": "1963", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1797_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1798", "question": "When did Dadju sign with Wati B the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["1996", "1997", "1995", "2012"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1798_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1799", "question": "When did Omnium Gatherum sign with Century Media Records the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2006", "2001", "2016", "2009"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1799_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1800", "question": "When did Insomnium sign with Century Media Records the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2010", "1998", "2006", "2004"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1800_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1801", "question": "When did Madonna sign with Sire the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1982", "id": "1982"}], "options": ["1982", "1975", "1976", "1977"], "target_options": "1982", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1801_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1802", "question": "When did Maurizio Pollini sign with Deutsche Grammophon the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1965", "1971", "1969", "1967"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1802_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1803", "question": "When did Stardew Valley start using Linux the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2003", "2016", "2010", "2009"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1803_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1804", "question": "When did The Room start using iOS the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2005", "2014", "2010", "2012"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1804_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1805", "question": "When did Stardew Valley start using Linux the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2016", "id": "2016"}], "options": ["2012", "2016", "2014", "2013"], "target_options": "2016", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1805_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1806", "question": "When did Touhou Project start using NEC PC-9800 series the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1974", "1997", "1972", "1963"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1806_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1807", "question": "When did Dead Cells start using Microsoft Windows the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2013", "2011", "2001", "2017"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1807_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1808", "question": "When did Bad North start using Microsoft Windows the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2018", "id": "2018"}], "options": ["2018", "2015", "2014", "2004"], "target_options": "2018", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1808_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1809", "question": "When did Pingus start using Microsoft Windows the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2007", "2010", "2006", "1996"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1809_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1810", "question": "When did Pingus start using Microsoft Windows the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2004", "1991", "2001", "2010"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1810_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1811", "question": "When did The Room start using iOS the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2002", "2012", "2000", "2005"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1811_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1812", "question": "When did Discord start using Xbox the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2019", "2016", "2022", "2020"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1812_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1813", "question": "When did Touhou Project start using NEC PC-9800 series the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1997", "1984", "1994", "1996"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1813_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1814", "question": "When did Potlatch start using Adobe AIR the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2020", "id": "2020"}], "options": ["2018", "2011", "2020", "2017"], "target_options": "2020", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1814_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1815", "question": "When did Jurassic World Evolution start using Nintendo Switch the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2020", "id": "2020"}], "options": ["2015", "2023", "2019", "2020"], "target_options": "2020", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1815_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1816", "question": "When did Factorio start using Nintendo Switch the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2021", "2014", "2018", "2022"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1816_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1817", "question": "When did Shadowverse start using Nintendo Switch the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2021", "id": "2021"}], "options": ["2021", "2014", "2017", "2016"], "target_options": "2021", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1817_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1818", "question": "When did MicroPython start using RISC-V the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2017", "2006", "2013", "2015"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1818_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1819", "question": "When was the Hemma's the last child Carloman of Bavaria born?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["869", "880", "2024", "878"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1819_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1820", "question": "When was the Hemma's the last child Carloman of Bavaria born?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["878", "875", "2024", "879"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1820_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1821", "question": "When was the Miyamoto Musashi's the last child Miyamoto Mikinosuke born?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "1643", "1647", "1650"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1821_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1822", "question": "When was the Henry Fok's the last child Timothy Fok born?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "2009", "1998", "2008"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1822_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1823", "question": "When was the Henry Fok's the last child Timothy Fok born?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "2010", "2000", "2008"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1823_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1824", "question": "When was the Run Run Shaw's the last child Shaw Vee-Meng born?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["2024", "2015", "2016", "2018"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1824_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1825", "question": "When did Albrecht Brandi leave U-380 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1944", "id": "1944"}], "options": ["1944", "1971", "1964", "1968"], "target_options": "1944", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1825_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1826", "question": "When did Engelbert Endrass leave U-47 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1940", "id": "1940"}], "options": ["1943", "1940", "1945", "1936"], "target_options": "1940", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1826_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1827", "question": "When did Engelbert Endrass leave U-47 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1940", "id": "1940"}], "options": ["1940", "1945", "1943", "1933"], "target_options": "1940", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1827_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1828", "question": "When did Albrecht Brandi leave U-380 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1944", "id": "1944"}], "options": ["1970", "1944", "1960", "1968"], "target_options": "1944", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1828_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1829", "question": "When did Victor Oehrn leave German cruiser Karlsruhe the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1935", "id": "1935"}], "options": ["1935", "2000", "1996", "1999"], "target_options": "1935", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1829_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1830", "question": "When did Victor Oehrn leave German cruiser Karlsruhe the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1935", "id": "1935"}], "options": ["1999", "1935", "1997", "2001"], "target_options": "1935", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1830_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1831", "question": "When did Felix von Bendemann leave SMS Gazelle the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1876", "id": "1876"}], "options": ["1920", "1913", "1917", "1876"], "target_options": "1876", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1831_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1832", "question": "When did Heinrich Liebe leave SMS Schleswig-Holstein the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1934", "id": "1934"}], "options": ["2000", "1934", "1992", "1999"], "target_options": "1934", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1832_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1833", "question": "When did Albert Lauzemis leave U-68 the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1942", "id": "1942"}], "options": ["1942", "1946", "1947", "1941"], "target_options": "1942", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1833_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1834", "question": "When did Sian Proctor become a member of Inspiration4 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2021", "id": "2021"}], "options": ["2021", "2015", "2012", "2005"], "target_options": "2021", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1834_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1835", "question": "When did Camille Grammer acquire the Grammer the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1997", "id": "1997"}], "options": ["1989", "1982", "1987", "1997"], "target_options": "1997", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1835_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1836", "question": "When was Viktor Ullmann released from the place of detention in Theresienstadt Ghetto the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1944", "id": "1944"}], "options": ["1948", "1940", "1946", "1944"], "target_options": "1944", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1836_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1837", "question": "When was Al Capone released from the place of detention in Alcatraz Federal Penitentiary the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1939", "id": "1939"}], "options": ["1952", "1939", "1946", "1949"], "target_options": "1939", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1837_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1838", "question": "When was Al Capone released from the place of detention in Alcatraz Federal Penitentiary the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1939", "id": "1939"}], "options": ["1943", "1939", "1949", "1950"], "target_options": "1939", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1838_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1839", "question": "When was Donald Tsang taken to the place of detention in Stanley Prison the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2017", "2015", "2012", "2006"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1839_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1840", "question": "When was Albert Speer released from the place of detention in Spandau Prison the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2024", "id": "2024"}], "options": ["1985", "1983", "2024", "1975"], "target_options": "2024", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1840_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1841", "question": "When was Tommy Chong taken to the place of detention in Taft Correctional Institution the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["1998", "1999", "1989", "2003"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1841_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1842", "question": "When was Jefferson Davis released from the place of detention in Fort Monroe the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1867", "id": "1867"}], "options": ["1891", "1894", "1867", "1881"], "target_options": "1867", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1842_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1843", "question": "When was Sergei Magnitsky released from the place of detention in Butyrka prison the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "2009", "id": "2009"}], "options": ["2016", "2009", "2012", "2011"], "target_options": "2009", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1843_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1844", "question": "When was Viktor Frankl released from the place of detention in Theresienstadt Ghetto the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1944", "id": "1944"}], "options": ["2001", "1994", "1944", "1999"], "target_options": "1944", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1844_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1845", "question": "When was Hubert Robert released from the place of detention in Prison Saint-Lazare the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1794", "id": "1794"}], "options": ["1810", "1808", "1813", "1794"], "target_options": "1794", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1845_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1846", "question": "When was Hubert Robert released from the place of detention in Prison Saint-Lazare the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1794", "id": "1794"}], "options": ["1810", "1813", "1794", "1803"], "target_options": "1794", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1846_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1847", "question": "When was Shyne taken to the place of detention in Clinton Correctional Facility the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["1993", "2001", "1996", "1998"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1847_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1848", "question": "When was Naftaly Frenkel released from the place of detention in Solovki prison camp the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1927", "id": "1927"}], "options": ["1955", "1962", "1965", "1927"], "target_options": "1927", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1848_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1849", "question": "When was Idol charted in Japan Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2023", "id": "2023"}], "options": ["2018", "2019", "2023", "2012"], "target_options": "2023", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1849_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1850", "question": "When was Machine Head charted in UK Albums Chart the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1972", "id": "1972"}], "options": ["1956", "1968", "1965", "1972"], "target_options": "1972", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1850_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1851", "question": "When was Machine Head charted in UK Albums Chart the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1972", "id": "1972"}], "options": ["1972", "1958", "1962", "1963"], "target_options": "1972", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1851_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1852", "question": "When was Jesus Christ Superstar charted in Billboard 200 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1970", "1963", "1971", "1969"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1852_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1853", "question": "When was Imagine charted in UK Albums Chart the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1966", "1967", "1971", "1957"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1853_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1854", "question": "When was Jesus Christ Superstar charted in Billboard 200 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1962", "1967", "1971", "1966"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1854_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1855", "question": "When was Shaft charted in Billboard Best Selling Soul LP's the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1969", "1966", "1971", "1961"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1855_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1856", "question": "When was All Things Must Pass charted in RPM100 Albums the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1970", "id": "1970"}], "options": ["1970", "1966", "1959", "1963"], "target_options": "1970", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1856_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1857", "question": "When was No Time to Die charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2020", "id": "2020"}], "options": ["2020", "2013", "2010", "2012"], "target_options": "2020", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1857_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1858", "question": "When was Tapestry charted in RPM100 Albums the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1971", "1970", "1961", "1974"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1858_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1859", "question": "When was We Found Love charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2005", "1994", "2012", "2002"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1859_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1860", "question": "When was American Pie charted in Billboard 200 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1972", "id": "1972"}], "options": ["1972", "1955", "1966", "1963"], "target_options": "1972", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1860_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1861", "question": "When was Old Town Road charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2014", "2019", "2009", "2013"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1861_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1862", "question": "When was One More Night charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2009", "2012", "2010", "2011"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1862_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1863", "question": "When was Set Fire to the Rain charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2006", "2012", "2002", "2003"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1863_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1864", "question": "When was Sunflower charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2010", "2015", "2017", "2019"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1864_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1865", "question": "When was Diamonds charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["1993", "2002", "2004", "2012"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1865_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1866", "question": "When was Shallow charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2019", "2016", "2011", "2021"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1866_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1867", "question": "When was We Are Young charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2006", "2007", "2003", "2012"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1867_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1868", "question": "When was Somebody That I Used to Know charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["1999", "2002", "2012", "2005"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1868_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1869", "question": "When was Locked Out of Heaven charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2004", "2012", "2007", "1997"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1869_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1870", "question": "When was Whistle charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2012", "2007", "2014", "2009"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1870_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1871", "question": "When was No Time to Die charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2020", "id": "2020"}], "options": ["2023", "2020", "2018", "2019"], "target_options": "2020", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1871_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1872", "question": "When was Truth Hurts charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2019", "2021", "2018", "2012"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1872_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1873", "question": "When was Lose You to Love Me charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2012", "2021", "2019", "2018"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1873_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1874", "question": "When was We Are Never Ever Getting Back Together charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2012", "2010", "2011", "2007"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1874_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1875", "question": "When was Sucker charted in Billboard Hot 100 the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2018", "2016", "2019", "2020"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1875_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1876", "question": "When was Ram charted in RPM100 Albums the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1960", "1967", "1971", "1970"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1876_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1877", "question": "When was Bridge over Troubled Water charted in UK Albums Chart the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1966", "1971", "1965", "1958"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1877_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1878", "question": "When was Bridge over Troubled Water charted in UK Albums Chart the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1962", "1959", "1971", "1964"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1878_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1879", "question": "When was Imagine charted in UK Albums Chart the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1962", "1971", "1961", "1963"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1879_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1880", "question": "When was All Things Must Pass charted in RPM100 Albums the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1970", "id": "1970"}], "options": ["1962", "1970", "1964", "1965"], "target_options": "1970", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1880_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1881", "question": "When was Led Zeppelin IV charted in UK Albums Chart the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1971", "id": "1971"}], "options": ["1961", "1962", "1971", "1956"], "target_options": "1971", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1881_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1882", "question": "When did Canada start participanting in World Curling Federation the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1960", "1966", "1955", "1961"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1882_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1883", "question": "When did Norway start participanting in International Organization of Journalists the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1937", "1946", "1933", "1940"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1883_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1884", "question": "When did Canada start participanting in World Curling Federation the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1951", "1966", "1941", "1954"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1884_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1885", "question": "When did Norway start participanting in International Convention on Load Lines the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1968", "id": "1968"}], "options": ["1961", "1967", "1964", "1968"], "target_options": "1968", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1885_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1886", "question": "When did Norway start participanting in International Organization of Journalists the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1946", "id": "1946"}], "options": ["1946", "1947", "1945", "1944"], "target_options": "1946", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1886_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1887", "question": "When did Maryland start participanting in National Popular Vote Interstate Compact the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2004", "2007", "2005", "2002"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1887_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1888", "question": "When did Maryland start participanting in National Popular Vote Interstate Compact the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2004", "2002", "2007", "1996"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1888_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1889", "question": "When was Gauss registered in Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1904", "id": "1904"}], "options": ["1902", "1900", "1907", "1904"], "target_options": "1904", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1889_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1890", "question": "When was HMCS Bonaventure registered in United Kingdom the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1943", "id": "1943"}], "options": ["1923", "1943", "1920", "1925"], "target_options": "1943", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1890_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1891", "question": "When was HSC Natchan Rera registered in Japan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2007", "2005", "1996", "2009"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1891_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1892", "question": "When was ADV Ocean Shield registered in Norway the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["1975", "2010", "1966", "1977"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1892_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1893", "question": "When did United States Marine Forces Europe and Africa apply to Africa the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["2008", "2002", "2005", "2003"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1893_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1894", "question": "When did Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement apply to Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2003", "2017", "2007", "2010"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1894_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1895", "question": "When did Mint apply to Canada the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["1997", "2003", "2004", "2010"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1895_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1896", "question": "When did Regional Comprehensive Economic Partnership apply to Japan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2022", "id": "2022"}], "options": ["2022", "2014", "2004", "2015"], "target_options": "2022", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1896_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1897", "question": "When did Protocol against the Illicit Manufacturing of and Trafficking in Firearms apply to Japan the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["2006", "2009", "2017", "2007"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1897_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1898", "question": "When did limited liability partnership apply to United States of America the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1982", "1991", "1970", "1980"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1898_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1899", "question": "When did Forestry Commission apply to England the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1919", "id": "1919"}], "options": ["1905", "1917", "1919", "1915"], "target_options": "1919", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1899_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1900", "question": "When did Forestry Commission apply to England the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1919", "id": "1919"}], "options": ["1916", "1917", "1922", "1919"], "target_options": "1919", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1900_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1901", "question": "When did Hymn of Riego apply to Spain the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1820", "id": "1820"}], "options": ["1808", "1820", "1816", "1814"], "target_options": "1820", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1901_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1902", "question": "When did limited liability partnership apply to United States of America the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1991", "1983", "1986", "1980"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1902_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1903", "question": "When did Miranda warning apply to United States of America the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1959", "1960", "1966", "1957"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1903_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1904", "question": "When did Senate of Finland cease to apply to Finland the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1918", "id": "1918"}], "options": ["1917", "1920", "1918", "1921"], "target_options": "1918", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1904_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1905", "question": "When did Prespa agreement apply to Greece the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2019", "id": "2019"}], "options": ["2009", "2005", "2019", "2010"], "target_options": "2019", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1905_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1906", "question": "When did Protocol III apply to Switzerland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2007", "2005", "2000", "2003"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1906_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1907", "question": "When did French university master apply to France the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1957", "1966", "1959", "1950"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1907_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1908", "question": "When did Charter of the Forest apply to United Kingdom of Great Britain and Ireland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1801", "id": "1801"}], "options": ["1789", "1791", "1779", "1801"], "target_options": "1801", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1908_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1909", "question": "When did Parliament of the United Kingdom apply to United Kingdom of Great Britain and Ireland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1801", "id": "1801"}], "options": ["1785", "1787", "1789", "1801"], "target_options": "1801", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1909_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1910", "question": "When did Act of the Parliament of the United Kingdom apply to United Kingdom of Great Britain and Ireland the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1801", "id": "1801"}], "options": ["1801", "1789", "1783", "1790"], "target_options": "1801", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1910_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1911", "question": "When did Deborah Levi start participating in athletics the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2012", "id": "2012"}], "options": ["2012", "2005", "1995", "2006"], "target_options": "2012", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1911_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1912", "question": "When did World Athletics start participating in athletics the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1912", "id": "1912"}], "options": ["1903", "1904", "1893", "1912"], "target_options": "1912", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1912_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1913", "question": "When did Carlyle Eubank start participating in cross country running the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2001", "id": "2001"}], "options": ["2002", "2001", "1997", "2000"], "target_options": "2001", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1913_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1914", "question": "When did FC Winterthur start participating in cricket the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1908", "id": "1908"}], "options": ["1905", "1915", "1908", "1917"], "target_options": "1908", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1914_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1915", "question": "When did Adriano Panatta start participating in tennis the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1969", "id": "1969"}], "options": ["1966", "1958", "1969", "1964"], "target_options": "1969", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1915_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1916", "question": "When did Ashleigh Barty start participating in cricket the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2015", "id": "2015"}], "options": ["2015", "2013", "2011", "2009"], "target_options": "2015", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1916_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1917", "question": "When did Tennis Borussia Berlin start participating in tennis the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1902", "id": "1902"}], "options": ["1892", "1894", "1902", "1883"], "target_options": "1902", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1917_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1918", "question": "When did Hard Rock Stadium start participating in American football the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1987", "id": "1987"}], "options": ["1950", "1987", "1949", "1939"], "target_options": "1987", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1918_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1919", "question": "When did Ellis Park Stadium start participating in tennis the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1931", "id": "1931"}], "options": ["1921", "1931", "1929", "1928"], "target_options": "1931", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1919_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1920", "question": "When did Rio Haryanto start participating in Formula Renault the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2008", "id": "2008"}], "options": ["1992", "2008", "1994", "1996"], "target_options": "2008", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1920_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1921", "question": "When did Nello Pagani stop participating in motorcycle road racing the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1955", "id": "1955"}], "options": ["1955", "1999", "2005", "2007"], "target_options": "1955", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1921_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1922", "question": "When did Fittipaldi Automotive start participating in Formula One the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1964", "1968", "1975", "1971"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1922_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1923", "question": "When did Paul di Resta start participating in British Formula Renault Championship the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2003", "1998", "1988", "2000"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1923_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1924", "question": "When did Charles Leclerc start participating in FIA Formula 2 Championship the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2017", "id": "2017"}], "options": ["1989", "1981", "2017", "1987"], "target_options": "2017", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1924_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1925", "question": "When did Sebastian Vettel start participating in Formula One the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2007", "2001", "1992", "2003"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1925_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1926", "question": "When did Fittipaldi FD start participating in Formula One the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1975", "id": "1975"}], "options": ["1973", "1976", "1969", "1975"], "target_options": "1975", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1926_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1927", "question": "When did All American Racers start participating in Formula One the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1966", "id": "1966"}], "options": ["1960", "1958", "1966", "1948"], "target_options": "1966", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1927_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1928", "question": "When did Alex Zanardi start participating in Formula One the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1991", "id": "1991"}], "options": ["1994", "1990", "1981", "1991"], "target_options": "1991", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1928_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1929", "question": "When did Marcus Ericsson start participating in Formula BMW the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2007", "id": "2007"}], "options": ["2007", "1982", "1993", "1990"], "target_options": "2007", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1929_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1930", "question": "When did Surtees start participating in Formula One the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1970", "id": "1970"}], "options": ["1963", "1965", "1959", "1970"], "target_options": "1970", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1930_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1931", "question": "When did Esteban Ocon start participating in kart racing the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2006", "2019", "2016", "2015"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1931_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1932", "question": "When did Stoffel Vandoorne start participating in French F4 Championship the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["1982", "1994", "2010", "1991"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1932_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1933", "question": "When did Geoff Duke stop participating in Formula One the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1961", "id": "1961"}], "options": ["2012", "2019", "1961", "2017"], "target_options": "1961", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1933_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1934", "question": "When did Brendon Hartley start participating in New Zealand Formula Ford Championship the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2003", "id": "2003"}], "options": ["2005", "2016", "2003", "2015"], "target_options": "2003", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1934_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1935", "question": "When did Max Verstappen start participating in kart racing the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["1974", "2005", "1969", "1973"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1935_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1936", "question": "When did Pascal Wehrlein start participating in ADAC Formel Masters the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2010", "id": "2010"}], "options": ["2010", "1998", "1997", "1993"], "target_options": "2010", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1936_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1937", "question": "When did Jolyon Palmer start participating in T Cars the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2005", "id": "2005"}], "options": ["1989", "2005", "1996", "1997"], "target_options": "2005", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1937_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1938", "question": "When did Keepmoat Stadium start participating in rugby league the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "2006", "id": "2006"}], "options": ["2005", "1997", "2006", "2003"], "target_options": "2006", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1938_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1939", "question": "When did Jarry Park Stadium stop participating in baseball the last time?", "answer": [{"label": "1976", "id": "1976"}], "options": ["1998", "1976", "1996", "1997"], "target_options": "1976", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1939_ua_en"]}, {"qid": "sup_knowledge_ab_en_1940", "question": "When did Estadio GEBA start participating in association football the first time?", "answer": [{"label": "1908", "id": "1908"}], "options": ["1908", "1903", "1909", "1905"], "target_options": "1908", "lan": "en", "relevent_qid_list": ["time_1940_ua_en"]}]